{"question":"What is the sum of the distinct prime factors of 2007?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"s","noEquations":[1],"equations":"s=3+223","answers":[226.0]}
{"question":"76 is 80% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"76=0.8*x","answers":[95.0]}
{"question":"80% of what number is 33.6?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.80*t=33.6","answers":[42.0]}
{"question":"9x3=?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9*3","answers":[27.0]}
{"question":"if an angle has the measure of 60 degrees, what is the measure of the supplement.?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=180-60","answers":[120.0]}
{"question":"40% of a = 60","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.4*t=60","answers":[150.0]}
{"question":"find the area of a playground that is 20 m long and 15 m wide.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=20*15","answers":[300.0]}
{"question":"how much interest will you have to pay for a credit card balance of $1074 that is 12 months overdue, if a 22% annual rate is charged?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=1074*0.22","answers":[236.28]}
{"question":"Taru surveyed 60 dentists and found that 48 favored the use of flouride toothpaste. Write a ratio to compare the number of dentists favoring the use of a flouride toothpaste to all dentists surveyed.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=48\/60","answers":[0.8]}
{"question":"10 is 30% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10=x*0.3","answers":[33.333]}
{"question":"What percent of 8 is 20?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8*t=20","answers":[2.5]}
{"question":"like 3% of 132, what is the easy way of finding the answer","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=132*0.03","answers":[3.96]}
{"question":"2.5% of what number is 2?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.025*t=2","answers":[80.0]}
{"question":"The forecast for tomorrow says that there is a 37% chance of rain. Describe the complimentary event and predict its probability.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1-0.37","answers":[0.63]}
{"question":"at the track meet, 80 students won ribbons. 48 of the ribbons were 1st place. What percent of the ribbons were 1st place?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=48\/80","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"When NH3 is prepared from 28 g N2 and excess H2, the theoretical yield of NH3 is 34 g. When this reaction is carried out in a given experiment, only 15 g is produced. What is the percentage yield? (Ignore significant figures for this problem.)","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=15\/34","answers":[0.4411764706]}
{"question":"What is 224% OF 320?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"n=2.240*320","answers":[716.8]}
{"question":"20 is what percent of 25?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"25*m=20","answers":[0.8]}
{"question":"Orange county had an estimated population of 883,308 in the 2000 Florida census. Pinellas county had an estimated population of 903,502. What is the difference in population between the two countries?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"d","noEquations":[1],"equations":"d=903502-883308","answers":[20194.0]}
{"question":"27,000 x 9,000","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=27000*9000","answers":[243000000.0]}
{"question":"The area of a rectangle is 437 cm. If its length is 23 cm, what is its width?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"23*m=437","answers":[19.0]}
{"question":"A standard deck of 52 cards is shuffled and one card is drawn and then replaced 15 times. How many times could you expect to draw a black card.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"n=15*0.500","answers":[7.5]}
{"question":"what's 2+2?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"n=2+2","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"The Quans planted a circular flower garder with a diameter of 2.3 m in their backyard, What length of fence, to the nearest tenth of a metre, is needed to completely surround the garden?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3.14*2.3","answers":[7.2]}
{"question":"10 yards tall equals how many feet tall?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=10*3","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"kelly spent 30 minutes in the afternoon waking her dog. What part of one hour did she spent walking her dog? write as fraction","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"r","noEquations":[1],"equations":"r=30\/60","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"n x 50 = 5,000","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"n*50=5000","answers":[100.0]}
{"question":"30% of a number is 12","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.3*n=12","answers":[40.0]}
{"question":"a trapezoid has an area of 72 and height of 9. what is its median","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=72\/9","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"whats 12 divided by 0.05?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=12\/0.05","answers":[240.0]}
{"question":"What is the volume of a regular n-gon prism with a base area of 4.3 m2 and a height of 3m?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4.3*3","answers":[12.9]}
{"question":"How do you figure out these kind of problems: Find the area of the entire circle given the area S of the sector. S= 9.5 m squared, one angle measure of the cirle is 90 degrees","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4*9.5","answers":[38.0]}
{"question":"Find: 41 out of 51 in percentage.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=41\/51","answers":[0.804]}
{"question":"What is 15% of 105?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.150*105","answers":[15.75]}
{"question":"111 is what percent of 1725?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=111\/1725","answers":[0.064]}
{"question":"Find: 32 out of 38 in percentage.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=32\/38","answers":[0.842]}
{"question":"297 divided by 4 is about ?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=297\/4","answers":[74.25]}
{"question":"Jogging shoes are on sale for $9.99. They were $18.95 before the sale. When they went on sale, Ed bought 2 pairs od size 8 1\/2, 1 pair of yellow and the other red and white. How much did he pay for the shoes?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2*9.99","answers":[19.98]}
{"question":"32 is 40% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.400*x=32","answers":[80.0]}
{"question":"Jesse earned $37,800 one year and then received a 3.75% raise. How much did he make the next year?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=37800*1.0375","answers":[39217.5]}
{"question":"what percent of 80 is 96?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"80*x=96","answers":[1.2]}
{"question":"If you have a product that is $178.00. What would 30% be?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=178*0.300","answers":[53.4]}
{"question":"What percent is 1 in a million?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"p=1\/1000000","answers":[0.0]}
{"question":"5 042g - 2.075kg IN to grams","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5042-2075","answers":[2967.0]}
{"question":"A company's 2006 revenue totaled 17,574,428. It costs totaled 14,283,502. What was the company's profit in 2006?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=17574428-14283502","answers":[3290926.0]}
{"question":"The probability that a new advertising campaign will increase sales is assessed as being 0.80. The probability that the cost of developing the new ad campaign can be kept within the original budget allocation is 0.40. Assuming that the two events are independent, find the probability that the cost is kept within budget and the campaign will increase.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.8*0.4","answers":[0.32]}
{"question":"what's 9 times 9? 81","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9*9","answers":[81.0]}
{"question":"A wheelchair ramp has a slope of 1\/10. if its rise is 5 1\/2 feet, what is its run?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5.5*10","answers":[55.0]}
{"question":"The mean of 25 quiz numbers is 73.69. Then every score in the sample receives a bonus of 4 bonus points. What is the new mean (after the bonus)?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=73.69+4","answers":[77.69]}
{"question":"what # is 92 % of 300","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.920*300","answers":[276.0]}
{"question":"how many feet are in 0.11 miles?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.11*5280","answers":[580.8]}
{"question":"Martha leaves home at 9 AM, bicycling at a rate of 24 miles per hour. Two hours later, john leaves, driving at a rate of 48 miles per hour. At what time will John catch up with Martha?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24*2=x","answers":[48.0]}
{"question":"I went pass the 200 pages (exactly 200 pages) to the end. Approximately 4,000 questions!!! Let's create a math problem with it. What is two times a hundred?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2*100=x","answers":[200.0]}
{"question":"0.42 x6.8","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.42*6.8=z","answers":[2.856]}
{"question":"a letter representing a specific number that never changes is called.??? In the expression 7y, the multipliers 7 and y are called.??? Divison can be used to show that 7\/40 can be written as a decimal","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7\/40=x","answers":[0.175]}
{"question":"If $500.00 is 2% of an amount, what was the amount?? I just can't get the answer, and the formula would be nice too. So i have $500.00 they told me it was 2% of an annual wage. What is THAT wage?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"500=x*0.02","answers":[25000.0]}
{"question":"A jet from San Fran to Kansas City, a distance of 2550 km, at a speed of 800 km\/h. Another jet going from KC to SF at 900 km\/h. How long after take off will they meet?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1700*x=2550","answers":[1.5]}
{"question":"To find the simple interest on a loan for 1 year at 12.5%, multiply the amount of the loan by 0.125. What simple interest will you pay on a loan of $1,458 at 12.5% for 1 year?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.125*1458=x","answers":[182.25]}
{"question":"just working out a mathematical sum, am I right by saying the ratio of 240 is 12 or do I have to say it is 20.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"240\/12=x","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"How do you find the height of a triangle with coordinates: X:(2, 1) Y:(5, 3) Z:(7, 1)","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3-1=x","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"mary is 20.0 years old and peter is 26.8 years old their ages corrected to nearest 1\/10 years . find the least difference between thir ages.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"26.8-20=x","answers":[6.8]}
{"question":"What is the greatest common divisor of 118 and 116?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"118-116=x","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"How many integers between 1 and 400 are multiples of 7?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"400\/7=x","answers":[57.1428571429]}
{"question":"I am trying to work out 20% of 520.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"520*0.2=x","answers":[104.0]}
{"question":"what would 1.70 be as a percentage %17 or %170?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.70*1=x","answers":[1.7]}
{"question":"I need to know what 495.923 inches is when converted to feet?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"495.923\/12=x","answers":[41.3269166667]}
{"question":"What's 3 divided by 4 1\/5?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3\/4.2=x","answers":[0.7142857143]}
{"question":"Why is 10 to the power of minus 1 not 1?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10^-1=x","answers":[0.1]}
{"question":"what is the ratio of 447 to 2643?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"447\/2643=x","answers":[0.169]}
{"question":"A man is walking away from a wall at a rate of 1 meter per second. There is a window in the wall at a height of 40 meters above the ground. When the man is 30 meters away from the building, at what rate is his distance from the window changing?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"50.606-50=m","answers":[0.606]}
{"question":"What is 40% of $3,320, paid 40% of the balance?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.40*3320=x","answers":[1328.0]}
{"question":"I got a 52\/70 on a project. What is this grade out of 100 points?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"52\/70=x","answers":[0.7428571429]}
{"question":"I want to charge the middle amount of this for rent. There are 2 other bedrooms available for rent in my building that are all the same. One is going for 750 and the other for 1,000. So what would the middle amount be?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1750\/2=x","answers":[875.0]}
{"question":"What is the of ways that 6 people can be seated in a car on a drive? A car holds exactly 6 people but only 2 of those 6 people can drive this car. What is the number of ways that the 6 people can be seated in the car on a drive?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"120+120=x","answers":[240.0]}
{"question":"What is 20% 0f 20?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20*0.2=x","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"What is the ratio of the length of a side of an equilateral triangle to the triangles perimeter? A. 1 : 1 B. 1 : 2 C. 1 : 3 D. 3 : 1","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1\/3","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"Use the distance formula to find the rate if a car travels 150 miles in 2 1\/2 hours?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"150=x*(2.5)","answers":[60.0]}
{"question":"which number is the decimal form of 7\/20? a:0.45 b:0.36 c:0.35 d:0.035","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7\/20=x","answers":[0.35]}
{"question":"_________ is 35% of 60?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.35*60","answers":[21.0]}
{"question":"How much is 20% of $4,000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2*400=y","answers":[800.0]}
{"question":"Which fraction is equivalent to 25%? 5\/6? 1\/4? 3\/4? 1\/3?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"25\/100=y","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"On a 100 question test, 60 questions involve algebra and 20 questions are difficult. if 8 of the difficult questions involve algebra, how many of the questions that are not difficult do not involve algebra?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"80-52=x","answers":[28.0]}
{"question":"What percent of 10 is 205?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*10=205","answers":[20.5]}
{"question":"9 is what percent of 72?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9\/72=x","answers":[0.125]}
{"question":"A parallelogram has adjacent sides of 176 ft and 312 ft. The altitude to the shorter side is 290 ft. What is the area of the parallelogram?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z=176*290","answers":[51040.0]}
{"question":"30 is 35% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"30=0.35*z","answers":[85.7142857143]}
{"question":"20% of c is 24. What is c?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.2*z=24","answers":[120.0]}
{"question":"Find the area of a parallelogram if the base is 11 inches and the height is 4 inches. a.15 square inches b.22 square inches c.30 square inches d.44 square inches","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=11*4","answers":[44.0]}
{"question":"I have record like this 8.50 m then 8.10 , 8.40, 5.20,.2.10, 2.30 there sum is in decimal 35.40 but i want sum in h minute , what i do?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.40*60=x","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"If my granddad was 37 in 1958 when my dad was born, and my dad is 48 now, what year was my granddad born?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1958-37=x","answers":[1921.0]}
{"question":"The lowest temperature on a winter morning was -8F. Later that same day the temperature reached a high of 24F. By how many degrees Fahrenheit did the temperature increase?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z=(24+8)","answers":[32.0]}
{"question":"What is the probability that a point picked at random, in a square figure [with side lengths of 10 (making the area 100)], will land in the shaded region of the square, (the shaded region's area being 84)?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"84\/100=x","answers":[0.84]}
{"question":"One kilometer is equal to 1000 meters. What fractional part of a kilometer is 700 meters?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"700\/1000=x","answers":[0.7]}
{"question":"What is 64% of 20?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.64*20=x","answers":[12.8]}
{"question":"How do you turn 10 1\/3% into a fraction?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"y=31\/300","answers":[0.1033333333]}
{"question":"I have 2426 square feet of flagstone and it cost 0.25 cents a pound and the flagstone covers about 100 square feet per ton. how many pounds will i need?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24.26*500=y","answers":[12130.0]}
{"question":"If I own 405 shares in a company and there is a total of 600 shares in the company what percentage do I hold.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"405\/600=x","answers":[0.675]}
{"question":"A 42 inch-long guitar is 10.5-feet-long on a stadium screen.A drum is 21 inches wide. How wide is the image on the stadium screen?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10.5\/2=x","answers":[5.25]}
{"question":"I got a 75\/100 on a midterm and the midterm is worth 25% of the overall grade. 25% Participation. - 25% Essay. - 25% Final. - 25% Midterm. So how much of the 25% do I get applied to my grade if I got a 75\/100 on the midterm.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"75*0.25=x","answers":[18.75]}
{"question":"write 20 3\/8% as a decimal, write 819% as a decimal?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"819\/100=y","answers":[8.19]}
{"question":"square root question 5\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a25?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5*5=y","answers":[25.0]}
{"question":"what is 60 percent of 2500?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.6*2500=x","answers":[1500.0]}
{"question":"How many years ago since 2011?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2013-2011=x","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"find a pattern in a string of numbers to determine the next number in the sequence and filling in the blank 16 4 20 24 44?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24+44=x","answers":[68.0]}
{"question":"How many feet is 65.3 inches?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"65.3\/12=x","answers":[5.4416666667]}
{"question":"If nC8 = nC7, find n","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8=(y-7)","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"42.5 billion aluminim cans were recycled in 1988. which represents 54.6%. so how many are produced in one year?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.546*x=42.5","answers":[77.8388278388]}
{"question":"what is 4 percent of 12 ounces?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12*0.04=x","answers":[0.48]}
{"question":"the area of a parallelogram is 39.06 cm2. the base is 9.3 cm. find the height.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"39.06\/9.3=x","answers":[4.2]}
{"question":"Solve: The perimeter of a square with a side length \"s\" is givien by the expression 4s. What is the perimeter of a square with sides of 7.5cm?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7.5*4=x","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"If a pizza is sliced into 8 equal pieces, what is the measure of the central angle represented by each slice? A. 35 degrees . B. 40 degrees . C. 45 degrees . D. 60 degrees.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"360\/8=x","answers":[45.0]}
{"question":"what percent is 200 out of 350?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"200\/350=x","answers":[0.5714285714]}
{"question":"what is 10% of 39.99?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.1*39.99=x","answers":[3.999]}
{"question":"What percent of 50 is 130?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"50*x=130","answers":[2.6]}
{"question":"What is the measure of each angle formed by two perpendicular lines? a. 45 b. 90 c. 180 d. 360","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"360\/4=x","answers":[90.0]}
{"question":"what is 19\/25 as a percent?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"19\/25=x","answers":[0.76]}
{"question":"What is the simple interest on a principal of $640 at the interest rate of 3.8% for 1 year?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"640*0.038=x","answers":[24.32]}
{"question":"monthly income:? percent budgeted: 7 1\/2%. amount budgeted: $240.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"240=0.075*x","answers":[3200.0]}
{"question":"The measure of an interior angle of an equilateral triangle must be _____. A. 60, B. 180 , C. 90, D. 45","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"180\/3=x","answers":[60.0]}
{"question":"What is 4 and 2 sevenths plus 1 and 5 sevenths equaled to?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4.28571428571+1.71428571429=x","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"Normal body temperature is 98 3\/5 degrees Fahrenheit. How many degrees above normal is a 100-degree fever? Use a space between the whole number and fraction.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"100-98.6=x","answers":[1.4]}
{"question":"If 65% of C is 39. what is C?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"y=39\/0.65","answers":[60.0]}
{"question":"Find the number of 2 3\/4 gallon cans which can be filled from a tank containing 90 3\/4 gallons of oil.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"90.75\/2.75=y","answers":[33.0]}
{"question":"how much is 85,000,000,000 divided by 200,000,000?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"85000000000\/200000000=x","answers":[425.0]}
{"question":"What is 7.5% of 280,000,000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.075*280000000=x","answers":[21000000.0]}
{"question":"you need to calculate the circumference after being given the diameter so if its 10cm .","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10*(3.14)=x","answers":[31.4]}
{"question":"A parallelogram has a height of 3 m and a base of 6 m. What is its area?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3*6","answers":[18.0]}
{"question":"You have made $3000 on the sale for your stock. the original cost of the stock was $15000? find the percentage of increase. A. 20% B. 10% C. 5% D. 3%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3000\/15000=x","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"log base(2) 5th root(2)? fraction form?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z=1\/5","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"Kit got 74\/84 on the exam meaning that she earned 74 points out of 80 possible write the decimal equivalent t? Show work.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"74\/84=z","answers":[0.880952381]}
{"question":"What's 20% of $450?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"450*0.2=x","answers":[90.0]}
{"question":"What is the inter quartile range? 31, 32, 33, 36, 42, 45, 49, 53, 57, 58, 64, 67, 69, 76, 78","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"67-36=z","answers":[31.0]}
{"question":"if i worked 23 hours and make 7.50 an hour, how much would my check be?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7.5*(23)=n","answers":[172.5]}
{"question":"what is the difference of 8 and 22?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"22-8=x","answers":[14.0]}
{"question":"I got a 52 out of 60 on my last test, so what would my percent and letter grades be?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=52\/60","answers":[0.8666666667]}
{"question":"What is 4,000,000,000 minus 36,000,000?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4000000000-36000000=x","answers":[3964000000.0]}
{"question":"What do you divide by to find 5% of 200,000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.05*200000=z","answers":[10000.0]}
{"question":"The kite shop buys a certain type of kite for 13 each and sells them for 15.60. What is the percent markup?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2.6\/13=x","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"A parallelogram has a base of 17 cm and a height of 6.5 cm. Find the area?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"17*6.5=x","answers":[110.5]}
{"question":"What is 7300 divided by 156?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7300\/156=x","answers":[46.7948717949]}
{"question":"2 4\/5 divided by 2 1\/10?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(2.8)\/(2.1)=x","answers":[1.3333333333]}
{"question":"What is 20 percent of $75?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.2*75=x","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"Identify the whole: what is 14% of 78? a. 78 b. 14 c. unknown d. cannot be determined from information given","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.14*(78)=x","answers":[10.92]}
{"question":"a family has a budget for washing and drying your clothes $50 per week. If a washer and dryer costs $ 1500, how many weeks that budget are needed to equalize the cost of a washer and dryer?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"y=1500\/50","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"How much is 120% of $68?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.20*68.00=y","answers":[81.6]}
{"question":"The label on a cereal box states the following:. -One serving of cereal contains 17 grams of carbohydrates.. -This number of grams is 6% of the maximum amount of carbohydrates that a person should eat in a day. . Based on this information, which of the following is closest to the maximum amount of carbohydrates that a person should eat in a day? . A. 1.02 grams. B. 2.83 grams. C. 102 grams. D. 283 grams.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6*y=1700","answers":[283.333333333]}
{"question":"Jordan has a bag that contains 246 marbles. There are 51 brown marbles and 195 gray marbles. Estimate the percent of brown marbles in the bag.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"51\/246=x","answers":[0.2073170732]}
{"question":"Let x and y be two (different) independent observations of the band weight from a DNA profile. Assume that X, Y can be taken samples from a Normal distribution with mean 2000 bp and standard deviation 10 bp. Let d = x-y be the difference where d can be assumed to be Normally distributed with mean zero and standard deviation 10\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a2 bp. Find the probability that the observed difference between x and y exceeds 30bp.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1-0.983=m","answers":[0.017]}
{"question":"Estimate 6,235 + 2,505. use rounding?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6235+2505=x","answers":[8740.0]}
{"question":"The water level of a river was 3 ft above normal. After an unusually dry season, the water level is 6 ft below normal. Find the range of the water levels of the river.","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3+6=x","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"Find the area of a parallelogram if the base is 9 inches and the height is 6 inches. (A)54 square inches (B)30 square inches (C) 27 square inches (D)15 square inches","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9*6=x","answers":[54.0]}
{"question":"What percentage is 225 of 265?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"225\/265=x","answers":[0.8490566038]}
{"question":"A local cricket team played 20 matches in 1 season. The percentage of matches won is 25%. What is the number of matches they won?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20*0.25=y","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"How do you convert a number into a percent if the question was to find 36% out of 25?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.36*25=x","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"What percent of 16 is 12.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*16=12","answers":[0.75]}
{"question":"Just say my balance is $256, how do i use the calculator to get 5% of this.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.05*256=y","answers":[12.8]}
{"question":"What is 38% of 2,000,000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.38*2000000=x","answers":[760000.0]}
{"question":"If the measure of one acute angle of a right triangle is 55, then the measure of the other acute angle is? A.25 B.35 C.45 D.55 E.125","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"90-55=x","answers":[35.0]}
{"question":"Evette has 41 1\/2 ft of string. She wants to cut it into pieces 3 3\/4 ft long. How many pieces of string will s?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(41.5)\/(3.75)=x","answers":[11.0666666667]}
{"question":"20% of what number is 10?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.2*z=10","answers":[50.0]}
{"question":"what is 5 1\/4 divided by 3 3\/5?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5.25\/3.6=x","answers":[1.4583333333]}
{"question":"An apartment building produces a net operating income of $34,000 per year. This $34,000 represents a 7% return. What did the building originally cost?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.07*x=34000","answers":[485714.2857140001]}
{"question":"what is 18 percent of 214,643.13?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.18*214643.13=x","answers":[38635.7634]}
{"question":"Add the absolute value of the two integers. Write the complete addition sentence and the answer. |-15|+|21|","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15+21=x","answers":[36.0]}
{"question":"employees new salary is 28,140 after a 5% raise. what was his salary before the raise?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*1.05=28140","answers":[26800.0]}
{"question":"An adult cat has a body mass of 3500 grams. It can eat up to 8% of its body mass in food each day. How many grams of food can the cat eat each day? Use estimation to justify that your answer is reasonable.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3500*0.08=x","answers":[280.0]}
{"question":"20 is what % of 5000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20=x*5000","answers":[0.004]}
{"question":"What is the d value of the following arithmetic sequence? 27, 41, 55, 69, 83, 97-","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"41-27=x","answers":[14.0]}
{"question":"The smallest natural number that is divisible by the numbers: 2, 3, 4, 6, 8, and 9?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8*9=x","answers":[72.0]}
{"question":"log3 27-log9 9?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3-1=z","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"A triangle has vertices at points with coordinates of (2.1), (9.1) and (3.9). What is the area of the triangle in square units? A. 7 B. 7 1\/2 C. 14 D. 27 E. 28","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"56\/2=z","answers":[28.0]}
{"question":"55 is what percent of 220?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"55\/220=x","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"3570 is 42% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3570=0.42*x","answers":[8500.0]}
{"question":"Calculate the range of the following numbers. Round to the nearest whole number if necessary. 15, 2, 49, 22, 63?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"63-2=x","answers":[61.0]}
{"question":"1 km equivalent a 10,000 cm?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.000*100000=x","answers":[100000.0]}
{"question":"What's 15 % of $145,000,00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"14500000*0.15=x","answers":[2175000.0]}
{"question":"12 1\/2% of 8 is?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.125*(8)=y","answers":[1.0]}
{"question":"Find the area of a rectangle whose vertices are (0, 0), (8, 0),(0, 5) and (8, 5)?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5*8=z","answers":[40.0]}
{"question":"What is 20% of 80?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(0.2)*(80)=y","answers":[16.0]}
{"question":"The Indianapolis Motor Speedway has 3,200,000 bricks that lie beneath the 2.5 miles of track. Find how many bricks lie under one mile of track at the race track. How do I do this?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3200000\/2.5=x","answers":[1280000.0]}
{"question":"4 is what percent of 50?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/50=x","answers":[0.08]}
{"question":"Express 7\/4 as a percent.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7\/4=x","answers":[1.75]}
{"question":"What is the sum of 1 and 1?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1+1","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"If f(x) = x + 2, find the value of x if f(x) = 12.","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x+2=12","answers":[10.0]}
{"question":"what percent of 54 is 135?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*54=135","answers":[2.5]}
{"question":"I have the number 640 and the number 80. I need to figure out what percentage 80 is of 640.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"p*640=80","answers":[0.125]}
{"question":"what is the reciprocal of 0.8.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1\/0.8","answers":[1.25]}
{"question":"what is the answer to 30 divided by 8 as a fraction?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"f","noEquations":[1],"equations":"f=30\/8","answers":[3.75]}
{"question":"20% of the number is 3. Find the number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.2*x=3","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"5 times a number equals 20what is the number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5*n=20","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"15 is 25% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15=0.25*x","answers":[60.0]}
{"question":"36 is 60% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"36=0.6*x","answers":[60.0]}
{"question":"A 3- digit number in which one digit is the average of the other two digits is called an average number. 456 is an average number because 5 is the average of 4 and 6. How many three digit average numbers are there?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"n=9*5","answers":[45.0]}
{"question":"what is 8% of 2,000.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2000*0.08","answers":[160.0]}
{"question":"what's 8% of 5.00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.08*5","answers":[0.4]}
{"question":"what percent of 50 is 6?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*50=6","answers":[0.12]}
{"question":"What percent of 80 is 50?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*80=50","answers":[0.625]}
{"question":"Megan likes to jog around a duck pond near her house. The distance around the pond is 0.4 mi. How many laps around the pond are necessary to run 5 mi?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=5\/0.4","answers":[12.5]}
{"question":"If 60 is 40% of a number, what is that number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"60=x*0.4","answers":[150.0]}
{"question":"In 1960, a farmer was paid $1 for one bushel of corn. In 2000, the price of one bushel of corn was 185% of the 1960 price. How much was a farmer paid for one bushel of corn in 2000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=1.85*1","answers":[1.85]}
{"question":"A softball players batting average is the ratio of hits made to the number of times at bat. If Ann's batting average is 0.320, how many hits would she expect to get in 25 times at bat?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t\/25=0.32","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"how to solve 6% of 19.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.06*19","answers":[1.14]}
{"question":"14 is what percent of 84?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"14=t*84","answers":[0.167]}
{"question":"what percent of 240 is 60?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t*240=60","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"The lateral area of a rectangular prism with height of 4 feet is 60 ft2. What is the perimeter of the base?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t*4=60","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"Line RS bisects PQ at point R. Find RQ if PQ = 14 centimeters?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=14\/2","answers":[7.0]}
{"question":"what is 15 percent of $49.99?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=49.99*0.15","answers":[7.499]}
{"question":"The three best bands each have 36 marchers. Each member receives a ribbon. use the Distributive Property to explain how to figure out how many ribbons are needed. Then solve.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=36*3","answers":[108.0]}
{"question":"A rope is 42 feet long, How many yards is that?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=42\/3","answers":[14.0]}
{"question":"45 divided by 6 =?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=45\/6","answers":[7.5]}
{"question":"4 to the negative 2 power.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4^(-2)","answers":[0.0625]}
{"question":"4,000 grams = kilograms? (1 gram = 0.001 kilograms)","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4000*0.001","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"A survey asked cat owners, does you cat have bad breath? out of 200 owners 80 answered yes to this question. what percent of the cat owners answered yes?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=80\/200","answers":[0.4]}
{"question":"15 is what percent of 24?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15=t*24","answers":[0.625]}
{"question":"Tim wants to put a rug in his room. The length of his room is 2 feet and the width of his room is 5 feet. How much rug will Tim need? Find the area.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=2*5","answers":[10.0]}
{"question":"if 145 is 15% of the whole, what is the whole?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"145=0.15*t","answers":[966.6666666667]}
{"question":"I have 37 grams total. I have 6% Thiamin how do I figure out the number of grams of thiamin?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=37*0.06","answers":[2.22]}
{"question":"what 12% of 240 is?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=240*0.12","answers":[28.8]}
{"question":"10 pounds lost in 4 weeks. That is a ratio. How would you make it a rate?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=10\/4","answers":[2.5]}
{"question":"What is 24 divided by 8?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=24\/8","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"30 is what percent of 150?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"30=t*150","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"The area of a rectangle is 2cm squared, If the length of the rectangleis 8cm, what is the width of the rectange?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8*t=2","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"At a rate if 7% what is the sales tax on a car priced at 9500?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=9500*0.07","answers":[665.0]}
{"question":"What is 14% of $25.99? (Rounded to the nearest cent)?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=25.99*0.14","answers":[3.6386]}
{"question":"I have a car that gives 16 mpg. Let x be the number of miles driven on 50 gallons of gas. I need to show both the set up of the proportion and the steps to solve. Including the units with my answer.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x\/50=16","answers":[800.0]}
{"question":"what is 0.8 divided by 4?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.8\/4","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"If I have $200,000 to spend, but I have allocated 8.55% of that in one month, how much is that 8.55%.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=200000*0.0855","answers":[17100.0]}
{"question":"35% of what number is 500?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t*0.35=500","answers":[1428.57]}
{"question":"Glenda has a $40 gift card to a cafe that sells her favourite tuna sandwich for $3.75 after tax. What are the possible numbers of tuna sandwiches can she buy with her gift card?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=40\/3.75","answers":[10.667]}
{"question":"the length and breadth of a lawn is 20m and 4.8m. what is the ratio of length to breadth?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=20\/4.8","answers":[4.167]}
{"question":"Layla has to read 48 pages for her history class before the end of the week. So far, she has read 15 pages. What fraction has she read?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=15\/48","answers":[0.3125]}
{"question":"6 divided by 1824?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6\/1824","answers":[0.003]}
{"question":"82 divided by 4?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=82\/4","answers":[20.5]}
{"question":"Recently, the exchange rate for U.S dollars to Indian rupees was $1 = 43.43 rupees. How many dollars would you get for 860 rupees?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=860\/43.43","answers":[19.802]}
{"question":"what is the probability that the number 4 will land face up in a cube with six sides.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1\/6","answers":[0.167]}
{"question":"How many miles are equal to 32,000 ft?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=32000\/5280","answers":[6.061]}
{"question":"Tia wants to plant a garden that will attract butterflies. She decides to plant parsley, dill, and fennel to attract swallowtail butterflies; scarlet milkweed to attract monarch butterflies; and thistles for Painted Lady butterflies. If Tia's garden is 30 feet long, how many feet should it be in width so that the area is 600 square feet?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"30*t=600","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"What is 15 over 100 reduced? then converted to a percent.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=15\/100","answers":[0.15]}
{"question":"how many millilitres are in 1,211 litres?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1211*1000","answers":[1211000.0]}
{"question":"The weekly milk order for the Tranquility Inn includes 40 gallons of low-fat milk and 15 gallons of chocolate milk. What is the ratio of the number of low-fat gallons to chocolate gallons in the Tranquility Inns weekly milk order?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=40\/15","answers":[2.6666666667]}
{"question":"if i make 600 hundred dollars a month, how much would i make in 11 months","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=600*11","answers":[6600.0]}
{"question":"how would i solve this type of problem 7 2\/5% of x is equal to74, solving for (x)?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.074*x=74","answers":[1000.0]}
{"question":"what is 20 percent off of 59.99?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=59.99*0.2","answers":[11.998]}
{"question":"it is based on theoretical probability and it says jar contains 50 marbles that are the same size. there are 15 blue, 8 yellow, and 27 red marbles. and then question says p(blue).","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=15\/50","answers":[0.3]}
{"question":"what is 2 plus 2?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2+2","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"24.5 is 35% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24.5=0.35*t","answers":[70.0]}
{"question":"In a Gallup poll of 1,038 adults, 540 said that second-hand smoke is very harmful. What is the percentage of adults who said second-hand smoke is very harmful?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=540\/1038","answers":[0.52]}
{"question":"A bag of chocolate covered candy, contains 23% green, 37% red, 22% blue, and 18% yellow candies. Marcus put 350 candies in a bowl. Find the total number of blue candies.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=350*0.22","answers":[77.0]}
{"question":"Calculate 33 1\/3% of 60?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=60*0.333","answers":[19.98]}
{"question":"a mountain climber ascends a mountain to its peak. the peak is 12,740 ft above sea level. the climber then descends 200 ft to meet a fellow climber. find the climber's elevation above sea level after meeting the other climber","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x+200=12740","answers":[12540.0]}
{"question":"An object has a mass of 57.6 g. Find the object's density, given that its volume is 40.25 cm^3.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"d","noEquations":[1],"equations":"d=57.6\/40.25","answers":[1.431]}
{"question":"Uncle Smith bought a shirt at 45% off. He saved $11.70. What was the sale price of the shirt?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m*0.45=11.7","answers":[26.0]}
{"question":"If a class collects $155 toward a fundraising goal of $775, what fraction represents the class's progress toward its goal?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"f","noEquations":[1],"equations":"f=155\/775","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"8 * 6 4\/5=?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8*6.8=x","answers":[54.4]}
{"question":"If Lana sells a stereo for $735.00 and makes $27 commission. What percentage commission does Lana get paid?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=27\/735","answers":[0.0367]}
{"question":"Solve X + 25 = 36","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x+25=36","answers":[11.0]}
{"question":"Water moves past a 10cm board in 1.3 seconds. How far the water will travel in a second.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=10\/1.3","answers":[7.692]}
{"question":"A craftsman makes miniature replicas of Victorian furniture. The scale model of a table that he made is 3 inches long. The full-size table is 36 inches long. What is the models scale?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"s","noEquations":[1],"equations":"s=3\/36","answers":[0.0833333333]}
{"question":"What percent of 250 is 128?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"250*x=128","answers":[0.512]}
{"question":"It takes two feet of ribbon to make a large bow. Jeannette has 250 feet of ribbon. How many bows can she make??","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"n=250\/2","answers":[125.0]}
{"question":"Suppose 75% of 6-year-olds weigh under 46 lb. How many 6-yearolds would you expect to weigh under 46 lb in a class of 32 age-six first-graders?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=0.75*32","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"the football team gained 23 yards on 1st down and were penalized 5 yards on 2nd down. What was the net result?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=23-5","answers":[18.0]}
{"question":"0.9% of 116","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.009*116","answers":[1.004]}
{"question":"suppose you and a friend are working for a nursery planting trees. Together you can plant 8 trees per hour. What is the greatest number of hours you and your friend would need to plant at most 40 trees?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=40\/8","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"What is 25% of 200?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=0.25*200","answers":[50.0]}
{"question":"Jan has 5 notebooks and 3 pens. How many different combinations of notebooks and pens could Jan possibly use in school one day?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"n=5*3","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"2.25 Divided by 3.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=2.25\/3","answers":[0.75]}
{"question":"3 divided by 4.155","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3\/4.155","answers":[0.7220216606]}
{"question":"288+N=106","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"288+n=106","answers":[-182.0]}
{"question":"what's the grade of the slope? The road is 24 ft. the hill is 3 ft.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=3\/24","answers":[0.125]}
{"question":"Arif and Keisha go to a restaurant for dinner. Their meal total $13.75 The Sales Tax is 5%. How much tax is added?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=13.75*0.05","answers":[0.688]}
{"question":"Of the sixth-grade students surveyed, 12% bring their lunches to school. Suppose 24 sixth-graders do this. How many sixth-graders are at the school?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.12*m=24","answers":[200.0]}
{"question":"45 is what percent of 66?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"66*m=45","answers":[0.682]}
{"question":"what is 60% of 125?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=0.6*125","answers":[75.0]}
{"question":"A Heron can travel an average of 400 km in 10 h. What is the rate of change of distance?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=400\/10","answers":[40.0]}
{"question":"If the diameter is 21, then what is the circumference?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=3.14*21","answers":[65.973]}
{"question":"5,682 divided by 900,854,023","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5682\/900854023","answers":[0.00000631]}
{"question":"there are 26 7th grade boys and 34 7th grade girls. there are also 30 8th grade boys and 22 8th grade girls. write in simplest form what the ratio is for 7th grade boys and 8th grade boys.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"r","noEquations":[1],"equations":"r=26\/30","answers":[0.8666666667]}
{"question":"Events A and B are mutually exclusive. Also, P(A) = 0.54 and P(B) = 0.09. What is P(A or B)?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=0.54+0.09","answers":[0.63]}
{"question":"convert 2.54 cm to meters","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2.54\/100","answers":[0.0254]}
{"question":"what is the number of months in 7 years?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"n=12*7","answers":[84.0]}
{"question":"Estimate the total weight of 2 boxes that weigh 9.4 lb and 62.6 lb using rounding and compatible numbers. Which estimate is closer to the actually weight?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=9.4+62.6","answers":[72.0]}
{"question":"what is 30\/80 simplified?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"f","noEquations":[1],"equations":"f=30\/80","answers":[0.375]}
{"question":"m = ____ cm","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=1\/10","answers":[0.1]}
{"question":"3 is 60% of what?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m*0.6=3","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"A carjack requires a force of 110 pounds to lift a 2,500 pound car. in simplest form, what is the ratio of the car's weight to the force required to lift the car?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"r","noEquations":[1],"equations":"r=2500\/110","answers":[22.7272727273]}
{"question":"A televised debate is being taped using two independent sound systems. The first has a 0.03 probability of failure during taping; the second has a 0.05 probability of failure. What is the probability that both will fail during taping?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"p=0.03*0.05","answers":[0.0015]}
{"question":"The scale factor between figure A and figure B is 0.25. If one side length of figure B is fifty-six yards, what is the corresponding side length of figure A?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=56*0.25","answers":[14.0]}
{"question":"If m varies directly as y and m is 6 when y is 36, find the constant of variation.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6=36*x","answers":[0.1666666667]}
{"question":"one year the postage rates for sending one ounce of mail first class was increased from 25 cents to 29 cents. The percent of increase in the 29 cent postage was most nearly to? A. 14 percent B. 16 percent C. 18 percent D . 20 percent","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4\/25","answers":[0.16]}
{"question":"a spinner has regions 1 through 15 what's the probability the spinne will stop on an even # or a multiple of 3","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=10\/15","answers":[0.6666666667]}
{"question":"how do you find the surface area of a triangular prism? Triangle Base 6cm, triangle height 5.2cm, prism height 16cm.","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"s","noEquations":[1],"equations":"s=33+297.12","answers":[330.12]}
{"question":"would you work out? A 5 litre can of paint covers 28 m2. A person buys 3 cans of paint to cover 70 m2. What percentage of the paint does the person use? Th","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2.5\/3","answers":[0.833]}
{"question":"97.5 is 39% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*0.390=97.5","answers":[250.0]}
{"question":"57% off of $99.99, the new cost?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=99.99*0.43","answers":[42.996]}
{"question":"what is 100,000,000 subtracted from 2?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=100000000-2","answers":[99999998.0]}
{"question":"what is 7 1\/4 pounds in ounces?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=7.25*16","answers":[116.0]}
{"question":"re are 100 balls in a hat. 6.0 of them are RED, and 94.0 are BLACK. T ee are drawn at random with replacement . culate the expected number of red balls in 3 draws.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3*0.06","answers":[0.18]}
{"question":"equal sums of maony were lend at simple intrest at 11% per annum for 3 1\/2 years and 4 1\/2 years respectively. If the difference in interests for 2 periods was 412.50$, find each sum.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*0.110=412.5","answers":[3750.0]}
{"question":"ruck travels 40 miles from point A to point B in exactly 1 hour. When the truck is halfway between point A and point B, a car starts from point A and travels at 50 miles per hour. How many miles has the car traveled when the truck reaches point B?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=50\/2","answers":[25.0]}
{"question":"Suppose that a random variable has standard deviation equal to 7. Each possible value of this random variable is first multiplied by 6, and then 42 is added to it. what is the standard deviation of the distribution of the new variable?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=7*6","answers":[42.0]}
{"question":"A cube 4 inches on each side is painted white and cut into 64 smaller cubes with equal volume. How many small cubes are painted white on exactly 2 faces.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2*12","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"if a cheetah ran 70 mph. how many seconds would it take to reach 400 yards at 70 mph?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=400\/34.222","answers":[11.688]}
{"question":"In 1999, 189 physical therapists ran in the new york city marathon. This was 1048 fewer than the number of engineers who ran. How many engineers ran in the marathon?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=189+1048","answers":[1237.0]}
{"question":"what is 3% of 44 lbs?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=44*0.030","answers":[1.32]}
{"question":"find the number whose 50% is 75.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*0.500=75","answers":[150.0]}
{"question":"What is 42 divided by 4?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=42\/4","answers":[10.5]}
{"question":"How much is 15% of $250?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=250*0.150","answers":[37.5]}
{"question":"What is the r value of the following geometric sequence? 40, 20, 10, 5,.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=20\/40","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"Two coins are tossed 20 times and the number of tails is observed. Outcome 2 1 0. Frequency 5 12 3. Compute the empirical probability that exactly one tail occurred.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"p=12\/20","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"What is 20% of 120 square feet?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.200*120","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"A survey of 21,400 people found that 1,892 stubbed a toe at least once in 2007. Based on those figures, what are the odds of someone stubbing their toe on any given day? For example, what are the odds of someone stubbing their toe tomorrow?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"p=1892\/21400","answers":[0.088]}
{"question":"15% is what number of 75?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"75\/x=0.150","answers":[500.0]}
{"question":"find the probability that is not a multiple of 3. A box contains 7 balls numbered 1 to 7 If a ball is taken at random from the box.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5\/7","answers":[0.7142857143]}
{"question":"How many volts are represented by 200 millivolts?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=200\/1000","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"1 mi is equivalent to 1609 m so 55 mph is?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=55*1609","answers":[88495.0]}
{"question":"find the average of four consecutive odd integers whose sum is 112. A. 25 B. 29 C. 31 D. 28 E. 30","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4*x=112","answers":[28.0]}
{"question":"work out a % of phone calls. take the total of calls on monday (58) and divide it by the total calls of the week (277).","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"p=58\/277","answers":[0.209]}
{"question":"A cone has a volume of 45 ft3. The volume of a cylinder with the same height and a congruent base is _____ ft3.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=45*3","answers":[135.0]}
{"question":"If John scores 20% of his team's points in a basketball game, how many points does the team score if John scores 14 points? A: 66 B: 74 C: 72 D: 70","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"14\/x=0.200","answers":[70.0]}
{"question":"the total production of Chairs and stools is 285,000. Chairs accounting for 120,000 and stools 165,000. How do I find out what percentage of chairs makes up final production? Ma","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=120000\/285000","answers":[0.4210526316]}
{"question":"2 to the negitive 2 power?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2^(-2)","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"a grocery store sells $500 in baked goods, $3,000 in groceries, $1500 in dairy productions,$1,000 in produce, and $2500 in the meat , By how many dollars do the sales in the meat department exceed the sales in the dairy department ? a.800 b.1000 c.1050 d.250 e.900","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2500-1500","answers":[1000.0]}
{"question":"If I'm paying $4 for 250 business cards, what am I paying per card and how did you find that value?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4\/250","answers":[0.016]}
{"question":"Solve the equation: 7 x = 42? A. x = - 6 B. x = 6 C. x = 7 D. x = - 7","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7*x=42","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"The world population was 4.2 billion people in 1982. The population in 1999 reached 6 billion. Find the percent of change from 1982 to 1999.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1.8\/4.2","answers":[0.4285714286]}
{"question":"A drawing of a fish has a scale of 2 cm:1 m. The drawing of the fish is 3 cm long. How long is the fish?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3\/2","answers":[1.5]}
{"question":"In 1996, the civilian labor force of the United states included 127 milion people, and 5% were uneployed. How many people in the civilian labor force were uneployed?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"n=127000000*0.050","answers":[6350000.0]}
{"question":"what is 8% of $20,000.00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.080*20000.00","answers":[1600.0]}
{"question":"What is the answer for 70 divided by 196 in simplest form?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=70\/196","answers":[0.3571428571]}
{"question":"The camp light has a switch that will allow the light to operate one, two, or all three bulbs at the same time. The batteries will last 6 hours with only one bulb burning and 3 hours with two bulbs burning. How long will the batteries last if all three bulbs are on? (Round your answer to the nearest tenth.)","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=6\/3","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"The number which best completes the sequence1 1\/2 , 5 , 10 1\/2 , 18?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=161+324","answers":[485.0]}
{"question":"how tall in feet is 151 cm and a half?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=151.5\/30.48","answers":[4.97]}
{"question":"A buyer's agent earned a $2,400 commision on a sale. If the total commision paid on the deal was 5.5%, what was the sales price of the house? A. $480,000 B. $43,636 C. $87,272 D. $26,400","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*0.055=2400","answers":[43636.0]}
{"question":"1999, the population of Alaska was 0.62 million. Write the population as a whole number.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.62*1000000","answers":[620000.0]}
{"question":"20 out of 30 is what percentage?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=20\/30","answers":[0.667]}
{"question":"How do you get 64 divided by 0.08?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=64\/0.08","answers":[800.0]}
{"question":"how many positive 2-digit integers can be formed using the digits {1, 2, 3} if repetition of digits is not allowed?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3*2","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"pose the payoff of a $1 ticket in a tri-state lottery game is $500 with a probability of .00005 and $0 the rest of the time. Let X be the random variable that represents a payoff. What is the payoff of x, on average?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=500*0.0005","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"You toss 3 coins. What is the probability that you get exactly 2 heads, given that you get at least one head?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3\/7","answers":[0.4285714286]}
{"question":"A rock has a density of 4 g\/ml and a mass of 16 grams. What is the volume this rock occupies?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=16\/4","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"What is 30% of $50?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=50*0.300","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"For example, if there is a 75 % chance of achieving something on a trial and error basis, what is the chances that you will succeed both times?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.75*0.75","answers":[0.563]}
{"question":"How many square feet is 7'6\" by 7'6\"?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"X","noEquations":[1],"equations":"X=7.5*7.5","answers":[56.25]}
{"question":"If a cylinder holds a volume of 100 cm3, and is 30 cm tall, what is the area of the bottom of the cylinder?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=100\/30","answers":[3.3333333333]}
{"question":"what is 20 percent of 150,000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=150000*0.200","answers":[30000.0]}
{"question":"how to solve 5.4 divided by 7.2?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5.4\/7.2","answers":[0.75]}
{"question":"What's the probability of Larry having fewer than two accidents a month? \"Larry Fitzgearld, the new parking attendant, believes the probability there will be no accidents in a given month is 5%. The probability of his having one, two or three acidents in a given month is 43%, 31%, and 21% respectively. What is the probability of Larry having fewer than two accidents a month?\"","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"p=0.050+0.430","answers":[0.48]}
{"question":"ase find the common difference in the arithmetic sequence: 205, 199, 193 ...","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=199-205","answers":[-6.0]}
{"question":"In order to lift a load a distance of 6m by a pulley, it is necessary to move the effort load by 3m. What would be the velocity ratio?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3\/6","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"ad to convert 1\/6% into a decimal. I","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1\/0.060","answers":[16.667]}
{"question":"marion deposited 800 dollars in a savings account. one year later, the teller posted $56 in her savings book.at what rate of interest was she paid on her savings ?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"800*x=56","answers":[0.07]}
{"question":"ips earns $9 per hour for helping his grampa with his yard work. write and solve a multiplcation problem to find how many hours he must help his grandpa to earn 54$","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9*x=54","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"A car travels 20 meters east in 1.0 second. The displacement of the car at the end of this 1.0-second interval?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=20*1.0","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"what is the percent when you divide 18.5 by 20?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"p=18.5\/20","answers":[0.925]}
{"question":"What is 21\/30 in simplest form?(Fraction)? 2over 30 in simplest form?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=21\/30","answers":[0.7]}
{"question":"find the number of ways all of the event can occur. event 1: 1 way, event 2: 3 ways","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1*3","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"in a deck of 52 cards. what is the probability of getting a 3 or 9?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"p=8\/52","answers":[0.1538461538]}
{"question":"A block of wood has a density of 0.6 g\/cm3 and a volume of 1.2 cm3. What is the mass of the block of wood?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=0.6*1.2","answers":[0.72]}
{"question":"what is 11 over 13 as a percent grade?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=11\/13","answers":[0.846]}
{"question":"10 is 5% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10=0.050*x","answers":[200.0]}
{"question":"what percentage would be 35 out of 42?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=35\/42","answers":[0.833]}
{"question":"what is the probability of picking an ace from a standard deck of 52 cards? A1\/10 B 1\/11 C.1\/12 D.1\/13","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"p=4\/52","answers":[0.0769230769]}
{"question":"What percent of 2.4 is 5.2?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*2.4=5.2","answers":[2.167]}
{"question":"the perimeter of a square is equal to 4s, where s is the length of one side. If the value of s is 7 feet, find the perimeter of the square.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4*7","answers":[28.0]}
{"question":"what is 18% of $225?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.180*225","answers":[40.5]}
{"question":"culate the percentage of 15, 88 of the number 91, 28 -","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=15888\/91285","answers":[0.174]}
{"question":"if i bought an xbox360 for \u00c3\u00af\u00c2\u00bf\u00c2\u00a1250, and sold it for \u00c3\u00af\u00c2\u00bf\u00c2\u00a1135, what percentage did i sell for?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=135\/250","answers":[0.54]}
{"question":"for $186.5, how must GST for 7 % ?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.07*186.50","answers":[13.055]}
{"question":"there have been 67 shuttle missions and 2 have failed. to the nearest 10th of a percent what percentage were successful?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=65\/67","answers":[0.97]}
{"question":"next number in sequence: 3, 15, 35, 63?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9*11","answers":[99.0]}
{"question":"this is the question. 35.3 g= mass. 1.60g\/cm cubed , i have to find the volume?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"v","noEquations":[1],"equations":"v=35.3\/1.6","answers":[22.063]}
{"question":"How old would a 13 year old be if they lived on Jupiter? 1 Jupiter year = 12 Earth years","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=13\/12","answers":[1.0833333333]}
{"question":"re are some sweets in a bag 18 of the sweats are toffees, 12 of the sweets are mints write down the ratio of the number of toffees to the number of mints give your ratio in the simplest form","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=18\/12","answers":[1.5]}
{"question":"t is the number of numbers that can be made from the numbers two and three such that the number contains 4 digits. 3, 2323, 2332, 3322, 3232, 3223","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"n=16-10","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"55% are skiers. 45% are snowboarders. On the opening day 200 patrons are randomly interviewed. How many of these patrons would have been expected to be snowboarders?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=200*0.450","answers":[90.0]}
{"question":"assume x collect 64 cigratte butts in a day. he can make 1 cigarette if he gets 8 butts. how many cigrette can he somke?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=64\/8","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"The density of silver at 20\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0C is 10.5 g\/cm3. What is the volume of a 73 g bar of silver?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"73\/x=10.5","answers":[6.9523809524]}
{"question":"after saturday's game, the entire High city High School football team went to eat at a restaurant. Altogether, 35 players ordered hamburgers, 28 ordered a milkshake and a hamburger. 3 ordered only a milkshake. How many players are on the team?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=35+3","answers":[38.0]}
{"question":"jan, ellen, rob, heather, and chris are finalists in a contest. the contest has prizes for 1st and 2nd place. how many different ways can the prizes be awarded?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5*4","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"You need 2.50lb of meat that sells for $2.70\/lb. Use this price to determine a factor to calculate the cost of the meat you need.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2.7*2.5","answers":[6.75]}
{"question":"the middle of the golf course there is a large storage lake, which is used to water the golf course. if the surface area of the lake is 550 square metre and the average depth is 2.5 metres, what is the volume of the lake??","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=550*2.5","answers":[1375.0]}
{"question":"The bottom area of a box is cm2 sand it iecm high n.gure out how much soil will the box hold (.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=576*12","answers":[6912.0]}
{"question":"Why is it when you divide 80 by 12?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=80\/12","answers":[6.6666666667]}
{"question":"If there is a possible total score of 740 points and a student has 694.4, what is their total percentage score?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=694.4\/740","answers":[0.938]}
{"question":"It has been found that 60 percent of homes subscribe to a cable service including the program \"Cooking with Math\". However, of these subscribers, 13 percent never watch \"Cooking with Math\", while 35 percent claim to watch it more than 5 times per week. Find the probability (as a decimal value) that a randomly selected home subscribes to a cable service including the program \"Cooking with Math\" and watches it more than 5 times per week.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.600*0.350","answers":[0.21]}
{"question":"What is 30% of $150.00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=150*0.300","answers":[45.0]}
{"question":"Find the area of a rectangle if its length measures 12 centimeters and its width measures 14 centimeters?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=12*14","answers":[168.0]}
{"question":"Sterling silver is composed of 92.5% silver and 7.5 % copper. If a sterling silver ring was found to contain 6.55 g of silver, what is the mass of the ring?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6.55\/0.925","answers":[7.081]}
{"question":"estaurant has 25 entrees and 40 side dishes. If Mary wants to order one entree and one side dish, how many different combinations of entree and side dish could she order? T","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=25*40","answers":[1000.0]}
{"question":"what is 4,000,000 divided by 12?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4000000\/12","answers":[333333.3333333333]}
{"question":"the perimeter of an rectangle is 24 cm ( 9 length and 3 width) what is the area of this rectangle?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"s","noEquations":[1],"equations":"s=9*3","answers":[27.0]}
{"question":"Assume that the box contains 10 balls: 4 red, 1 green, and 5 blue. Two balls are drawn at random, one after the other without replacement. What is the probability that the first ball was blue, given that the second was red?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"p=5\/9","answers":[0.5555555556]}
{"question":"42 is 60% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"42=0.6*x","answers":[70.0]}
{"question":"each bottle of water is 500 ml. how many ounces is in one 500 ml bottle of water?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=500\/29.57","answers":[16.909]}
{"question":"(-4)^3(-4). How do i solve this?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=(-4)^4","answers":[256.0]}
{"question":"Two angles are supplementary. The first angle measures 40\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0. What is the measurement of the second angle? A50\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0 120\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0 60\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0 140\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=180-40","answers":[140.0]}
{"question":"How much is 1.8 minutes?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1.8*60","answers":[108.0]}
{"question":"How many possible combonations are there of these 4 numbers?k I have these four numbers 2,2,5 ,7 a nd I want to how to find out how many combonations there are for these four numbers and maybe a site where I can enter them in and it lists all the combonations for me.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3*2","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"is 6\/18 a equal fraction to 1\/8 or 1\/3?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6\/18","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"Annual Premium per $1000. Age Male Age Female 10 Year 20 Year Straight Life 25 28 3.25 5.84 15.66 30 33 3.82 7.93 18.98 35 38 4.55 10.33 22.38 How much is the life insurance premium for a 30 year old male, $320,000 straight life policy?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=18.98*320","answers":[6073.6]}
{"question":"What is 15 over 24 in simplest form?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=15\/24","answers":[0.625]}
{"question":"sales force of a business consists of 10 men and 10 women . A production unit of 6 people is set up at random .WatWis the probability that it will consist of all men ?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=210\/38760","answers":[0.0054179567]}
{"question":"Use the arithmetic sequence of numbers 2, 4, 6, 8, 10. to find the following: What is d , the difference between any two consecutive terms?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"d","noEquations":[1],"equations":"d=4-2","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"Jodi earned $22.75 for 3 1\/2 hours. What was her hourly wage?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=22.75\/3.5","answers":[6.5]}
{"question":"5 times 15?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5*15","answers":[75.0]}
{"question":"what is 6 divide by 131?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6\/131","answers":[0.0458015267]}
{"question":"The United States Is The World's Leading Exporter Of Wheat With Approximately 27.8 Billion Metric Tons Per r. Suppose Turkey Exports 10 % Of The U.S. Total. About How Many Metric Tons Are Exported By Turkey ? . 18 Billion B.8 Billion C.5 Billion D.3 Billion","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=27.8*0.100","answers":[2.78]}
{"question":"There were 2 identical flights of steps. For the first flight of steps, Sam walked up some steps and ran 7 steps in 67 seconds. For the 2nd flight of steps, Sam walked up some steps and ran 5 steps in 43conds. How long will Sam take to walk up both flights of steps?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=67+43","answers":[110.0]}
{"question":"ox of tape conatins 1075 ft of tape, each roll contains 10 3\/4 ft. how many rolls of tape are in the box.?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1075\/10.75","answers":[100.0]}
{"question":"The population of a state was 4,309,000, with 35.8% represented by a minority. What is the best estimate of the minority population in this state? A: 1,540,000 B: 154,300,000 C: 770,000 D: 12,000,000","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=4309000*0.358","answers":[1542622.0]}
{"question":"an accentric millionaire revisited his hometown and offer each boy $ 10 and each girl $6. all the girls accepted the offer, but 40% of the boys declined. how much money was given out if there were 2240 boys and girls in the town?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6*2240","answers":[13440.0]}
{"question":"in honors geometry i have a 73 what is 20% of 73?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.200*73","answers":[14.6]}
{"question":"What is 20% of $21.46?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.200*21.46","answers":[4.29]}
{"question":"A portable hair dryer plugged into a 110 V outlet, has a current of 10 A flowing through it. What is the power rating of the hair dryer?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"p=110*10","answers":[1100.0]}
{"question":"how do you express \u00c3\u00af\u00c2\u00bf\u00c2\u00a125 as a percentage of \u00c3\u00af\u00c2\u00bf\u00c2\u00a1274 correct to 1 decimal place?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=25\/274","answers":[0.091]}
{"question":"Emily weighed 10.6 stone at 26 before she got married, 3 years later and two days after her wedding she weighed 8.4 stone, how much weight has she lost in total.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=10.6-8.4","answers":[2.2]}
{"question":"the distance around the equator of Neptune is about 154,566 kilometers. What is the equatorial diameter of Neptune? Use 3.14 for pi. A. 49,225km B. 24,612.5km C. 49,212km D. 24,627.5km","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*3.14=154566","answers":[49224.841]}
{"question":"In 1997 the probability that a randomly selected movie ticket in France was not a U. S. film was approximately 0.5. Furthermore, the probability that the ticket was for a French film, given that it was not for a U. S. film was 0.6. What is the probability that a randomly selected movie ticket was for a French film?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.5*0.6","answers":[0.3]}
{"question":"If p is 25% of q, then q is what percent of p?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1\/0.250","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"12 7\/50 change to decimal?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=(607\/50)","answers":[12.14]}
{"question":"what is the answer to 3 divided by 6","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"t","noEquations":[1],"equations":"t=3\/6","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"pose there are 6 roads connecting town A to town B and 8 roads connecting town B to town C in how many ways. In how many ways can a person travel from A to C via B?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6*8=x","answers":[48.0]}
{"question":"use 1.7 as the square root of 3 what is the area of equilateral triangle abc with a base of 12 miles?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=36*1.7","answers":[61.2]}
{"question":"can anyone help me work out what 17 & 1\/2 percent of $2050.00 also the same percentage of $250.00","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.175*250","answers":[43.75]}
{"question":"inches to 1 1\/2 feet","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"64\/18=y","answers":[3.5555555556]}
{"question":"Amy weighs 180 pounds. After 1 week she weighs 165 pounds. What is the percent in change? eed 2 find d % in chang freom 180 to 150.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=15\/180","answers":[0.0833333333]}
{"question":"If I have sent out 50 questionnaires, and 30 came back, what would be my response rate in %.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"30\/50=x","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"y 12% of an iceberg's mass is above water. If the mass above water is 9,000,000 kg, what is the mass of the entire iceberg?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.12*x=9000000","answers":[75000000.0]}
{"question":"The side of a regular pentagon is 12 cm. Find the perimeter. The perimeter is: A. 60 cm B. 72 cm C. 30 cm D. 36 cm","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12*5=x","answers":[60.0]}
{"question":"what is the value of (-5) 2?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(-5)^2=x","answers":[25.0]}
{"question":"owners of SUperb Coffee want to buy 100 bags of coffee from Great Aroma. They take a sample of 10 bags and agree to buy the consignment if, at most, 1 bag in the sample fails to meet their exacting quality requirement. Great Aroma knows that 10% of the total consigment will not meet their requirements. What is the probability that they will buy the consigment?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.1*10=y","answers":[1.0]}
{"question":"Probability? ix married couples are standing in a room. if 2 people are chosen at random, find the probability that one is male and the other is female a. 1\/3 b. 6\/11 c. 1\/11 d. 16\/33","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6\/11","answers":[0.5454545455]}
{"question":"how do i find the perimeter when the area equals 96 yd2 of a rectangle. To the side of the rectangle the measure ment is 12 yd and the base is the letter b?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"96=12*z","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"how many 2-digit numbers can you make with the digits 4, 5, 6, 7 if no digits are repeated?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4*3=x","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"What is the probability in 200 extractions to have exactly the output of 100 heads and 100 tails?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z=100\/200","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"101 out of 101 elected members of state assembly say that 75% of their colleques are liars? many honest membes arre in state assmebly?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"101-75=y","answers":[26.0]}
{"question":"find the average speed for the giagistance and time. show the unit analysis to check units, . blem: D k Rutan and jeana yeager flew nonstop around the world, a distance of 24,986.73 miles, in 216.06 hours","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z=24986.73\/216.06","answers":[115.647]}
{"question":"if 0.5 as a fraction is 1\/2, how do you write 0.49 (non terminating) as a fraction?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10*x=4.999999","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":", and it shows it simplified to 3\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a5. How did they get that? Can someone please give me an explaination? And if I have a problem like: \u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a169, how would that be simplified like the first one? Th","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9*5=x","answers":[45.0]}
{"question":"I'm just trying to figure out if most people think the way I do. I say it her birthday is 3 days before. Just wondering if some people would consider it to be 2 days before. I'll wait to reveal her actual birthday.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"25-3=x","answers":[22.0]}
{"question":"What is 8 1\/2% as a fraction? nderstand how to do it but i cant seem to find the answer because of th 1\/2.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"y=17\/200","answers":[0.085]}
{"question":"How many elementary events are in the sample space of the experiment of rolling a 6-faced die thrice? 6, 216, 18, 36","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"36*6=x","answers":[216.0]}
{"question":": HOW DO YOU FIND THE PERCENT OF A NUMBER? If you wanted to find 62% of 355, how would you do tha","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.62*355=x","answers":[220.1]}
{"question":"4 men & 3 women are to be seated in 7 chair row.find the probability for each arrangement if the men sit together","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"576\/5040=z","answers":[0.1142857143]}
{"question":"is 40 out of 60 the same as 2\/3?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"40\/60=x","answers":[0.6666666667]}
{"question":"if there exist 4 different weight orange, given that the sum of weight of 2 of this 4 orange are 69g, 83g, 95g, 100g, 114g respectively. however, there exist 1 combination of 2 orange that haven't been weight together, what is the sum of weight of this 2 orange that haven't been weight together.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"183-95=x","answers":[88.0]}
{"question":"mail is delivered each day between 1 pm and 3:30pm. today is your birthday and you are expecting a package in the mail from your aunt. while waitin for the delivery at the door the phone rings. you are away from the door for 15 minutes. what is the probability that you mised the delivery?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15\/150=x","answers":[0.1]}
{"question":"ause of a membership drive for a community center, the current membership is 125% of what it was a year ago. The membership last year was 7400 members. How many members does the community center have this year?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7400+1850=x","answers":[9250.0]}
{"question":"Find the area of a rectangle that is 7.5 cm long and 4 cm wide. 30 sq. cm 3.5 sq. cm 11.5 sq. cm 1.875 sq. cm","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=7.5*4","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"tiply- (\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a3 + \u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a5)(\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a3 - \u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a5)","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3-5=x","answers":[-2.0]}
{"question":"convert 1.87 grams to mg? A.7mg B ..187mg C 8.70mg D 8..7mg","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.87*1000=x","answers":[1870.0]}
{"question":"is 2\/66 in simplest form?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2\/66=x","answers":[0.0303030303]}
{"question":"solve. Round the tenth if necessary. bonnie rae spent 15% of her savings on textbooks. If her savings were 0,Fin f the amount that she spent on text books. $80 b.$84 c $90 d.$94","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.15*560","answers":[84.0]}
{"question":"how to figure 2% of $199,000.00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"199000*0.02=x","answers":[3980.0]}
{"question":"its a rectangular box and one side is 3'2 and the bottom is 5'1 and the other side is 2'11 th. estimatee answ10a,of, anstop of thit lx.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5*3=z","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"ompany uses printer cartridges from three manufacturers. Manufacturers A, B, and C supply, respectively, 60%, 30% and 10% of the companys cartridges. 1% of cartridges from A, 2% from B, and 3% from C are defective. If a cartridge is randomly chosen and found to be defective, what is the probability that it is from manufacturer B?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.006\/0.015=x","answers":[0.4]}
{"question":"multiply. (7 + sqrt 3) (7 - sqrt 3)?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"49-3=x","answers":[46.0]}
{"question":"I'm studying for the Asvab. 4 divided by 0.05","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/0.05=x","answers":[80.0]}
{"question":"4702 days= how many years?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4702\/365=x","answers":[12.8821917808]}
{"question":"Te Florida Motor Speedway has 3,200,000 bricks that lie beneath the 2.5 miles of track. Find out how many brick lie under one mile of track at the race track.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3200000\/2.5=x","answers":[1280000.0]}
{"question":"of a sum of money is \u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00a324$ find the sum of money? .","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24\/x=0.15","answers":[160.0]}
{"question":"stion: use these numbers: 5, -7, 3, -4, ,-1, and use the operations of : adding, subtracting, multiplying, and dividing, only ONCE EACH to form the target number of 4.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5-1=x","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"'s parents have agreed to lend him 60 % of the cost of buying a second hand car. If joe still has to find $328 himself, how much does the car cost?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"328\/0.4=x","answers":[820.0]}
{"question":"Maria takes 6 classes. In 5 of those classes, she has an A. Write a fraction to describe the fraction of classes in which she has an A.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5\/6","answers":[0.8333333333]}
{"question":"What is 6\/10 in decimal form?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6\/10=x","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"How do you find the percentage of a number. Ex. Dan worked 60\/76 per week. 60\/76 how do find the answer?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"60\/76=x","answers":[0.7894736842]}
{"question":".6 is 32% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"193.6=(0.32)*(x)","answers":[605.0]}
{"question":"If you roll a pair of 6-side dice twice, what is the probability of rolling a combined 5 AND then a combined 8?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5\/324=z","answers":[0.0154320988]}
{"question":"11. Simon arrived at work at 8 : 15 A.M. and left work at 10: 30 P.M. If Simon gets paid by the hour at a rate of $10 and time and 1\/2 for any hours worked over 8 in a day. How much did Simon get paid?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"93.75+80=x","answers":[173.75]}
{"question":"res 2 right triangles, one is small the other is big. the small triangle's base is 2met ers and the diagonal part is 3met ers. the big triangle's base is the variable N and the diagonal part is 12met ers. Solve for N. Pl","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2*4=x","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"If I have 2 strings, 1 is 2 yds long and the other is 5.5 ft long, how many inches of string do I have?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"66+72=x","answers":[138.0]}
{"question":"What percent of 72 is 25?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"25\/72=x","answers":[0.347]}
{"question":"What is 4.95% of 16 and how would I do this simple mathematical equation?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"16*0.0495=x","answers":[0.792]}
{"question":"what is the domain and range of 18x^(2)-20?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0-20","answers":[-20.0]}
{"question":"A rectangle has a perimeter of 30 cm? t would be the new perimeter if the length and width of the rectangle is doubled in size? A.18 cm B.120 cm C.36 cm D.60 cm","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"30*2=x","answers":[60.0]}
{"question":"If this person has 40kg of something and gave 32kg away, what fraction is it?d whole question reads: oan had 40kg of rice. She gave 32kg of them to Mary. What fraction of rice was given to Mary?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"32\/40=x","answers":[0.8]}
{"question":"-7,-4,-, 6, 11, 14, 13, 8, 2, \u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0080\u00c2\u00934,-8 -","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"23\/12=x","answers":[1.9166666667]}
{"question":"Solve for | -4.6 -8.3 |? 12.9 B. -12.9 C. 3.7 D. -3.7","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4.6+8.3=x","answers":[12.9]}
{"question":"what is 2 1\/2 years at a rate of 5.2 percent?e question says Kara inherits $1300 from her parents. How much will Kara have if she invessts in a Cd for 2 1\/2 years at a rate of 5.2 percent?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1300+169=x","answers":[1469.0]}
{"question":"21 out of 28 points whats the percentage? is scored 21 points her team scored 28 what percentage did she score","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"21\/28=x","answers":[0.75]}
{"question":"W","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=16\/3","answers":[5.3333333333]}
{"question":"whats 8.2(10)?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(10)*8.2=x","answers":[82.0]}
{"question":"What is 0.1 of 180??","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.1*(180)=x","answers":[18.0]}
{"question":"Subtract. Write your answer as a mixed number in simplest form. 6 1\/9 - 1 7\/9?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6.11111111111-1.77777777778=x","answers":[4.333333]}
{"question":"what is the lowest common multiple of 12, 24, and 26?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24*13=x","answers":[312.0]}
{"question":"k so i have to find the lcm of 2 and 5 using prime factorization mode","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2*5=x","answers":[10.0]}
{"question":"sin 57 = sin u find u degrees in between 0 and 360 not equal to 57","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"180-57=y","answers":[123.0]}
{"question":"The sequence above is formed by squaring the odd positive integers, beginning with 1. What is the difference between the 8th and 9th terms of this sequence? . 1, 9, 25, 49, . . ..","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(32)*(2)=x","answers":[64.0]}
{"question":null,"operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6\/2=n","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"what is 75% OF 40,000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.75*40000=x","answers":[30000.0]}
{"question":"there are 800 people on the train at Manchester 1\/10 of these people are children work out 1\/10 of 800","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"800\/10=y","answers":[80.0]}
{"question":"Can someone tell me what negative 4 to the 2nd power minus negative 6 to the 3rd power is? is it positive 200?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"16+216=x","answers":[232.0]}
{"question":"he perimeter of a rectangular garden is 302 feet. If the width of the garden is 67 feet, what is its length?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"67+y=151","answers":[84.0]}
{"question":"I'm thinking of a number . When I subtract 13 and multiply the answer by 3, I get 24?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8+13=x","answers":[21.0]}
{"question":"ar moving at 35 miles per hour travels a distance of 51,3 .eet each second. about how far does the car travel in 7.1 seconds?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"51.3*7.1=x","answers":[364.23]}
{"question":"Find 19 percent of 152?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.19*152=x","answers":[28.88]}
{"question":"Convert 30 g\/L to the unit g\/mL?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=30\/1000","answers":[0.03]}
{"question":"tudent counts the number of waves passing a lighthouse. The student counts 15 waves passing the lighthouse in 10 seconds. what is the is the frequency of these waves? A5 METERS\/ SECONDS B.5 HERTZ C..5 HERTZ D150 METERS \/ SECOND","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15\/10=x","answers":[1.5]}
{"question":"What is 8 1\/3 plus 1 1\/3?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8.33333333333+1.33333333333=x","answers":[9.666667]}
{"question":"10 2\/3 as improper fraction? what is 10 2\/3 as an improper fraction.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=32\/3","answers":[10.6666666667]}
{"question":"Algebra 2 Can someone please help? ed takes a job that pays 3000 the first month and increases 100 each month for 2 years. What will be his salary at the end of 2 years? How much did he earn over the 2 years?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3000+2300=x","answers":[5300.0]}
{"question":"H","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2011-1993=x","answers":[18.0]}
{"question":null,"operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"135\/180=x","answers":[0.75]}
{"question":"If you get paid $8.00 per hour at your job and insurance is $200 a month, how many hours will you have to.?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"200\/8=x","answers":[25.0]}
{"question":"t is the LCM of 88 and 12. I","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z=3*88","answers":[264.0]}
{"question":"a statistics professor plans classes so carefully that the lengths of her classes are uniformly distributed between 49 and 54 minutes?d the probability that a given class period runs between 51.25 and 51.5","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.25\/5=x","answers":[0.05]}
{"question":"Iou have a circle with C as its center, and B as a point outside of the circle, and A as a point on the circle, and AC is 12, and AB is 16, and the portion of BC from B to the circle is 8, how do you figure out BC? ..","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8+12=n","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"What is 10 % of $25,000.00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.10*25000.00","answers":[2500.0]}
{"question":"If 10001 is 17 in binary, what is 18 in binary?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10000+10=y","answers":[10010.0]}
{"question":"Mr. Chaplin sells a car for $ 35,000.00. If he earns a commission of 4%, how much money does he earn? (A) $1,000.00 (B)$2,000.00 (C)$1,400.00 (D)$1,600.00","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"35000*0.04=z","answers":[1400.0]}
{"question":"5 chips numbered 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 are in a line. What's the probability that the 5 digit number is a multiple of 6?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2\/5=x","answers":[0.4]}
{"question":"What is 10% of $ 900,000.00 Mexican pesos?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"900000.00*0.1=x","answers":[90000.0]}
{"question":"If i have 1500 texts a month, how many texts can i use a day?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1500\/30=x","answers":[50.0]}
{"question":"Find the base of the parallelogram if the area is 120 in2 and the height is 8 inches.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"120=y*8","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"Find the difference between 2 1\/4 and 1 1\/5?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2.25-1.2=x","answers":[1.05]}
{"question":"Mary received $15 for her weekly allowance. She spent $10 at the movie theater with her friends. What fraction of the money, in simplest form, was spent at the theater?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=10\/15","answers":[0.6666666667]}
{"question":"How many days of school did I go ? A.5 B.4 C.3 D.2","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3+2=x","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"tudent is 18 years of age in 1995 when he is attending the 12th grade, how old is he now after 12 years? Is","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"18+12=x","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"How many millimeters are in two thousand meters?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1000*2000=x","answers":[2000000.0]}
{"question":"An equilateral triangle has rotational symmetry. What is the angle of rotation? (e)degrees (B)degrees (C)degrees (D) degrees","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"360\/3=x","answers":[120.0]}
{"question":"We spent 296 dollars total. Roomie A spent 238 dollars. Roomie B spent 58 dollars. Roomie C spent 0 dollars. If the total cost is to be split evenly 3 ways (which is like 98.something each), how much does Roomie B and Roomie C owe Roomie A?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"296\/3=x","answers":[98.6666666667]}
{"question":"t year, original price of a popular sweater was $40. This year, the price is $42. Find the percent of increase in price.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2\/40=x","answers":[0.05]}
{"question":"what is the sum of 10 and 17? what is the product of 9 and 3?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10+17=x","answers":[27.0]}
{"question":"Two bales of hay weigh a total of 1.5 tons. How many pounds is this? A 1,500 B 2,000 C 2,500. D 3,000.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2000*1.5=y","answers":[3000.0]}
{"question":"(-2, -8),(1, 4)? d the slope of the line passing through each pair of points?.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=12\/3","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"Find the average value of 2 sinx-sin2x on the interval 0 , pie?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4-0=m","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"Write the ratio of 16 cats to 12 cats in the lowest terms. 16\/12 b.12\/16 c.4\/3 d.3\/4","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"16\/12=x","answers":[1.3333333333]}
{"question":"Wat is the slope of the line passing through the points (2,0 ) and (6,2 4) -6 1\/6 6 -1\/6","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24\/4=x","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"There are two boxes box 1 has 1 red ball, 1 green ball, and 1 blue ball box 2 has 2 red balls, and 1 blue ball to win the game you must get a blue and a red ball you must pick from box 1 first then pick from box 2 what is the probability of winning?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1\/3","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"Find an angle theta in the second quadrant for which tan theta = -1. look for an angle between 0 and 360 degrees?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"90+45=x","answers":[135.0]}
{"question":"3 boys, 2 girls and a puppy sit at a round table.yhow many ways can they be arranged if the puppy is to be seated between the two girls?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6*2=x","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"Change the fraction 13\/20 to a decimal? (A)0.015 (B)0.15 (C)0.065 (D) 0.65","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"13\/20=x","answers":[0.65]}
{"question":"If you have 21.50, 26.70, 20.50, 28.15, what is the average?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"96.85\/4=z","answers":[24.2125]}
{"question":"What is 3% of 700?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.03*700=x","answers":[21.0]}
{"question":"ectangular door measures 5 feet by 6 feet 8 inches. What is the distance from one corner of the door to the diagonally opposite corner?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2+2=x","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"Ive just been transferring balances to my 0% credit card, and saw i had to leave 95% of my credit limit free. Can someone please tell me what 95% of \u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00a33,$00 is?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3000*0.95=x","answers":[2850.0]}
{"question":"What is the approximate value of cos 31\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00ba14'? (Use a table and interpolation)? .8563 .8551 .5185 d 0.5165","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.8557-0.0006=x","answers":[0.8551]}
{"question":"I am 5 feet 7 inches and 3\/4 tall according to my tape measure, how many centimeters is that?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"67.75*2.54=x","answers":[172.085]}
{"question":"Im 7 stone how many pounds am I.And if i am 158cm how may inches and feet am i!","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7*14=y","answers":[98.0]}
{"question":"The width of a swimming pool is 18.5 ft, and the length is 10.75 ft. Ratio of length to width as whole numbers? 43\/74 b. 5\/9 c. 74\/43 d. 9\/5","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10.75\/18.5=x","answers":[0.5810810811]}
{"question":"= 169","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"13*x=169","answers":[13.0]}
{"question":"Bob ate 74 crackers in 30 minutes. How many crackers could Bob eat in 45 minutes?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"74+37=y","answers":[111.0]}
{"question":"Mrs. Fleming bought a freezer. It is 4 feet long, 2 feet wide, and has a volume of 36 cubic feet. What is the freezers height?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"36\/8=y","answers":[4.5]}
{"question":"red missed a class test. His teacher, Mr Happy, knows that Alfred usually scores 1.6 standard deviations above the class mean. For the test that Alfred missed, the class mean was 18 and the standard deviation was 4. If Mr Happy is going to give Alfred a mark based on his standard score, what mark should Alfred receive?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6.4+18=x","answers":[24.4]}
{"question":"500 billion divided by 135 million?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"100000\/27=x","answers":[3703.7037037]}
{"question":"What is the method for working this out? If the value of a Euro is 1.33 to $1 and you have 300 Euros, how many $ would you get?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"300\/1.33=x","answers":[225.563909774]}
{"question":"2\/3% of 24$ is what?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24.00*0.6666=x","answers":[15.9984]}
{"question":"(-2)","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5+2=x","answers":[7.0]}
{"question":"te 275% and 5% as equivalent decimals","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5\/100=m","answers":[0.05]}
{"question":"500 students are enrolled in at least two of these three classes: Math, English, and History. 170 are enrolled in both Math and English, 150 are enrolled in both History and English, and 300 are enrolled in Math and History. How many of the 500 students are enrolled in all three?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(y+20)=140","answers":[120.0]}
{"question":"n you line the numbers up like the column method in addition...y you times 76 and 52 you times the 2 and the 6 then the 2 and the 7....y know??","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"76*52=x","answers":[3952.0]}
{"question":"Of every 5 hot dogs lester sold, 3 had mustard. What % did not have mustard? A 40% B 2\/5% C 60% D none?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2\/5=x","answers":[0.4]}
{"question":"How much is 90,000,000 divided by 4800?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"90000000\/4800=x","answers":[18750.0]}
{"question":"What are odd numbers? ( ),5 ,7 o(B),6 ,8 ?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7\/1=y","answers":[7.0]}
{"question":"electricity costs of a business increased from $10,000 to $13,000 the next year. To the nearest whole percent, what was the rate of increase?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3000\/10000=x","answers":[0.3]}
{"question":"Find the common difference between the terms of the following arithmetic sequence. -6, -1, 4, 9, 14, .? Find the common difference between the terms of the following arithmetic sequence. -6, -1, 4, 9, 14, ..","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4+1=x","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"What is 41 percent of 25 question?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.41*25=x","answers":[10.25]}
{"question":"100 is 85% of what number?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"y=100\/0.85","answers":[117.647058824]}
{"question":"-12*cos95 degree= 14.1","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"13+1.046=z","answers":[14.046]}
{"question":"Given a bag of marbles, 9 blue, 5 red, and 2 white. What is the probability of choosing one red marble?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z=5\/16","answers":[0.3125]}
{"question":"ustomer purchased a jacket for $65. This was 80% of the original price. What was the original price? 61.75 B$78.00 C.80.00 D.81.25","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"65\/0.8=x","answers":[81.25]}
{"question":"Ii have a 310 Litre tank of water andIi need to put a chemical in it which the dosage rate is 1 scoop per 38 Litres (10 US gallons) How many scoops would i need to put h","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"310\/38=x","answers":[8.1578947368]}
{"question":"ermine to the correct number of significant figures the mass (g) of nickel in a 78.3 g sample of a mineral that is 91.04% nickel by mass.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(78.3)*(0.9104)=x","answers":[71.28432]}
{"question":"r. Adams' salary last year was $45,000. He will get an 8% increase this year. What is his new salary? (A) $3, (B)60 $ (C).3000 (D)$ 5,036 (E) $45,360 $48,600","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"45000*1.08=x","answers":[48600.0]}
{"question":"Find the least common multiple of 12, 20, and 72.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20*18=x","answers":[360.0]}
{"question":"Find the percentage; 130% of 70. 2.1 b.21 c 9.1 d.91","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.3*70=x","answers":[91.0]}
{"question":"do you get feet into square yards ? ? How much carpeting does Mrs.W ned? b If the carpeting cost $38 per square yard, how much will it cost? P","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"32.222*38=x","answers":[1224.436]}
{"question":"nces spends 1\/3 of the day sleeping, 1\/4 of the day studying and 1\/8 of the day eating. How many hours in the day does she have left?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24-17=y","answers":[7.0]}
{"question":"is known that making 1lb of honey requires 20,000 trips by bees to flowers to gather nectar. How many pounds of honey would 45,000 trips produce?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"45000\/20000=x","answers":[2.25]}
{"question":"How do I make 1\/6 a decimal?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1\/6=x","answers":[0.1666666667]}
{"question":"Lts' say I''m Running at the speed of 8 mph for 1 hour I just Covered 8 miles. Now what I want to know is how many mins it takes me to cover 1 mile of those 8 miles","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"60\/8=x","answers":[7.5]}
{"question":"What is 5 percent of $530.00? A.$26.50. B.$556.50. C.525.00. D.503.50.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"530*0.05=x","answers":[26.5]}
{"question":"What's 1.7 as a percentage of 5.5?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.7\/5.5=x","answers":[0.3090909091]}
{"question":"ine cards are numbered 1 to 9 inclusive. If cards are drawn one at a time at random & they are not replaced, find the probability that the result will be an odd card, even, even odd, odd, & even?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z=1\/42","answers":[0.0238095238]}
{"question":"How to find the ratio of 1 : 500. If i wanted to find out the ratio of what 35000 mm is to 1 : 500","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"35000\/500=x","answers":[70.0]}
{"question":"works for $15.50 per hour for a health care facility. He is supposed to get a 75 cent per hour raise at one year of service. What will his percent increase in hourly pay be?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.75\/15.5=x","answers":[0.048]}
{"question":"In a AAA map of Ohio, 1 inch equals approximately 10 or 18 kilometers. If the distance on the map between Paulding and Eaton is 9.8 inches, how many kilometers is it between the two towns?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9.8*18=y","answers":[176.4]}
{"question":"sheet of aluminum is 0.012 of an inch thick. How high is a stack of 3,427 sheets? (A) 28 inche (B)s 33 inche (C)s 41 inches","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.012*3427=x","answers":[41.124]}
{"question":"If kalvin flips two coins 50 times and they land Heads-Heads 16 times, Tails-tails 10 times, and head-tails 24 times, what is the experimental probability that they will land tails-tails?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10\/50=x","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"What is 28% of 309,000,000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.28*309000000=x","answers":[86520000.0]}
{"question":"is 30% of what number i?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"70=0.3*x","answers":[233.333333333]}
{"question":"Which combination of numbers in this group has the highest value?m+ (-4), 4*|-2|, -4 * |2|, or | -4 | * (-2)","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4*2=x","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"nda is training to be a volunteer at her library. She wonders what the probability is that the first item she'll get to check out for a customer will be a video. So, on her first day of training, she tracks what items are checked out. The results are shown here in a tally chart. OKS: 37 Vieos:28 Maazines:19","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"28\/84=x","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"What percent of 18 is 0.5?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.5\/18=x","answers":[0.0277777778]}
{"question":"How many ft is 146cm?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"146\/30.48=n","answers":[4.7900262467]}
{"question":"How can i find the angle of a sector in radians. The radius of the sector is 5cm. The Arc Length is 8.4cm.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5*x=8.4","answers":[1.68]}
{"question":"Each of the five identical cards is numbered on one of its sides with a different integer from 1 to 5. Tcards are turned over and then shuffled so that they are not in a predictable order. If the two cards are selected at random without replacement, what is the probability that thei sum is at least 8?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2\/10=x","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"the probability that a person wears glasses is 0.36 and the probability that a person is afraid of sharks is 0.61, what is the probability that a randomly selected person will wear glasses and be afraid of sharks? Round your answer to the nearest hundredth. A 0. 7 B.0. 2 C.0. 5 D.0. 9","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.36*0.61=x","answers":[0.2196]}
{"question":"In how many ways can a club of 20 members choose a president and a vice president?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20*19=x","answers":[380.0]}
{"question":"Hdo I calculate this? I want to find the number that is exacly in the midle between the numbers, 748 and 0,4532","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.028\/2=x","answers":[0.514]}
{"question":"At camp today, kids can choose art, swimming, or music. Of those activities, 40 kids choose swimming, 16 chooart, and 24 choose music. What is the ratio of kids who choose music to kids who choose swimming? A2\/5 B.2\/3 C15","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24\/40=x","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"What percentage is 45,000,000 out of 6,000,000,000?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"45000000\/6000000000=x","answers":[0.0075]}
{"question":"A computer was priced at $850. You paid 20%? much was not paid in cash? (A)0 $(B)0 $(C)0 $(D)0","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"850-170=x","answers":[680.0]}
{"question":"I have $30. And I invest that money make 2 tshrts for someone. And than I charge that person $50 for the 2 shirts. So I'm making a $20 profit right? But I originally put $30 into it. So I'm making less than what I put into it. But at the end I have $50 from the customer. Obviously it seems like im making money but at the same time losing? So am I making a profit?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=50-30","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"What is the ratio 22 : 31 as a decimal?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"22\/31=x","answers":[0.7096774194]}
{"question":"Express the following as a percent: 8 out of 12. Round to the nearest whole number. % % D.%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8\/12=x","answers":[0.6666666667]}
{"question":"What is 1\/3 of 24?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24\/3=x","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"A stem and leaf plot for the number of touchdowns scored by all division 1a football teams is shown below. A) if a team is selected at random, find the probability the team scored at least 34 touch downs ( round to the nearest thousandth) 1|3 4 5 7 8 8 2|0 1 2 2 3 4 5 7 8 8 9 3|0 0 1 1 1 2 2 3 3 4 4 5 5 7 7 7 8 9 4|0 0 1 2 2 3 4 5 5 5 5 6 7 8 8 9 5|0 2 3 5 5 7 8 6|1 3 6 7 7| 8|7","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5\/9","answers":[0.5555555556]}
{"question":"Choose the fraction equivalent in simplest form for the decimal 0.7.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"70\/100=x","answers":[0.7]}
{"question":"Andy walks 36.6 miles with his mother to earn money for charity. they walk 12.2 miles a day. How many days do they walk? A.2.5 days B.3 days C.3.2 days D.3.5 days","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"36.6\/12.2=x","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"ave 20 rupees. I bought 1, 2, 5 rupee stamps. They are different in numbers by the reason of no change, the shop keeper gives 3 one rupee stamps. So how many stamp(s) I have.?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20-3=x","answers":[17.0]}
{"question":"W is the average of 50 77, 80, and 80?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"287\/4=x","answers":[71.75]}
{"question":"probability that event A occurs is .790. e probability that event B occurs is .580. e probability that both events A and B occur is .260, find P(B\\A).","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.58-0.26=m","answers":[0.32]}
{"question":"lage College awarded 26 varsity letters in c w, 15 in swimming, and 16 in soccer. If awards went to 46 students and only 2 lettered in all sports, how many students lettered in two of the three sports?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"51-44=x","answers":[7.0]}
{"question":"W is 20% of $306???","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.2*306=x","answers":[61.2]}
{"question":"weights of 10 apples picked at random from a box of apples were found to be: 6 ounces, 8 ounces, 9 ounces, 8 ounces, 6 ounces, 4 ounces, 6 ounces, 6 ounces, 9 ounces, and 11 ounces. Find the mean weight.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"73\/10=x","answers":[7.3]}
{"question":"F the quotient of 24 and 9 to two decimal places.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24\/9=x","answers":[2.6666666667]}
{"question":"henry can paint a wall in 20 minutes and peter can paint the same wall in 30 minutes, how much of the wall can henry and peter paint if they work together for 1 minute?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1\/12","answers":[0.0833333333]}
{"question":"aker used 52 1\/2 cups of flour to make 15 loaves of bread. How many QUAquarterps of flour were used? its : 2 cups = 13 quarters","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"52.5*4=y","answers":[210.0]}
{"question":"15 is what percent of 60?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"16\/60=x","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"a retail manufacturing process last year, there were 29 defective parts. The company boasted that they manufactered 160 non-defective parts. About what percent of the parts were defective? 15% defective b18% defective cc. 22% defective. 29% defective","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"29\/189=x","answers":[0.1534391534]}
{"question":"a 10-pound steak costs $6.55, how much would 1 pound cost? Round your answer to the nearest cent. A.$.65 B.$.66 C.$1.65 or D. $6.55","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6.55\/10=x","answers":[0.655]}
{"question":"ardo has 6 colors of fabric, red bl,ue green yellow orange and white . Hlans to make flags using 2 colors, how many possible combinations of 2 colors can he choose. ?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6*5=x","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"Suppose 80% of kids who visit a doctor have a fever, and 15% of kids with a fever have sore throats. What is the probability that a kid who goes to the doctor has a fever and a sore throat?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.8*0.15=x","answers":[0.12]}
{"question":"ecieved my grade for a test. It says I can get a possible 70 points total for the test. It says I only recieved 55 points of the possible 70, so what would be my grade percentage?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"55\/70=x","answers":[0.7857142857]}
{"question":"What would 20% of 200000 be?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.20*200000=y","answers":[40000.0]}
{"question":"a product normally retails for $40.00 and we give you a $10 discount, what percentage discount do you receive?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10\/40=x","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"What is 8\/21 in decimal form?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8\/21=x","answers":[0.380952381]}
{"question":"Suppose Ruth Ann has 4 routes she can choose from to get from school to the library, and 6 routes from the library to her home. How many routes are there from Ruth Ann's school to her home with a stop at the library? A. 16 B. 36 C. 24 D. 360","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6*4=x","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"I got a 47 out of 50 on an exam, what is my percentage grade out of 100?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"47\/50=x","answers":[0.94]}
{"question":"What is the probability of rolling a 3 on two consecutive rolls of a fair die? Round your answer to the nearest hundredth? A. 0.01 ) ( B. 0.03 ) ( C. 0.13 ) ( D 0.17 )","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1\/36=x","answers":[0.0277777778]}
{"question":"what percent of 400 is 1 1\/3?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*400=1.333","answers":[0.0033325]}
{"question":"t would the percent change be? Final mass 1.00 Initial mass 0.92 S","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.0\/0.92=x","answers":[1.0869565217]}
{"question":"n the input shaft of a gear box was rotated 36 times it was found that the input shaft rotated 5.5 times . culate the gear ratio between input and output shafts correct to 2 decimal places","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"36\/5.5=x","answers":[6.5454545454]}
{"question":"u start with a # add 5 then multiply by 7 the result is 133. what was the original #","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(x+5)=19","answers":[14.0]}
{"question":"fill in the blank. 95% confidence is to 1.96 as 89% confidence is to ___?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"95*x=174.44","answers":[1.8362105263]}
{"question":"A number cube with faces numbered 1 through 6 is rolled. What is the probability the number cube lands with a number greater than 4 face up?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2\/6=x","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"O number line, there are 9 equal intervals between 0 and 1. if the square rot of x is on the sixth dash of the number line going from 0 to 1, what is the value of x ?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.6*0.6=x","answers":[0.36]}
{"question":"the 16071 degrees in mathematics given by US colleges, 73% were bachelor's degrees, 21% were master's degrees, and the rest of doctorates. Women earned 48% of the bachelor's degrees, 42% of the master's degrees, and 29% of the doctorates. You choose a mathematics degree at random and find that it was awarded to a woman. What is the probability that it is a bachelor's degree?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"35.04\/45.6=y","answers":[0.7684210526]}
{"question":"Can you find the slope of the line that passes through the points (-6, -4) and (-2, 5)?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"q","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9\/4=q","answers":[2.25]}
{"question":"if i have two essays, one worth 30% and the other 70%. The pass mark is 40% but i have got 0 for the 30% essay leaving just the 70% essay to pass of. Is it possible to pass ? and if the 70% essay is out of 100, what mark would i need?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.7*x=0.4","answers":[0.5714285714]}
{"question":"Which fraction is in simplest form? 8\/10 4\/16 9\/25 15\/63 or none of the above","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9\/25=x","answers":[0.36]}
{"question":"What is 4 2\/3 subtracted from 5 1\/5?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5.2-4.66666666667=x","answers":[0.533333]}
{"question":"write 0.36 as a fraction?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"36\/100=x","answers":[0.36]}
{"question":"What is 10 with exponet of 7 divided by 10?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7-1=x","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"jarvis spent $1.04 on candy mints. Each mint cost less than $0.06. how many mints did he get? estimate: A 5 B 10 C 15 D 20","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1\/0.05=x","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"What's 8.75% of $45?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"45*00.0875=x","answers":[3.9375]}
{"question":"A man and a woman shared a lucky draw prize of $6000 in the ratio 2 : 3. The woman divides her part of the share among her mother, her two daughters and herself in the ratio 3 : 1 : 1 : 5. How much will her mother got?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"360*3=x","answers":[1080.0]}
{"question":"Suppose that for a certain football game the probability that the home team will be aheahiat half-time is 0.60 and the probabilitrothat the home team will be ahead at halfotime as well as at the final e s 0.45. What is the probability that the home team will wi this game given that it is ahead at the half? A. B.. C.. D..","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.45\/0.60=z","answers":[0.75]}
{"question":"is 60% of what number ? I","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"48=0.6*x","answers":[80.0]}
{"question":"What is the slope of the line passing through the points ( 7, 5 ) and ( 0, 0 )?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5\/7","answers":[0.7142857143]}
{"question":"how many more bottles does she need to sell in order to make a profit of $100, a is selling botled water at a beachside stand. each botttle sells for 1.50 and cost 1.00 she has already sold 90.00.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.5*x=10","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"t is 16% of 50?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.16*50=x","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"The perimeter of a church window is 60 inches. If the window is in the shape of a regular pentagon, what is the length of each side of the window? A. 12 inches B. 10 inches C. 6 inches C. 8 inches","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5*x=60","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"ere are the first five terms of a number sequence. 126 122 118 114 11.0 find the 21st term of the number sequence, the 20th term of the number sequence ibs up","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"50-4=x","answers":[46.0]}
{"question":"e fair dice were tossed, and the sum of the resulting tosses was recorded. This process was repeated 20,000 times using a computer simulation. The number of times the sum of the five tosses equaled 27 was 40. What is the estimated probability that the sum of the five dice will be 27?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"40\/20000=x","answers":[0.002]}
{"question":"how many 30 cmx30cm boards fit in 36 square metres?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20*20=x","answers":[400.0]}
{"question":"the blueprint of a house, 33 millimeters represents 6 meters. The actual length of the living room is 5 meters. What is its length on the blueprint?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6*x=165","answers":[27.5]}
{"question":"At Johnson's general store, T-shirts are on sale at 2 for $5.50. At that rate, how much will 5 T-shirts cost?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5*2.75=x","answers":[13.75]}
{"question":"ume that all variables represent positive real numbers (-\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a5)^2+(\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a5+\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a6)^2","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1+11=x","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"e just ran a race that was 3500 meters long. How many kilometers was the race? 350 km .5 km 5 km .35 km","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3500\/1000=y","answers":[3.5]}
{"question":"Sarah scored 80% on her recent math test. If there were 20 problems on the test, how many questions did she get correct?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z\/20=0.8","answers":[16.0]}
{"question":"How long would a car travelling at 20 mph take to cover 18 miles?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=18\/20","answers":[0.9]}
{"question":"have to fill in the missing blanks. 3 7 13 21 ? 5 20 51 104 ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"21+10=x","answers":[31.0]}
{"question":"abel on a soup can is unrolled to form a rectangle. If the rectangle has an area of 144cm2 and a height of 12 cm, what is the circumference of the can?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"144\/12=z","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"what would the answer be to 3\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a3 mulitplied by \u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a2?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(3*2)=x","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"Write a linear equation for a line that goes through (5, -8) and (-9, -8).","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"o","noEquations":[1],"equations":"o+8=0","answers":[-8.0]}
{"question":"iece of metal 3 7\/8 inches long is to be cut from a longer piece of 5 1\/16 inches. What will be the length of the remaining piece?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5.0625-3.875=x","answers":[1.1875]}
{"question":"How many ways can 12 people be partitioned into three groups of four people? . 2000 . 34,650 . 17,320 . 5,775 . none of the above.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"34650\/6=x","answers":[5775.0]}
{"question":"What's the next number?? 1, 2, 6, 42, 1806, ?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1806*1807=x","answers":[3263442.0]}
{"question":"135 is what percentage of 150? Okay if something is 150 and is now 135 what is the percentage of loss?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15\/150=x","answers":[0.1]}
{"question":"What is 36,753 divided by 107?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"36753\/107=x","answers":[343.485981308]}
{"question":"174 is what percent of 600?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"600*x=174","answers":[0.29]}
{"question":"tie drives a gas tanker truck. Gertie's truck holds 1000 gallons of gas, which includes the gas necessary to operate the truck. Gerties truck is a gas guzzler and gets a galloping one mile per gallon. She needs to transport 3000 gallons of gas to a Galveston gas station 1000 miles away. She can store gas along the way as necessary to retrieve at a later time, but can't purchase any additional gas. What is the largest amount of gas Gertie can get to Galveston?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1000\/1=x","answers":[1000.0]}
{"question":"Ive exams tomorrow and they are worth 20% of my overall grade. if i have a 77 wh,at do i need to get on the exam to get at least an 80 as my final grade? t","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"308+z=400","answers":[92.0]}
{"question":"What is the Lowest Common Multiple (LCM) for 124, 56, 128 and 39?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z=128*8463","answers":[1083264.0]}
{"question":"California Gold rush caused the population of San Fransisco to grow from 850 people in 1848 to 36,151 in 1852. What was the percent of increase in population of San Fransisco from 1848 to 1852?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"36151\/850=x","answers":[42.5305882353]}
{"question":"monique plans to decorate a rectangular flag with 4-inch square patches. The flag is 5 feet long and 4 feet wide. How many patches does it take?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15*12=x","answers":[180.0]}
{"question":"cost of making an article was increased and was divided b\/w materials,wag es & overheads in the ratio 1:4: 5 . article was sold for $9.20, with a profit of 15%. Calculate the cost of making an article.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9.20\/1.15","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"What is 3 1\/2 plus 2 1\/8 equals?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3.5+2.125=x","answers":[5.625]}
{"question":"What is 10% of $3,860.26?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.1*3860.26=x","answers":[386.026]}
{"question":"How much is 3, 547 over the cell phone bill cost if its 0.40 cents for each additional call?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3547*0.40=x","answers":[1418.8]}
{"question":"If 1 pound is 20 shillings and 1 shilling is 12 pence, how many pences are in one pound?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20*(12)=y","answers":[240.0]}
{"question":"What is the greatest number less than 10000, which is exactly divisible by 48, 60 and 64?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"o","noEquations":[1],"equations":"960*10=o","answers":[9600.0]}
{"question":"What is 38.8% of 9,144?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.388*9144=y","answers":[3547.872]}
{"question":"lim x-->0 (x*sin(x)) \/ (1 - cos(x))","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2\/1=x","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"Probability of 2 dice sums equalling odd?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z=18\/36","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"If you typed 225 words in 7 and a half minutes, how many words are you averaging per minute?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"225\/7.5=x","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"he cost of building a bridge in 1995 was estimated to be \u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00a3$4 million. When it was finally completed in 1998 it's total cost amounted to $37.7 million. What was the percentage increase?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24000000\/37700000=x","answers":[0.6366047745]}
{"question":"iles = 8 km ow many miles in 60km?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"60*0.625=m","answers":[37.5]}
{"question":"What is the smallest positive integer which has a remainder of one when divided by 2, 3, 4, 5, and 6?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"60+1=x","answers":[61.0]}
{"question":"What is the perimeter of a square that has the same area as a 2-inch by 8-inch rectangle?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8*2=x","answers":[16.0]}
{"question":"When the price for a color television is 240 dollars , the average monthly sales for this item at a departmentore is 500 . For each 10 dollar increase in price, the average monthly sales fall by 30 units. What is the average monthly sales if the price is 260 dollar per color television?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"500-60=x","answers":[440.0]}
{"question":"What is the original price before the 60% decrease if the new price is 840$?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.4*x=840","answers":[2100.0]}
{"question":"What is 18\/20 as percent? a.90% b.85% c.80% d.75%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=90\/100","answers":[0.9]}
{"question":"A metal rod has a length of 5m and a volume of 3750cm. What is the area of the cross-section?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3750\/500=x","answers":[7.5]}
{"question":"ay I started with a full tank of gas and I traveled 120 miles (mostly freeway). A the end, I used up 4.79 gallons. Ga much mpg does my car get and how do I calculate it?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=120\/4.79","answers":[25.0521920668]}
{"question":"find the product of greatest 3 digit number and smallest 4 digit number","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"999*1000=y","answers":[999000.0]}
{"question":"If the sales tax on a 30.00 item is 1.80, what is the sales tax rate?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"30.00*x=1.80","answers":[0.06]}
{"question":"3 is 0.2 percent of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3=0.002*x","answers":[1500.0]}
{"question":"There are total 90 boxes, and there is a gold box that you want to open. and you have 30 chances to open any boxes. Then what's the probability of getting the gold box?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"30\/90=y","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"a chemical is 42% pure. of 800 grams of the chemical, how much is pure?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.42*800=y","answers":[336.0]}
{"question":"water costs &1.25 per 1000 gallons and a 1000 gallons is = to 7.58 cubic feet and i used 38,000 gallons of water in 6 months ho,w much should my water bill be?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"38*1.25=x","answers":[47.5]}
{"question":"have 2 box.first include 5 white card and 4 black and second include 7 white and 10 black.we choose 1 card from first box then put it into second without watching it.now we choose 1 card from second box so whats the probablity of the choosen card been white?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.247+0.173=x","answers":[0.42]}
{"question":"There are 30 children in a class. 12 of them can play badminton, 8 of them can play table tennis. Find the greatest possible number of children that can play neither of the 2 games.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"30-12=x","answers":[18.0]}
{"question":"armer wishes to enclose a rectangular field of area 450 ft using an existing wall as one of the sides. The cost of the fence for the other 3 sides is $3 per foot. Find the dimensions that minimize the cost of the fence.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"450\/15=x","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"long does it take tom to drive 135 miles on I205 if he merges on to it at 10AM and drives non stop with the cruse control at 60MPHompl","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"135\/60=x","answers":[2.25]}
{"question":"In a weekend baseball tourney joel had 4 hits 13 times at bat. That is, he hit safely 4\/13 of the time? rite the decimal equivalent for joels hitting, rounding to three decimal places.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/13=x","answers":[0.3076923077]}
{"question":"divide the number 999999 with 99 .","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"999999\/99=x","answers":[10101.0]}
{"question":"Plane travels at about over L.A. at 560 km\/hour and 3 hours later, travels over Chicago at about 600 km\/hr. What is the acceleration of a plane?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(40)\/(3)=x","answers":[13.3333333333]}
{"question":"What are the lowest common multiples of 625, and 30?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1*5=x","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"0.63 is equal to? .63% b 6.3% c.3% d630%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"63\/100=x","answers":[0.63]}
{"question":"The car Colleen is driving gets 30 1\/3 miles per gallon of gas. She used 2 1\/5 gallons of gas going from her home to her grandparents' home. She used another 3 3\/10 gallons traveling from her grandparents' home to her cousin's apartment. What was the total distance Colleen drove?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5.5*30.333=x","answers":[166.8315]}
{"question":"182cm is how many feet?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"182\/30=z","answers":[6.0666666667]}
{"question":"Find your percent correct on a test if you received 50 out of 75 possible. a.33% b.67% c. 25% d.30%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"50\/75=x","answers":[0.6666666667]}
{"question":"rushed-stone walk surrounds a circular flower bed that is 1m wide. If the area of the entire region is 21.98 m\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b2, ind the radius of the flower bed to the nearest tenth of a meter. \"Use pi \u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0089\u00c2\u0088 3.14","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2.65-1=z","answers":[1.65]}
{"question":"can i get the per cet of 200 to 30,000 ? l","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"200\/30000=x","answers":[0.0066666667]}
{"question":"What decimal part of 240 is 160?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"160\/240=x","answers":[0.6666666667]}
{"question":"strength of gravity on Earth relative to the moon is 6:1. How much would a person weigh on the moon if they weigh 180 pounds on Earth?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"180\/6=x","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"Is 60 milliliters equal to 2 fluid ounces?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2*29.57=x","answers":[59.14]}
{"question":"Paul invested $5000 in a time deposit. What interest will. he earn for 1 year if the interest rate is 6.5%?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5000*0.065=x","answers":[325.0]}
{"question":"ing costs $2.89 per square foot. What is the cost to tile a kitchen whose dimensions are 4 yards by 5 yards?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2.89*180=m","answers":[520.2]}
{"question":"determine the lowest common denominator in the following fractions: 3\/4 2\/3 7\/12 9\/16","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3*16=x","answers":[48.0]}
{"question":"how long does it take to drive a mile on a moped that goes the speed of 20-25 mph.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"60\/20=x","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"what is radical 75 + radical 48 over radical 3?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5+4=x","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"a man has a patio and he wants to cover it with bricks. the bricks cost 19 cent. the bricks are 6 inches by 12 inches. the patio is 3 ft by 4 ft. how many bricks does he need and how much will it cost.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.19*(24)=x","answers":[4.56]}
{"question":"How many litres of water must be added to 8 litres of a 40% acid solution to obtain a 10 % acid solution??","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8*3=x","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"convert .1803 to a fraction, but the 8 and 3 have a repeating bar over them.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=182\/990","answers":[0.1838383838]}
{"question":"There are 4 sopranos and 7 altos in the choir. How many different soprano\/alto duets can be formed?e 18 . 21 c 24 d 28","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7*4=x","answers":[28.0]}
{"question":"how do you find a 2 digit number a multiple of both 3 and 4 the sum of its digits is 15, what is a prime numbe","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3\/3=x","answers":[1.0]}
{"question":"whats the mean of this data 63, 71, 72, 77, 77, 78, 86, 77, 88, 88?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=777\/10","answers":[77.7]}
{"question":"what's 15% Of 500.00 or even 10 %?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.1*500=x","answers":[50.0]}
{"question":"the kitchen table is 4 ft wide and 6 ft wide. How many 1 ft square tiles will fit on top of the surface of table","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6*4=x","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"6 drums of oil will heat 5 identical buildings for 3 days, how many days will 10 drums of oil last when heating 2 of the same buildings? 10 B. 12 C) 12.5 D. 14.5 E. 18","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"25\/2=x","answers":[12.5]}
{"question":"there are 25 spots 800 possible people, what is the probability of getting a spot? the person can't be repicked rytime someone is picked in a spot, they are removed from the pool, i.e. 800...9..798..etc.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"25\/800=x","answers":[0.03125]}
{"question":"25 cents per square foot, I need 312 feet. what's the price?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.25*312=x","answers":[78.0]}
{"question":"Round to tenths if necessary. The number of ballots cast in a parish election is 12,969, If the number registered voters in the parish is 19,800 what percent has voted? a. 65% b. 65.5%ac. 66% 66 2\/3%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12969\/19800=x","answers":[0.655]}
{"question":"ch ratio is not equal to 4\/9? 45a.95 16b.36 8\/c.8 2d.45","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"45\/95=x","answers":[0.4736842105]}
{"question":"The hanes own a 1 3\/4-acre lot. If they buy an adjacent 2 1\/3-acre lot how many acres will they own in all? a.3 1\/12 b.3 1\/4 c.3 4\/7 d.4 1\/12","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.75+2.333=x","answers":[4.083333]}
{"question":"if jared is turning 16 on august 4th 2008 what year was he born?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2008-16=x","answers":[1992.0]}
{"question":"25.0 divided by 29.4?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"25\/29.4=x","answers":[0.8503401361]}
{"question":"What is this calculation? of \u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00a36,$32,840.12","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2\/100=y","answers":[0.02]}
{"question":"how close is 3.22 cm to 4 cm?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4-3.22=x","answers":[0.78]}
{"question":"what's the answer to this 3 times the cube root of 62 divided by 1009 then half then subtract 90123?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.0235-90123=x","answers":[-90122.9765]}
{"question":"In rays 8 hours work day, he works 79% of the day, and inspects other works 21% of the day, how many hours in his 8 hour work day does he inspect other workers?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.21*(8)=x","answers":[1.68]}
{"question":"I am a number less than 50. Two of my factors are 3 and 5. My digits are 1 apart. Who am I?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9*5","answers":[45.0]}
{"question":"How do you find the least or greatest in a group of decimals? roblem: 0.002, 0.0019, 0.0004","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2\/1000=m","answers":[0.002]}
{"question":"tate is selected at random from the 50 states of the united states. what is the probability that it is 1 of the 6 new england states?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6\/50=x","answers":[0.12]}
{"question":"what is 33.3% of $36,000.00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"36000.00*0.333=x","answers":[11988.0]}
{"question":"The average of 33 consecutive whole numbers is 58. What is the smallest of these whole numbers?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"58-16=x","answers":[42.0]}
{"question":"what percent is this 63 houses finished 28?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"28\/63=x","answers":[0.4444444444]}
{"question":"what is 10% of 65?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"65*0.1=x","answers":[6.5]}
{"question":"ylindrical metal rod of radius 1 cm and length 80 cm is melted down and recast into a cylindrical rod of radius 2 cm. How long is the new rod?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"80\/4=z","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"t is 0.378 as a fraction in its simplest form?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.378*1=y","answers":[0.378]}
{"question":"In a city-wide survey, bicycle owners were asked how many bicycles they owned and whether any had been stolen during previous year.The results indicated that people in the city owned 9017 bicycles and of these 450 had been stolen. Based on this info, which statement is most reasonable? A- No bicycle owners will have their bicycles stolen this year B- All bicycle owners will have their bicycles stolen this year C- The probability that any one bicyle will be stolen is about 1\/5. D- The probability that anyone bicycle will be stolen is about 1\/20","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"500\/10000=x","answers":[0.05]}
{"question":"What is 2.8% of $29,205.24?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.028*29205.24=x","answers":[817.74672]}
{"question":"what is 46 divided by 3 1\/2?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"46\/3.5=x","answers":[13.1428571429]}
{"question":"If a diagonal in a rectangle is 90 m long, how long would a bisected piece of the diagonal be? a.m 60b.m 45c.m 37d.5 m","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"90\/2=x","answers":[45.0]}
{"question":"team b is 4 1\/2 games behind team a in the standings. Team c is 2 1\/2 games behind team b.HHw many games? nd team a is team c?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4.5+2.5=x","answers":[7.0]}
{"question":"A machine runs on a mixture of petrol and ethanol mixed in the ratio 11 : 3. How much petrol is needed to mix 10 liters if it is to be added to an existing 5 liters mixed in the ratio 3 : 1?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7.85714285714-3.75=x","answers":[4.107143]}
{"question":"what is the least common multiple for 24 48 58?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"n=24*58","answers":[1392.0]}
{"question":"t is 0.27 percent of 400,000???","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.27*400000=x","answers":[108000.0]}
{"question":"2-ounce box of corn muffins cereal costs $2.50. At that rate, how much does an 1-ounce box of corn muffins cereal cost?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2.50\/12=x","answers":[0.2083333333]}
{"question":"ectangle had an area of 8cm\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b2. f the length is 6 2\/5 (Six and Two Fiths) what is the width?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8=6.4*x","answers":[1.25]}
{"question":"how to work out percentages and what is 10 % out of 18. xxxx","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"18*0.10=x","answers":[1.8]}
{"question":"there are schools in a city that have internet access there are 21733 elementary schools, 7286 secondary schools and 10682 high schools that have internet access. There is a total of 51745 elementary schools, 14012 secondary schools and 17229 high schools. if you were to visit an elementary school what probability do you have to find internet access?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"21733\/51745=x","answers":[0.4200019326]}
{"question":"4 \/ 5","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/5=x","answers":[0.8]}
{"question":"Approximately what percentage is equal to 1\/6? A: 17% B: 15% C: 20% D: 25%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1\/6=x","answers":[0.1666666667]}
{"question":"a watch lost 1 minute and 12 seconds in 24 days how many seconds did it loose per day?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"72\/24=x","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"ngle1 and angle2 are complementary angles. given the measure of angle1, find angle2. angle1-=3d egrees","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=(90-43)","answers":[47.0]}
{"question":"when numbers are divided by 24 the qutient is 7 and remainder is 13 find the number?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"168+13=x","answers":[181.0]}
{"question":"The odds in favor of an event E occurring are 11 to 8. What is the probability of E occurring? (Round your answer to three decimal places.)","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"11\/19=z","answers":[0.5789473684]}
{"question":"car travels at 96 miles an hour for 40 minutes, how many miles has the car traveled in this time?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"32+32=y","answers":[64.0]}
{"question":"A small farming community in Texas covers 14 square kilometers. There are 420 individuals who live within the town limits. What is the population density of this community? a. 0.03 individuals per square kilometer. b. 53 individuals per square kilometer. c. 30 individuals per square kilometer. d. 10.24 individuals per square kilometer.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"420\/14=x","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"What is the LCM (Least Common Multiple) for 19, 38, 29?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"29*38=x","answers":[1102.0]}
{"question":"Chris's credit card has a restriction that he must pay either 10% of the unpaid balance or $25, whichever is greater. Which will he pay if he has an unpaid balance of $237?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.1*237=y","answers":[23.7]}
{"question":"Multiply. Write your answer as a mixed number in simplest form. 1 1\/7 x 3 1\/4","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.14285714286*3.25=x","answers":[3.714286]}
{"question":"hat is 75% of 28","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.75*28=x","answers":[21.0]}
{"question":"what is 30$ off a $125 dollar shirt?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"125.00-37.50=y","answers":[87.5]}
{"question":"Please help. the ratio of girls to boys is 2 to 5 if there are 60 boys , how many girls are there?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4*6=x","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"How much is 1 1\/2 divided by 1 1\/3?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.5\/1.3=x","answers":[1.1538461538]}
{"question":"what's 10 percent of 5,000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5000*0.10=x","answers":[500.0]}
{"question":"what is 10% of 370.00?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"370\/10=x","answers":[37.0]}
{"question":"uming that the change in daily closing prices for stocks on the New York Stock Exchange is a random variable that is normally distributed with a mean of $.35 and a standard deviation of $.33. Based on this information, what is the probability that a randomly selected stock will close up $.75 or more?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1-0.8869=x","answers":[0.1131]}
{"question":"the map, the distance between Chicago and Evanston measures 0.625 in. What is the actual distance? The scale is 1 in.:1 mi.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.625*18=x","answers":[11.25]}
{"question":"tax rate on a used car in Overshoe County is 6%. What is the sales tax on a sport utility with a selling price of $15,000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.06*15000=x","answers":[900.0]}
{"question":"Round to the nearest hundredth. 962 is what percent of 1788? A. 0.05%2. 0.54% . 185.86% D53.80%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=962\/1788","answers":[0.538]}
{"question":"ma and Betty are playing a number game. Wilma tells Betty, \"I'm thinking of a number between 1 and 10. If I take the number and add 4 to it and then multiply that by 3, I get 30.\" What number is Wilma thinking of?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"y+4=10","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"What is the probability of drawing a five or a spade from a standard deck of cards? A. 4\/26 B. 5\/52 C. 11\/13 D. 4\/13","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=16\/52","answers":[0.3076923077]}
{"question":"bulilding a lobster tank the dimensions are 6ft long by 2ft wide by 1ft deep, i need to know about how many gallons of water it should hold.. Th","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12*7.48=x","answers":[89.76]}
{"question":"a sales of 5 3\/4% is charged on a blouse price @ $42 how mch sales tax paid?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.0575*42=x","answers":[2.415]}
{"question":"ectangle has an area of 50 sq. in. and a base 10 in. Write and solve an equation to find the height of the rectangle. W","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"50\/10=x","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"What is 600% of 5?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6*5=y","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"d the slope of the line that goes through the given points, 7) and (6,5) 0,50) and(60,90)","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5-7","answers":[-2.0]}
{"question":"Graces average driving speed is 9 miles per hour faster than mias in the same length of time it takes grace to drive 220 miles mia onlu drives 184 miles what is graces average driving peed?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"184\/4=z","answers":[46.0]}
{"question":"ent out a survey where 2456 people responded, and I need to know out of these 2456, 1973 answered yes to a question. What is the percentage of people who said yes to the survey.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1973\/2456=z","answers":[0.8033387622]}
{"question":"im driving 2300 miles,ocar gets 20 miles per gallon highway r, ghly 300 per tank c, someone help me out on the cost i","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2300\/20=x","answers":[115.0]}
{"question":"The area of a parallelogram is 420 cm2 and the height is 35 cm. Find the corresponding base? 385 cm b.455 cm c 14,700 cm2 d.12 cm","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"420\/35=x","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"what is the Less Common Multipler for 8, 15, 20?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2400\/20=z","answers":[120.0]}
{"question":"my living room is 12 feet 9 inches by 15 feet by 10 inches, can some one tell me how many sq metres that is?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"o","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(3.8862)*(4.826)=o","answers":[18.754801]}
{"question":"drove to his grandparents' house for a holiday weekend. The total distance (one-way) was 362 miles and it took him 7 hours. How fast was Ted driving? (Ro A. mph B.3 mph C. mph D. mph","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"362\/7=x","answers":[51.7142857143]}
{"question":"en parallelogram DEFG. If the measure of angle D = 57, find the measure of angle G. A 0. B. C.3","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"180-57=x","answers":[123.0]}
{"question":"Three people can deliver 1000 leaflets in 30 minutes. How long would it take 5 peole to deliver 1000 leaflets ?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"90\/5=x","answers":[18.0]}
{"question":"what does the fraction 4\/9 ths make? ike 1\/4 makes 25 so what does 4\/9t hs make ?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/9=x","answers":[0.4444444444]}
{"question":"what is the answer to -5.68 divided by (-0.02)?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5.68\/0.02=x","answers":[284.0]}
{"question":"To make an orange dye, 3 parts of red dye are mixed with 2 parts of yellow dye. To make a green dye, 2 parts of blue dye are mixed with 1 part of yellow dye. If equal amounts of green and orange are mixed, what is the proportion of yellow dye in the new mixture?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=11\/30","answers":[0.3666666667]}
{"question":"How much hours have passed? m 7:00 this morning to 9:00 now","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9+5=x","answers":[14.0]}
{"question":"says if you are starting a player in 7 out of 20 soccer games, what decimal describes your starting record. I put 7 out of 20 into a fraction 7\/20. Thats right so far isn't it? Now how would I put it in a decimal?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7\/20=x","answers":[0.35]}
{"question":"Jones rolled a number cube 30 times. On 4 of those rolls, his number cube landed on 6? What is the experimental probability that the next roll will be a 6?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/30=x","answers":[0.1333333333]}
{"question":"62 1\/2 of t is 35.wWat is t?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"62.5*x=35","answers":[0.56]}
{"question":"actory sells 4,000 printed T-shirts for $7.50 each. Returns and allowances were $925. The store's merchandise inventory on June 1 was $24,750. Purchases during the month were $9,375. The merchandise inventory on June 30 was $26,250. Operating costs were $3,750. t was the net income? $_______","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"55325-37875=x","answers":[17450.0]}
{"question":"The formula for the volume of a cylinder is volume equals pie radius^2 height. What is the volumre of a cylinder if its radius is 3 cm and its height is 1.4cm?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3*x=9","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"27 feet and 10 inches length and 19 feet breath","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"27.83*19=x","answers":[528.77]}
{"question":"greatest common factor of 45, 75, and 105?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3*5=x","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"ave a 40% off coupon & I want to buy a Hi-Def DVD that cost $40. With 40% off, how much do I pay &","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"40-16=y","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"What is 125\/tan45?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"125\/1=x","answers":[125.0]}
{"question":"A line passing through (11, 1) and (7, y) is parallel to a line with slope - What is the value of y?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x-1=8","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"something is 40% of 20% of something.. then it's what % of 100%? I","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.4*0.2=z","answers":[0.08]}
{"question":"You drop a rock off a bridge 30 ft above the ground into a stream. How longdoes it take thr rock to hit the water? A.1.50 sec B.1.37 sec C.1.88 sec D.2.10 sec","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"p","noEquations":[1],"equations":"43.93\/32.17=p","answers":[1.3655579733]}
{"question":"of X is 50. Solve for X.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"25*y=5000","answers":[200.0]}
{"question":"go see a movie today. I starts at 45 the movie is 1hr and 28min . Long und what time does the movie end.?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(73-60)=x","answers":[13.0]}
{"question":"The legs on a table are 2 7\/8 inches high. The top is 24 inches wide, 48 inches long, and 1 3\/16 inches thick. How high above the floor is the table surface?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2.875+1.1875=x","answers":[4.0625]}
{"question":"for every $50 spent on petrol,$37 of this is tax. work out $37 as a percentage of $50.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"37\/50=x","answers":[0.74]}
{"question":"your going to travel to montreal, ottawa, halifax and calgary, but the order is arbritrary. You put 4 marbles in bowl, each one labeled for 1 city, and draw randomly. The first marble is teh first city you will visit the second is the second you'll vist. What probability that you will visit ottawa just before or after you visit montreal?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12\/24=x","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"sum of the digits of a two digit number is 8. When 18 is added to the number, the digits are reversed. Find the number?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"17+18=x","answers":[35.0]}
{"question":"6 1\/2% of what number of bottles is 130 bottles?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.065*x=130","answers":[2000.0]}
{"question":"find out 84% of 75","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"75*0.84=y","answers":[63.0]}
{"question":"7800 is what % of 9750?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*(9750)=7800","answers":[0.8]}
{"question":"My brother born Dec 23,1985.wWat year did he turn 18?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1985+18=x","answers":[2003.0]}
{"question":"how many cubic yard of concrete is needed. The dimensions of the pad will be 40 feet x 40 feet x 4 inches deep.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"533.3333\/27=x","answers":[19.7530851852]}
{"question":"what is the next number at the end 5 7 6 8 7 ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8+1=x","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"he temperature at the summit of Mt. Mansfield dropped 17\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0 between 4 p.m. and 11 p.m. If the temperature at 11 p.m. was 11\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0, what was the temperature at 4 p.m. A. -2F. B. F. \u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0C. F. D. F.6\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0F","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"11+17=x","answers":[28.0]}
{"question":"Dividing Decimals and Integers by Decimals 301.5(divided b) 1.34","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"301.5\/1.34=x","answers":[225.0]}
{"question":"$90 - $18. What percentage am I taking away from 90?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"18\/90=x","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"ulate the volume of a water tank in the shape of a cylinder with a diameter of 28cm and a height of 40,cm. If water of volume 18.48 litres is present in the tank calculate the height of the water in the tank. Use pi as 22\/7","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"18480=616*z","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"What is 0.999999. in fraction form?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9\/9=x","answers":[1.0]}
{"question":"what is the 8.25% of $32.94?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(0.0825)*(32.94)=x","answers":[2.71755]}
{"question":"If you draw one card at random from a deck of 15 cards numbered 1 through 15,? nclusive, what is the probability that the number you draw is divisible by 3 and odd?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"y=3\/15","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"ing a certain period of days, observations were made on the weather. It was noted that whenever it rained in the morning it was clear in the afternoon and whenever it rained in the afternoon, it had been clear on that morning. During this period, it rained on 9 days and was clear on 6 mornings and on 7 afternoons. How long was the period of days?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9+4=y","answers":[13.0]}
{"question":"the floor plan of Jacob's House, 3,000 square feet are under roof. Of this, 2,400 square feet are air-conditioned. The 425 square feet of garage and 175 square feet of porch are not air-conditioned. If jacob encloses and air-conditions the porch, what percent of the area under roof will be air-conditioned? Sh","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2575\/3000=x","answers":[0.8583333333]}
{"question":"if 20 ounce of popcorn cost $2.80. if the unit price stays the same, what is the cost of 35 ounce of popcorn?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(0.14*35)=x","answers":[4.9]}
{"question":"a play sells 1572, then 2nd year sells 1753, in the 3rd it sells 152 less then the 2nd how many sold third year?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1753-152=x","answers":[1601.0]}
{"question":"maximum number of grams of fat (F) that should be in a diet varies directly as a person's weight (W). A person weighing 96 lb should have no more than 64 g of fat per day, what is the maximum daily fat intake for a person weighing 42 lb?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"96*x=2688","answers":[28.0]}
{"question":"t is 5% of 80?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.05=x\/80","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"There are 14,000 registered voters in Waterston. In the last election 5,600 voted. What percent of the registered voters participated in the last election?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5600\/14000=x","answers":[0.4]}
{"question":"t is the slope? ( -3) (9,7) T","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=10\/5","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"average (arithmetic mean) of a list of 10 numbers is 15. If one of the numbers is removed, the average of the remaining numbers is 14. What is the number that was removed?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"150-126=y","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"If I buy 25 candy bars at 3\/$1.00, how much do I owe you?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"25\/3=y","answers":[8.3333333333]}
{"question":"are looking up at the top of a tree that is 10 m apart from you. If the tree is 15 m taller than you, at what angle are you looking upward?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15\/10=z","answers":[1.5]}
{"question":"A person had a rectangular-shaped garden with sides of lengths 16 feet and 9 feet? garden was changed into a square design with the same area as the original r tangular-shaped garden. How many feet in length are each of the sides of the new s are-shaped garden? 7 B.9 C 12 D.5 square root7 E.16","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"16*9=x","answers":[144.0]}
{"question":"what percent of $260 is $5?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5\/260=x","answers":[0.0192307692]}
{"question":"Find the percentage; 35% of 40?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.35*40=x","answers":[14.0]}
{"question":"What is the equivalent of 3 over 30?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3\/30=x","answers":[0.1]}
{"question":"30 percent of what number is 18?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.30*x=18","answers":[60.0]}
{"question":"ore leaving the warehouse, a truck driver noted that the mileage gauge registered 4,357 4\/10 m es. When he arrived at the delivery site, the mileage gauge then registered 4,400 1\/10 miles. How many miles did he drive from the warehouse to the delivery site?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4400.1-4357.4=z","answers":[42.7]}
{"question":"Mrs. Perez bought sixteen cans of vegetables 5 cans of corn, 4 of beans, 1 of tomatoes, and 6 of beets. If she reaches into her cupboard and pulls out one of the cans without looking, what is the chance of it being beans?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/16=x","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"Write 0.0008 1\/5 as a decimal without the fraction?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.0008*0.2=x","answers":[0.00016]}
{"question":"how 45 divided by 60 equals 0.75.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"45\/60=x","answers":[0.75]}
{"question":"how much is 25% of $4,000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.25*4000=m","answers":[1000.0]}
{"question":"what times 1.5 equals 1?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*1.5=1","answers":[0.6666666667]}
{"question":"The experimental probability of a defective laptop being produced by a certain company is 0.032. If the company produced 134,000 laptops, how many would the experimental probably suggest are defective? Round answers to the nearest to the nearest whole laptop. A. 428 B. 4,188 C.4,288 D. 41,875","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.032*134000=y","answers":[4288.0]}
{"question":"A sum of 3 equal numbers gives 24, what that number is?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3*x=24","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"You toss a coin and randomly select a number from 0 to 9? t is the probability of getting tails and selecting 8? a A b. B950 c. C050 d. D250","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1\/20","answers":[0.05]}
{"question":"What is the total length of 2 pieces of tubing which measure 4.5 cm and 3.222 cm.","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4.5+3.222=x","answers":[7.722]}
{"question":"40 is what percent of 800?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"40=x*800","answers":[0.05]}
{"question":"hur is treating his friends to a meal at Chez Rich. Te meals added up to $136.45. If he tips the waiter 15%, what is the amount of the tip. $20.46 b.$20.47 c $13.36 d.$13.37","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"136.45*0.15=x","answers":[20.468]}
{"question":"Which ratio is equivalent to 3 : 11? (A) 22 (B): 45 (C): 55 (D): 77","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3\/11=x","answers":[0.273]}
{"question":"What is the height of a solid with a volume of 120 m3 and base of 30 m2?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"120=30*x","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"WHAT IS put 4 over 10 in a decimal 2 different decimals?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/10=x","answers":[0.4]}
{"question":"17 11\/12 divided by 6 1\/10","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(17.9166666667)\/(6.1)=z","answers":[2.93715847]}
{"question":"Find the range of this set of data: 13, 5, 32, 16, 9, 12, 6, 23, 64?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"64-5=x","answers":[59.0]}
{"question":"many hours does it take to travel 300 km at 75 km\/h? (Use the formula d = rt.) A.2h B4h C225 h C22500 h","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"300\/75=x","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"What percent of $14,701.19 is $12,453.21?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12453.21\/14701.19=x","answers":[0.847088569]}
{"question":"A veterinarian weighs 140 lb. When she steps on a scale while holding a dog, the scale shows 192 lb. Let d represent the weight of the dog. Does the dog weigh 52 lb?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"140+x=192","answers":[52.0]}
{"question":"the Poisson distribution of a random variable lambda ( 5 occurrences per ten-minute time interval. If we want to analyze the number of occurrences per hour, we must use an adjusted value for lambda equal to ____. a.10b. 20c. 60d. 30e.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5*6=x","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"the thousands digit is interchanged with the units digit of 8,543, the resulting number is a. 4,995 less than 8,543 b. 495 less than 8,543 c. al to 8,543 4d. more than 8,543 4e. 95 more than 8,543","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8543-4995=x","answers":[3548.0]}
{"question":"aseball player has 10 hits out of 20 times at bat.How Hany consecutive pitches must he hit to raise the player's batting average to 0.600? Th","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15\/25=x","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"a map,the distance of 20 kilometres was represented by a length of 80 centimetres.The scale of the map was 1:n C. culate the value of n? E","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"80\/20=x","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"A class of 25 students has 15 girls and 10 boys. what is the PROBABILITY a girl will be chosen at random?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15\/25=x","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"How many grams are 1500 milligrams?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1500\/1000=x","answers":[1.5]}
{"question":"what is 20 percent of 700?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.2*700=x","answers":[140.0]}
{"question":"What is 5 percent of 700?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.05*700=x","answers":[35.0]}
{"question":"A vegetable garden is 12 meters long by 7 meters wide. In one square meter, count two toads.Estimate the population of toads in the garden.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"84*2=x","answers":[168.0]}
{"question":"Find the common ratio for the following geometric sequence? 4, 12, 36, 108","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=12\/4","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"Write 1 5\/7 as an improper fraction? 6\/7 B12\/7 C13\/7 D14\/7","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=12\/7","answers":[1.7142857143]}
{"question":"What is 126 and 1\/4 minus 78 and 2\/3 ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"126.25-78.6666666667=x","answers":[47.583333]}
{"question":"A website is offering a promotion, during which customers can buy up to 100 photos for a flat fee. The cost per photo varies inversely with the number of photos a customer buys as shown in the table below. What function models the data? Number of photos (n) 20, 40, 50, 80. Cost per photo in cents (n) 5, 2.5, 2, 1.25","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20*5=x","answers":[100.0]}
{"question":"what 113.813 inches is when converted to feet?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"113.813\/12=x","answers":[9.4844166667]}
{"question":"How much percent is 2,167,900 of 5,284,330.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2167900\/5284330=y","answers":[0.4102506846]}
{"question":"Find the range for the set of data, 114, 533, 220, 576, 415, 269?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"576-114=x","answers":[462.0]}
{"question":"I have 4 coins. i throw them all. what is the probability that 3 would be heads.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/16=x","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"pose you have a pipe with circumference 8 cm and length 20 cm and that 8 turns of a wire are wrapped around the pipe. What is the lenght to the wire? T","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8*8=x","answers":[64.0]}
{"question":"what is 0.7 of an hour?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.7*60=x","answers":[42.0]}
{"question":"What is 10% of $1,340.00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.10*1340=x","answers":[134.0]}
{"question":"What is 20% of $30,000,000.00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"30000000*0.2=y","answers":[6000000.0]}
{"question":"A company manufactures batteries in batches of 29 and there is a 3% rate of defects. Find the mean number of defects per batch. a. 0.899 b. 0.841 c. 0.87 d. 28.13","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.03*29=x","answers":[0.87]}
{"question":"Pyramid P is similar to pyramid Q. The volume of pyramid P is 980 cm3, and the volume of pyramid Q is 3307.5 cm3. Find the scale factor that would enlarge pyramid P to the size of pyramid Q. A. 27\/8 B. 3\/2 C. 8\/27 D. 2\/3","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3307.5\/980=x","answers":[3.375]}
{"question":"ide and express as a mixed number in lowest term: \/8 divided by 5 5\/14","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5.625\/5.35714285714=x","answers":[1.05]}
{"question":"what's 3 divided by 102?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3\/102=x","answers":[0.0294117647]}
{"question":"what is 1.65m in feet?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(1.65)*(3.2808399)=z","answers":[5.413386]}
{"question":"pilue means 22 is divided by 7 is, nt i't? th","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"22\/7=x","answers":[3.1428571429]}
{"question":"? d to find out what percentage 95000 is of 2,374,000.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"95000\/2374000=x","answers":[0.0400168492]}
{"question":"quare roots of 25...b","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3*5=x","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"arn \u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00a320$ per day, and out of te \u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00a320$ i have to give my partner \u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00a360$ What percentage (%) does my partner recieve.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"60\/200=x","answers":[0.3]}
{"question":"determine the range. 21, 10, 12, 7, 8?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"21-7=x","answers":[14.0]}
{"question":"what percent is 118 of 205?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"118\/205=z","answers":[0.5756097561]}
{"question":"what 2.3 percent of 527.00 dollars is?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"527*0.023=y","answers":[12.121]}
{"question":"Identify the amount in the statement \"140 is 28% of 500.\"?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"500*0.28=x","answers":[140.0]}
{"question":"of 80? th","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.03*80=x","answers":[2.4]}
{"question":"theast bound us 284 out of lubbock intersected IH 20. at its point of intersection us 284 becomes the middle boundry to 2 supplementary angles. the northwest angle measures 55 degrees. what is the measure of the second angle formed to the east?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"180-55=y","answers":[125.0]}
{"question":"What is 30% of 200?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.3*200","answers":[60.0]}
{"question":"Find the measure of the supplement of 58.eAa B \u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0 C \u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0 D \u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"180-58=x","answers":[122.0]}
{"question":"0.00 x .270%","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"100*0.00027=x","answers":[0.027]}
{"question":"I made a 61.5 on a test out of 70 possible points. How do I convert that into 100 points?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"61.5\/70=x","answers":[0.8785714286]}
{"question":"my bill is $18.77 and I want to leave a 15% tip. What is 15% of the bill?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.15*18.77=x","answers":[2.8155]}
{"question":"have 7 friends who want to go to a concert with you, but you only have room in your car for 2 of them. To avoid accusations of favoritism, you have your friends draw straws: There are 5 long and 2 short straws, and the short straws win. How many possible pairs of friends could be chosen in this way?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7*3=m","answers":[21.0]}
{"question":"what is 40% of 85?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"85*0.4=x","answers":[34.0]}
{"question":"divided by 2.3","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8.5\/2.3=x","answers":[3.6956521739]}
{"question":"If 400 people are employed at a company and 52 work at HQ, what percentage is that?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"52\/400=x","answers":[0.13]}
{"question":"Heres the chart: al subjects: 100 N. ber of Headaches: 80 N. ber of No Headaches: 20 #. Number Headaches treated with 10 Mg atorvastatin: 15 #. Number Headaches Treated with Placebo: 65 #. Number No Headaches Treated with 10 mg Atorvastatin: 17 #. Number No Headaches Treated with Placebo: 3 . If one subject is randomly selected, find theoblemablity that he or she had a headache, given that thubject is was treated with 10 me of Ator astatin","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15\/32=x","answers":[0.46875]}
{"question":"re are 6 numbers on a normal dice. What is the probability that if you roll the dice, you'll get a 5 or a 6? Express your answer as a fraction with no spaces. Reduce the fraction to its simplest form.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1\/3","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"change 33\/8 into a decimal?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"33\/8=x","answers":[4.125]}
{"question":"t is 150% of 75?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.5*75=y","answers":[112.5]}
{"question":"CD player you want costs $81.50. Your parents have offered to give you 70% of the cost. About how much money will they give you?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"81.50*0.7=y","answers":[57.05]}
{"question":"150 is 75% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.75*x=150","answers":[200.0]}
{"question":"i cant seem to understand how to solve this | - 8\/3 |? 2 1\/3 B.2 2\/3 C -2 1\/3 D.-2 2\/3","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8\/3=x","answers":[2.6666666667]}
{"question":"What percentage is 525\/550?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"525\/550=x","answers":[0.9545454545]}
{"question":"If you divide a number that is smaller than 56 by a number that is greater than 7, what can you definitely say about the relative value of the quotient? a.It must be greater than 8. b.It must be equal to 6. c.It will be between 7 and 56. d.None of these. e.It must be less than 8.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"56\/7=x","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"what is the probability that out of 4 children 3 are girls and 1 is a boy?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/16=x","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"If cos 72 = sin x, find the number of degrees in the measure of acute angle x? would be one of the following: A. 18 18\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0B. 36 36\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0C. 72 72\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0D.8\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(90-72)=x","answers":[18.0]}
{"question":"32 is 14% of what number ?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"32\/0.14=x","answers":[228.571428571]}
{"question":"30 gram compound contains: 12 grams of Carbon, 2 grams of Hydrogen. 16 grams of Oxygen What percentage of the entire compound is Carbon A.) 12% B.) 30% C.) 40% D.) 30","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12\/30=x","answers":[0.4]}
{"question":"Beaumont, Texas is about 150 miles from Toledo Bend. IF Leo Miller leaves Beaumont at 4 am, and averages 45 mph, when should he arrive at Toledo Bend?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"150\/45=x","answers":[3.3333333333]}
{"question":"What is 30 percent of 300?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.3*300=y","answers":[90.0]}
{"question":"d the product of 3(26) using the distributive property","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3*(26)=x","answers":[78.0]}
{"question":"his year's total sales for All-Star Producers are $649,608. During this same time frame, computer equipment sales accounted for $335,508 of the firm's total sales revenue. What is the percentage of sales for computer equipment compared to total sal es? If necessary, round your answer to the nearest tenth of a percen","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"y=335508\/649608","answers":[0.5164776296]}
{"question":"How many students chose green as their favorite color? favorite colors of 250 students. 20% purple. 10% yellow. 20% green. 25% blue. 15% red. 10% other.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"250*0.20=x","answers":[50.0]}
{"question":"n a single card is drawn from an ordinary 52-card deck, find the odds in favor of getting a red 9 or a black 2. their like 4 red 9's in a deck? or how many is their?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/52=x","answers":[0.0769230769]}
{"question":"A circle passes through the vertices of a right triangle P(-4, -6), Q(-4, 18), R(16, -6). Find the sum of x and y-coordinates of the centre of this circle..","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6+6=z","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"find 10% of a 1.50","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.1*1.50=y","answers":[0.15]}
{"question":"What percentage out of 100 does 21\/27 convert to?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"21\/27=x","answers":[0.7777777778]}
{"question":"If 1 of 255 subjects is randomly selected, f the probability that the person is over 40, if 85 people are over 40.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"85\/255=x","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"What is 75% of 1,887?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.75*1887=x","answers":[1415.25]}
{"question":"If 5 to the power of x equals 7. d the value of 5 to the power of 2x.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7*7=z","answers":[49.0]}
{"question":"ping only significant digits, express the following in decimal form: 6.5\u00c3\u0083\u00c2\u00970. x 67","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6.50*0.667=x","answers":[4.3355]}
{"question":"1 Japanses yen equals 0.0079 euros, then 1 euro equals how many Japanese yen? A. 126.5823 B.126.0079 C.0.0079 D.0.5823","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1\/0.0079=x","answers":[126.582278481]}
{"question":"what does 10% of 50 equal?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.10*50=z","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"Whats the product of 0.4 and 9?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.4*9=x","answers":[3.6]}
{"question":"If i bought a Honda Civic for 13,000 and paid back the loan over 5 years with a 7% interest. How much would I be paying back a month?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.07*13000=x","answers":[910.0]}
{"question":"Charles bought a used car and later sold it for a 20% profit. If he sold it for $4596, how much did rles pay for the used car?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4596=1.2*x","answers":[3830.0]}
{"question":"The floor of a rectangular deck has an area of 600 sq ft. The floor is 20 ft wide. How long is the floor? 15 ft. B 20 ft. C 30 ft. D 45 ft.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"600\/20=n","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"What is 4 divided by square root of 5?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/2.236=x","answers":[1.7889087656]}
{"question":"what is 25 percent of 10000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.25*10000=m","answers":[2500.0]}
{"question":"a forest, it rained 36 out of 90 days. Wh t is the decimal equivalent of 36 ou of 90?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"36\/90=x","answers":[0.4]}
{"question":"Eleana's budget is 40% on food, 10% other, 30% savings, and 20% clothes. How much did she budget for food? ana has $400.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"400*0.4=y","answers":[160.0]}
{"question":"( 41 - -4 )?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"41+4=x","answers":[45.0]}
{"question":"Find the base edge of a square prism with height of 6 m and lateral area of 144 m2.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24*x=144","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"39,000,000 out of 300,000,000 people can wiggle their ears. This is one out of how many people?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"300000000\/39000000=x","answers":[7.6923076923]}
{"question":"I made $58,000 in 2007 and paid $10,000 in federal income tax, what percentage did I pay in tax? ho","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10000\/58000=x","answers":[0.1724137931]}
{"question":"is what percent of 200.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"90\/200=x","answers":[0.45]}
{"question":"The perimeter of a church window is 80 inches. If the window is in the shape of a square, what is the length? A. 40 inches B. 60 inches C. 20 inches D. 15 inches","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"80\/4=x","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"Two cyclists start biking from a trail's start 3 hours apart. The second cyclist travels at 10 miles per hour and starts 3 hours after the first cyclist who is traveling at 6 miles per hour. How much time will pass before the second cyclist catches up with the first from the time the second cyclist started biking? A. 2 hours B. 42 Houhours . 5 3\/4h ours D. 6 hoursT E. 7 m\/ours","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"18\/4=x","answers":[4.5]}
{"question":"W is 58 kilos in pounds?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"58*2.2=z","answers":[127.6]}
{"question":"You pass a road sign saying \"New York 153 km.\" If you drive at a constant speed of 65 mi\/h, how long should it take you to reach New York? (Round to the nearest minute.)","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z=95.625\/65","answers":[1.4711538462]}
{"question":"iamond ring sold for $2553.60 including tax. If the tax rate where the diamond was purchased is 6.4%, find the price of the ring before the tax was added. (Round to the nearest cent, if necessary.) A.717.03 B.390.17 C. $2400.00 $24D.63.43","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*1.064=2553.6","answers":[2400.0]}
{"question":"What speed in mph would I be going if I did 105 miles in 2 hour 20 min?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"105\/2.33333333333=x","answers":[45.0000000001]}
{"question":"t is 2 1\/2 as an improper fraction?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5\/2","answers":[2.5]}
{"question":"of 70 is _____.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.35*70=x","answers":[24.5]}
{"question":"How can I find out 15% of $200 with a calculator?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.15*200=y","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"What is the variance of the following data? If necessary, round your answer to two decimal places? 10, 12, 15, 18, 11, 13, 14, 16, 19, 20. answers: 12.34 11.78 10.56 9.34","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"105.6\/10=x","answers":[10.56]}
{"question":"What is 25% of 40?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.25*40","answers":[10.0]}
{"question":"offe shop shop has 11 jelly doughnuts. If there are 55 doughnuts in the shop. what percent of them are jelly ? 5% b.0% c20.% d.4%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"11\/55=x","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"Please help me to solve the problem. (2*\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a28)\/7.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(10.58\/7)=y","answers":[1.5114285714]}
{"question":"whats 3% out of 6,662?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.03*6662","answers":[199.86]}
{"question":"What is the probability of getting a 2 or a 12 on two dice?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2\/36=x","answers":[0.0555555556]}
{"question":"IRS auditor randomly selects 3 tax returns from 58 returns of which 5 contain errors. What is the probability that she selects none of those containing errors?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=(53\/58)","answers":[0.9137931034]}
{"question":"Regular price for a coat is $120. It is on sale for 25% off the regular price. What is the SALE price of the coat?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"120*0.75=x","answers":[90.0]}
{"question":"All the students going to Westerville High School had to take an entrance exam. The exam began at 8:15 A.M. And lasted for 210 minutes. How many hours was the exam? What time was the exam completed?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"210\/60=x","answers":[3.5]}
{"question":"ave $120.00 and i what somthieng that is $4.95 not including tax ho.w many of those can i get with $120","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"120\/4.95=x","answers":[24.2424242424]}
{"question":"Leaning Tower of Pisa should stand at 60 meters, but because it is tilted, it only stands at 58 meters. At what angle of inclination is the tower tilted? - a. -6b. -8c. i","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"90-14.8=x","answers":[75.2]}
{"question":"What is 25% of $8,100.00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8100*0.25=x","answers":[2025.0]}
{"question":"earchers have observed that regular smokers have an average life span that is normally distributed and is 68 years with a standard deviation of 10 years. What percent of smokers will live beyond age 76?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1-0.78814=m","answers":[0.21186]}
{"question":"Out of the first 100 customers, how many will receive a bumper sticker and a 10% discount? ry fourth customer at a store gets a free bumper sticker, and every tenth customer gets a 10% discount. a. 25 b. 10 c.0 d.5","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"100\/20=x","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"0\/5(-27)-49(10)","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"540-490=x","answers":[50.0]}
{"question":"18 and 3\/4's is what % of 75?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"18.75\/75=x","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"I got 23 answers right out of 75. What percentage did I get out of 100?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"23\/75=x","answers":[0.3066666667]}
{"question":"10% of $560?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.1*560=x","answers":[56.0]}
{"question":"this is a pie chart. It shows the distribution of a person's total yearly income of $36,000. I have to find the amount budgeted for utilities. U lities is 8% F, d 25% R, t 30% O , er 8% E, ertainment 5% C, thing 12% T, nsportation 12%","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"36000*0.08=x","answers":[2880.0]}
{"question":"188,000 is what percent of 210000?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"188000\/210000=x","answers":[0.895]}
{"question":"Each perosn in a sample of 300 residents in Buncombe County was asked whether he or she favored having a single countywide police department. The county cnsists of one large city and a number of small townships. The response of those sampoled, with their place of residence specified is given in the following table. Residence\/--Favor--Oppose-- Tota Live in city\/-- 130---50----180 Live outside city\/---85---35---120 Total\/--215---85---300 If one person from the sample is selected at random, find the probability that the person favors a single countywide police force.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"215\/300=x","answers":[0.7166666667]}
{"question":"2001 the average yearly wage was \u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00a321$42 O. average, people spent 31644 on their family holiday W. t percentage of the average yearly wage is that? s","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"31644\/21842=x","answers":[1.4487684278]}
{"question":"If 7% of a number is 42, is the number 3609?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.07*x=42","answers":[600.0]}
{"question":"The area of a rectangular garden is 4472 ft. (2) (to the second power.) If the length of the garden is 86 feet, what is its width?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(4472)=(86)*(x)","answers":[52.0]}
{"question":"if base of a parallelogram is 6 1\/2 in. and height is 1 1\/2 in. what is its area?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6.5*1.5=z","answers":[9.75]}
{"question":"is received a $735 end of year bonus, if her regular salary was $24,500, what was the percent of the bonus if all employees were given fixed percent of thier regular salary as thier bonus","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24500*x=735","answers":[0.03]}
{"question":"Four boys washed a car for 50 cents. They didn't know how to divide the money equally, so the car owner said,\"I will give the four of you 4\/5 of the total amount. And the first one to tell me how much it is, I will give1\/2 of the other 1\/5.\" What did the smart boy earn?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10+5=x","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"next number in the series 4, 12, 6, 12, 36, 18, 36, is:","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(36*3)=x","answers":[108.0]}
{"question":"Solve. Round to tenths if necessary.There are 18 violins players in an orchestra.II this is 24% of the?estra membership,find the number of members in the orchestra? a members b. 7 members c. 7 members d. 7 members","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"y=18\/0.24","answers":[75.0]}
{"question":"to figure out what 15 percent of 24 is","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24*0.15=x","answers":[3.6]}
{"question":"The area of the base of a cuboid 35 cm2. its volume is 280cm3. what is the height?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"280\/35=x","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"ure out how many centimeters are ub 72inc hes. I","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"72*2.54=x","answers":[182.88]}
{"question":"d.c.b.a.","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"535+528=x","answers":[1063.0]}
{"question":"if you had 22,700 to begin with and you were earning 7,500 dollars a day how long would it take to get $933600","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"910900\/7500=x","answers":[121.453333333]}
{"question":"If I started out with 25.00 and made 10.13, what percentage would I have made on top of the original 25.00?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10.13\/25.00=x","answers":[0.4052]}
{"question":"t is 3.9% of 2500 billion?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.039*2500=x","answers":[97.5]}
{"question":"A car gets 21 mpg. How many miles can it get if the tank is full with 14 gallons?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"21*14=x","answers":[294.0]}
{"question":"would you go about solving this: 11\/2 % of 5416","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5416*0.125=y","answers":[677.0]}
{"question":"A person was fined for exceeding the speed limit by 10 mph. Another person was also fined for exceeding the sampeed limit by 10mtwice the sameno the sond person was traveling at a speed of 35 mph, find the speed limit.","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x+20=35","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"amount required is 70000 dollars after 10 years at 9% compounded semiannually.WhatWis the semiannual payment? und the answer to 2 decimal places.]","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"70000*0.09=y","answers":[6300.0]}
{"question":"if something cost 18$ and the tax is 7.75%. what would the item cost?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.0775*18=x","answers":[19.395]}
{"question":"What's 30% off of 54 dollars ?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"54*0.7=x","answers":[37.8]}
{"question":"t is 3% of 300?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x\/300=0.03","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"18th hole of St Andrews Golf course is 520 m in length. How long will it be on a plan of the golf course. The scale is 1: 9000))","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"520\/9000=x","answers":[0.0577777778]}
{"question":"dents st the University of Washington built a model globe 42 ft in diameter using a scale of 1 : 1,000,000. About how tall is Mt. Everest on the model? (Mt. Everest is about 29,000 ft tall)","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"29000\/1000000=x","answers":[0.029]}
{"question":"A PARALLELOGRAM ABCD ,dia gonal ac measures 34m and the perpendicular of ac from either of the vertices B and D is 12m.find the area of the parallelogram.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"34*12=z","answers":[408.0]}
{"question":"In a game of craps, a player looses on the roll if a 2, 3 or 12 is tossed on first roll.d the probability of loosing on first roll.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z=1\/9","answers":[0.1111111111]}
{"question":"you made 450.00, fica tax is 12.00, so on and so forth, what is the percentage, h","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12\/450=x","answers":[0.0266666667]}
{"question":"?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"200\/255=x","answers":[0.7843137255]}
{"question":"what is the sum of 4 7\/8 plus 5 1\/6?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4.875+5.16666666667=x","answers":[10.041667]}
{"question":"How would you find my overall percentage? total possible points was 400 and i got 336.5 (63.5 is the difference)","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"336.5\/400=x","answers":[0.84125]}
{"question":"what number is 80% of 250?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"250*(0.8)=x","answers":[200.0]}
{"question":"what is 15% of 36,000$ ?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.15*36000=x","answers":[5400.0]}
{"question":"ommittee of 3 people is to be randomly selected from a group of 5 women and 8 men. What is the probability that the committee will consist only of women? 5\/143 B.7\/143 C 28\/143 D.30\/143","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10\/286=y","answers":[0.034965035]}
{"question":"find the range of the following set of numbers: 247, 562, 498, 149, 568, 327, 470?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"568-149=x","answers":[419.0]}
{"question":"A","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2*3.14","answers":[6.28]}
{"question":"What can 5, 3, and 6 all go into evenly?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5*6=x","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"H","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"76*2.54=x","answers":[193.04]}
{"question":"2 1\/2 subtract by 8 3\/4 equals what?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8.75-2.5=x","answers":[6.25]}
{"question":"How do you divide a whole number by a fraction? feet divided by 1 3\/4","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"14\/1.75=x","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"What percent of 980 is 294?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*980=294","answers":[0.3]}
{"question":"How many numbers from 100 to 200 are greater than 166?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"200-166=x","answers":[34.0]}
{"question":". Whatever wants to make a 150 square foot rectanguala vegetable garden alon thge side of her garage. If the garage is 20 feet long, how side should the garden be?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=150\/20","answers":[7.5]}
{"question":"H","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10.6666666667*60=x","answers":[640.0]}
{"question":",","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"239.99*0.85=x","answers":[203.9915]}
{"question":null,"operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"500*x=33000","answers":[66.0]}
{"question":"least common multiple 45 and 54?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"54*5=y","answers":[270.0]}
{"question":"How many miles is 10.5 km?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10.5*0.62137=x","answers":[6.524]}
{"question":"5 1\/16 inches divided by 3 7\/8 inches?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5.0625\/3.875=x","answers":[1.3064516129]}
{"question":"0.7 is 19% of what number? _____?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.19*x=0.7","answers":[3.6842105263]}
{"question":"The number of calories burned while doing an activity can be expressed by rm,ileere r is the rate of calories burned and m is the the number of minutes spenting anthetivity ca blem: a120 pound student playing volleyball burns 2.7 calories per minute. if the student plays for 30 minutes, how many calories does the student burn?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=(2.7)*(30)","answers":[81.0]}
{"question":"What is 5 over 6 as a decimal?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5\/6=x","answers":[0.8333333333]}
{"question":"A feeding trough full of water is 5 ft long and its ends are isosceles triangles having a base and height of 3 ft. Water leaks out of the tano at ate of 5 (ft)^3\/min. How fast is the water level falling when the wer in the tank is 6 in. deep?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5\/2.5=x","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"$49 paid for restaurant and a 15% tip. How much would the tip be?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"49*0.15=x","answers":[7.35]}
{"question":"What is the square footage of a 12 x 15 room?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12*15=x","answers":[180.0]}
{"question":"What ise LCM of 6 and 27 ann","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"27*2=x","answers":[54.0]}
{"question":"The area of a parallelogram is 420cm2(sqaured) and the height is 35cm. Find the corresponding base.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"420=x*35","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"What's the next number in the sequence 22, 25, 28, 31 is? A 32 B 33 C 34 D 35","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"31+3=x","answers":[34.0]}
{"question":"An organization of 10 men and 15 women. I want to form a committee of 6 members and I will select them at random wFind the prosability that the committee consists of at least one maninUse 3 decimaloblaces in h answer","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1-0.0283=y","answers":[0.9717]}
{"question":"Write the ratio of 25 cars to 15 cars in lowest terms? A. 25\/15 B 15\/25 C 5\/3 D 3\/5","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"25\/15=x","answers":[1.6666666667]}
{"question":"Ihe VAT is increased to 19%. What divisor (correct to 5 significant figures) is needed to find the VAT part of the total price?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1\/0.19=x","answers":[5.2631578947]}
{"question":"What is 20% of $20?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.2*20=y","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"What does 3\/4 equal is it?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3\/4=x","answers":[0.75]}
{"question":"2 students are in a sports club. 4 play soccer, 6 play tennis, 8 play basketball, 1 plays both soccer and tennis, 1 plays both soccer and basketball, and 4 play tennis and basketball. No member of the club plays all three sports. If three students are reandomly selected from the club, what is the probability that each sport will be represented?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=141\/220","answers":[0.6409090909]}
{"question":"What percentage 39 is of 68?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"39=x*68","answers":[0.5735294118]}
{"question":"Jeff's car gets 444 mile with a full tank of gas. If his gas tank holds twelve gallons, how many miles per gallon is his car getting?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"444\/12=x","answers":[37.0]}
{"question":"fair dice of tossed. Find the Probabilites in each of the following cases: 1]The sum of the numbers obtained is 7. 2","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6\/36","answers":[0.1666666667]}
{"question":"What's 29% of $500?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.29*500=x","answers":[145.0]}
{"question":"ave a 6 yard by 4 yard piece of cloth. What is the area of the largest circular piece that can be cut? l ve answer in terms of pi. E","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3.14*4=y","answers":[12.56]}
{"question":"What is the Answer to square the number 15? ? which is the answer to the question 3375, 225, 30, or 3.87","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15*15=x","answers":[225.0]}
{"question":"ave an 86.5% in math and i am pretty sure i got 100% on my final which is 10% of my grade. whaW would my grade be?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.8785*100=z","answers":[87.85]}
{"question":"first 31st term of a geometric sequence is 123 and the 32nd term is 1107. What is the 33rd term.?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1107*9=y","answers":[9963.0]}
{"question":"What is 189 divided by 243 in a fraction simplest form?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"189\/243=x","answers":[0.7777777778]}
{"question":"A six sided die is rolled. what is the probability of rolling a 3 or 4? a. 2 b. 1\/3 c. 1\/6 d. 1\/36","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2\/6=x","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"what is 9% of 15?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.09*15","answers":[1.35]}
{"question":"What percent of 50 is 12?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*50=12","answers":[0.24]}
{"question":"40 is what percent of 135? round to the nearest 10 ths place?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"135*x=40","answers":[0.296]}
{"question":"The 3 pound lemon cost $1.44, what was the cost per pound?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.44\/3=x","answers":[0.48]}
{"question":"many yards are contained in 324.1 centimeters? ( yard= 91.46 centimeters)","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"324.1\/91.46=x","answers":[3.5436256287]}
{"question":"n a train, it took 3\/4 hour to travel a distance of 52 1\/2 miles. What was the average speed of the train?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"52.5\/0.75=x","answers":[70.0]}
{"question":"Tickets for a raffle are numbered consecutively. If John sold tickets numbered 67 through 186, inclusive, how many tickets did he sell? 117 118 119 120 121","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"186-67=x","answers":[119.0]}
{"question":"F area of rectangle 3\" by 8\" if a circle has radius of 2\"","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3*8=x","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"Wha'ts the LCM of 5, 15, 45?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9*5=x","answers":[45.0]}
{"question":"The formula r=2\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a5L can be used to approximate the speed r, in miles per hour, of a car that has left skid marks of length L, in feet. How far will a car skid at 40 mph?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"40=(25)*y","answers":[1.6]}
{"question":"What is 67 percent of this number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(0.67)*(17)=x","answers":[11.39]}
{"question":"am going to choose 1o f 3 different cereals and 1 of 5 different fruits to add to it..In how many ways can I do this?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3*5=x","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"What number decreased by 20% is 16?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=16\/0.8","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"The number which best completes the sequence below is: 107\u00c3\u00af\u00c2\u00bc\u00c2\u008c 214\u00c3\u00af\u00c2\u00bc\u00c2\u008c 642\u00c3\u00af\u00c2\u00bc\u00c2\u008c 2,568\u00c3\u00af\u00c2\u00bc\u00c2\u008c 12,840. A. 76,400. B. 76,004. C. 77,000. D. 77,040. E. 77,400.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12840*6=n","answers":[77040.0]}
{"question":"What is 5 and 1\/18 divided by 4 and 4\/9?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5.05555555556\/4.44444444444=x","answers":[1.1375]}
{"question":"7% of what number is 105? A. 15 B. 150 C. 1,500 D. 1.5","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.07*x=105","answers":[1500.0]}
{"question":"A rectangle measures 25 cm by 10 cm. What is its area?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"25*10=x","answers":[250.0]}
{"question":"The area of a parallelogram is 36 cm2. The height of the parallelogram is 3 centimeters. How long is the base?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"36=x*3","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"Suppose that blood is 92% water. Find the decimal notation for 92%.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"92\/100=y","answers":[0.92]}
{"question":"long does the nurse allow for infusing 6 ml when the infusion bag contains 150 ml and the infusion rate is 1.5 ml per minute?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6\/1.5=x","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"The least positive integer which, is divisible by 2, 3 and 4 is?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3*4=x","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"tant noodles are only sold in bags of 5 packets.Eac h bag is sold at $2.But Ada only has $13.How Hany packets of instant noodles can Ada buy at most?I ca","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6*5=x","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"An apple costs 35 cents and a pear costs 55 cents. John has $20 and he has to buy at least 5 of each fruit. t is the maximum number of fruit he can buy with $20? How much change can he get back?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5*0.55=x","answers":[2.75]}
{"question":"3 divided by 2.9 te?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"82.3\/2.9=x","answers":[28.3793103448]}
{"question":"Change 225% to a mixed number? 2.5 b22 ..5 c0. 2.25 d.2 25","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"225\/100=y","answers":[2.25]}
{"question":"Find the supplement of 127 degrees? (A)53 degrees (B) 233 degrees (C)143 degrees (D) not possible","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"180-127=x","answers":[53.0]}
{"question":"h Per Person 10 : $34.07 190 : 53.18 191930 : 36.74 1940 : 59.40 1950 : 179.03 1960 : 177.47 1970 : 265.3980 : 570.51 190 : 1,062.86 200 : 2,075.63 y what multiple did the amount of currency per person grow from 1910 to 2000?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2075.63\/34.07=x","answers":[60.9225124743]}
{"question":"gal in 5 min .dI 5 divided into 30 and i wIuld get the answer 6 ?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"30\/5=x","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"What is 600 over 1125 ( thats a fraction) when simplified to lowest terms?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"600\/1125=n","answers":[0.5333333333]}
{"question":"How can 9\/9 be equal to 1 and at the same time be equal to 0.99999 with the repeating bar on the last place?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10*x=9.99999","answers":[0.999]}
{"question":"The product of 2 numbers is 875. There HCF is 5. What'll be the LCM?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"875\/5=x","answers":[175.0]}
{"question":"What is 20 percent of $4,273,000 please?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.20*4273000=x","answers":[854600.0]}
{"question":"Find the range of each set of numbers.e,5 ,4 ,1 ,9 ,8 ,8 ,5 ,2 . i aId them all together,and get the number and divid ite?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9-1=y","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"d: 32 out of 38 in percentage (a. 12% b. 50% c. 55.8% c. d4.2)%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"32\/38=x","answers":[0.8421052632]}
{"question":"area of Lake Ontario is about 8% of the total area of the Great Lakes. Th area of Lake Ontario is about 7576.8 square miles. Wht is the area of the Graet Lakes?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7576.8=0.08*x","answers":[94710.0]}
{"question":"a. A 30m ladder leans against a wall of a building. If the foot of the ladder is 10m from the building. What is the angler the ladder makes with the ground? Let me explain the picture: It's an acute triangle. 30m hypotenuse, 10m adjacent side, opposite side ? and 0ll a - on it is inside the triangle. An","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10\/30=x","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"A solid metalcylinder of radius 6 cm and height 18 cm is melted and recast as cone of radius 6 cm? Find height","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"18*3=x","answers":[54.0]}
{"question":"ap indicates the distannce from rock island to River Bluff as 513 miles. If Mr Morris drives this distance in 9 hours, what is his average speed? (A)ph 60(B)55 ? 3(C)60 ?(D53 mph","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=513\/9","answers":[57.0]}
{"question":"What interest will you pay on a $1000 loan for 1 year if the interest rate is 7%?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1000*0.07=x","answers":[70.0]}
{"question":"peting cost $20 per square yard. You can carpet a room that has a width of 15ft for $800. What is the length of the room in feet?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"360\/15=x","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"If you receive $1,382.50 in commission from $27,650.00, what is the commission rate?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1382.50\/27650.00=x","answers":[0.05]}
{"question":"Te are 80 questions, tre are 48 correct h,w do i fInd the % that 48 is of 80? th","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"48\/80=x","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"pose you have a pipe with circumference 6cm and length 30 cm and that 8 turns of a wire are wrapped around the pipe. What is length of the wire?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8*6=x","answers":[48.0]}
{"question":"tate whether each sequence is arithmetic, geometric, or neither. If it is arithmetic or geometric state the common difference or common ratio and write the next three terms of the sequence. 1) 1 ,3 ,9 ,27, .","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3\/1=x","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"Farmer had 100 cows in winter. In spring the herd increased by 10%. In summer farmer sold 10% of animals. How many cows left?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"110-11=x","answers":[99.0]}
{"question":"This is what is says on the paper Integer Subtraction; range (-99) to (+99) (G) Question: (+9) - (-69)","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9+69=x","answers":[78.0]}
{"question":"a doctor prescribed 36 pills and directed you to take them every 4 hours, how many days would they last?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24\/4=x","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"On a map that Joshua is using, 1\/4 inch represents 150 miles. On the map, he measured 1 and 1\/4 inches from his home to his grandparents' home. Part A: Describe how he could find the number of miles to his grandparents' home. Part B: Find the distance.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"150*5=x","answers":[750.0]}
{"question":"Rt triangle angles are 90 45 45 thThypotanoeeuside is 110cm what the other 2 sides the other 2 sides are the same lenthg","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.707*110=x","answers":[77.77]}
{"question":"angle 1: 15, 20 and 22 Trangle 2: 9,12, 13. 2 Iam supposed to find the scale factor of these triangles an.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15\/9=x","answers":[1.6666666667]}
{"question":"W's 21% 0f 68 and how did you get it?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.21*68=x","answers":[14.28]}
{"question":"You are climbing a mountain and you are below the mountain's peak at an altitude of 8580 ft. The angle of elevation to the peak is 30.5 degrees. The distance (along the face of the mountain) between you and the peak is 7426 ft. What is the altitude of the peak?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3769+8580=x","answers":[12349.0]}
{"question":"How many 10 minutes are in a day?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1440\/10=y","answers":[144.0]}
{"question":"Help with how to convert a mixed number to a decimal or precent.empute 2 1\/5% of 96 miles....","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.022*96=x","answers":[2.112]}
{"question":"have a movie and you have 884,555 views all together and you get paid $2.50 per 1000 views.How much money have you made?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"884.555*2.5=x","answers":[2211.3875]}
{"question":"In a test I got 68% 0 verall. If the test was out of 600, how many marks did I get?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.68*600=x","answers":[408.0]}
{"question":"If 5 boys can pack 5 gifts in 5 minutes, how many boys can pack 50 gifts in 50 minutes?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10*5=x","answers":[50.0]}
{"question":"A 120 lb. student playing volleyball burns 2.7 cal. per min. If she plays for 30 min, how many cal. r burned?spent doing the activity.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2.7*30=x","answers":[81.0]}
{"question":"all of Malaysian rubber, displayed in a museum of science and technology rolled off the 1.25 meter high display table and onto the floor. It bounced, rose to a height of 0.75 meter, and was caught at t top of it's bounce. at fraction of the original height was the bounce height of the ball? A","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.75\/1.25=x","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"What is 23 Percent of 20?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.23*20=y","answers":[4.6]}
{"question":"What % of 0.8 is 0.2?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.2\/0.8=x","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"What is 30% of 20g?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.3*20=y","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"What percent of $1,021,230.14 is $40,997?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1021230.14*x=40997","answers":[0.0401447219]}
{"question":"speed a boat travels is usually measured in nautical miles per hour, or knots. The Staten Island ferry in New York, which provides service between Manhattan and Staten Island, can travel at 15.5 knots. Find the speed in mles per hour (Knit: 1 knot: 1.15 miles per hour.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15.5*1.15=x","answers":[17.825]}
{"question":"How many feet 10000 foot pounds can move a small apple? 10000 foot ponds is equal to 13,558.1795 joules, 1 joule is the amount of force used to move an apple 3 feet","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"13558.1795*(3)=x","answers":[40674.5385]}
{"question":"sa wants to cover a shelf with shelf papers. The shelf is 11.5 in long and 25.6 in wide. Estimate the nearest square inch the amount of shelf papers Luisa will need. 312 in.^2 B.86 in.^2 C.7 in.^2 D.75 in.^2","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12*26=x","answers":[312.0]}
{"question":"$15,155.84 is 2% of what number?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15155.84\/0.02=x","answers":[757792.0]}
{"question":"5 ft 2 in = 4 ft and how many inches?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=12+2","answers":[14.0]}
{"question":"Tobey knows that 1 mile is aproxp. 1imately61 Km.k Wile driving in Canada, a sign reads \" Montreal 220 km\" How many miles is Tobey from Montreal?; Round to the nearest tenth of a mile.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"220\/1.61=x","answers":[136.645962733]}
{"question":"6 is 40% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.4*x=6","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"What is my class rank in percentage if I am 42 out of 341? I in the top 10% or 20%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"42\/341=x","answers":[0.1231671554]}
{"question":"d the angle of elevation of the sun from the ground to the top of a tree when a tree that is 10 yards tall casts a shadow 14 yards long. Round to the nearest degree. A.54 B 36 C.46 D.44","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(10\/14)=x","answers":[0.7142857143]}
{"question":"400 is what percent of 40? . 900 b. 1000 c. 1100 d. 1200","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"400\/40=x","answers":[10.0]}
{"question":"A is at the top left and B is at the top right lower than A. C and D are collinear. C is at the bottom right and D is at the bottom left. D is further than A to the left and C is further than B to the right. Please see the diagram below and IGNORE the dots which are needed to show the locations of the vertices. .... A .........B ...D______________C Angle ABC is 160 degrees. Angle CAB is 10 degrees. Angle ACB is 10 degrees. Angle CAD is 30 degrees. Angle ACD is 70 degrees. Angle ADC is 80 degrees. Find angle BDC.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"80\/2=y","answers":[40.0]}
{"question":"A football team gain 7 yards on the first play. Then loss 9 yards on the second play and gain 6 yards on the third play to get first down they need 10 yards in four plays. How many yards do they need on the fourth play to get 1st down?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4+x=10","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"How do I find the exact percentage off my pay check? do I find out what percent uncle sam takes out of my pay check? In one week I made 1792.00 (Gross) taxes taken out were 424.86 leaves me with 1367.14 (Net). The way I did it was by guessing the percentage but it is off. It's not 24% nor 23% it is in between. 23.7% I would like to know how to calculate the exact percentage?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"42486\/179200=x","answers":[0.2370870536]}
{"question":"If A(-1, 1) and B(3, 1) are the endpoints of one side of square ABCD, what is the area of the square?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4*4=x","answers":[16.0]}
{"question":"Solve for x: 24 is 60% of x?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.6*x=24","answers":[40.0]}
{"question":"How do you get a percent of 120 like 120% of 80 and 80% of 120?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.2*80=z","answers":[96.0]}
{"question":"I scored 35 on a test with 45 questions. What is the percentage I got right?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"35\/45=x","answers":[0.7777777778]}
{"question":"What grade % is 12 out of 14?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12\/14=x","answers":[0.8571428571]}
{"question":"etal strip is being installed around a workbench that is 12 feet long and 2 feet wide. If the stripping costs $7 per foot, find the total cost of the stripping.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"n","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7*28=n","answers":[196.0]}
{"question":"If you worked from 11:00AM till 2:45 PM and got paid at 9.60 per hour.Wwhat does that come to","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3.75*9.60=x","answers":[36.0]}
{"question":"Help with statistics please! If two events are independent then? they must be mutually exclusive b.b. the sum of their probabilitimust be equal to one c.the probability of their intersection must be zero d.d. none of these answers is correctne a December day the probability of snow is .300. The probability of a cold day is .500. The probability of snow and a cold day is .150. Are snow and cold weather independent events? only if given that it snowed b.b. no c. yes only when they are mutually exclusive","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.30*0.50=x","answers":[0.15]}
{"question":"A 5-card hand is dealt from a standard deck of 52 cards. Find the probability, correct to 7 decimal places, that the 5-card hand contains no aces.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1712304\/2598960=z","answers":[0.6588419983]}
{"question":"Water weighs 62.4 lbs per cubic foot. What is the weight of the water in a filled pool 51 feet long? 21 feet wide and 4 inches deep, to the nearest tenth of a pound.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"357*62.4=x","answers":[22276.8]}
{"question":"How to convert a percent into a fraction: just like this problem 37 1\/2?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"y=37.5\/100","answers":[0.375]}
{"question":"Find the value of 7\/15 of 3\/2 feet. (A)\/45 [](B)10 [](C)7 [](D)14","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7\/10=x","answers":[0.7]}
{"question":"A square with a side of 4 has an area that is 80% of rectangle WXYZ. What is the area of rectangle WXYZ? (A)20 (B)200 (C)25 (D)2","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.8*x=16","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"Find the circumference of a circle whose diameter is 8 inches. (Use 3.14 for PI)? (A)24 in (B).96 in (C)12 in","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3.14*(8)=x","answers":[25.12]}
{"question":"63 is 37 1\/2 % of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"63=0.375*x","answers":[168.0]}
{"question":"For breakfast, the cafeteria offers scrambled eggs with one slice of toast or an egg sandwich made with two slices of toast. In fifteen minutes, they sold 22 breakfasts and used 39 slices of bread. Use a model to determine how many egg sandwiches they sold. (A)16 (B) 17 (C) 18 (D) 19","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"39-22=x","answers":[17.0]}
{"question":"Hdo you know that 7 divided by 9 less then a?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7\/9=x","answers":[0.7777777778]}
{"question":"Express 21\/13 as a percent. round to the nearest tenth, if necessary?61.9% b:0 .6% c:1 .6% d:1 61.5%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"21\/13=x","answers":[1.6153846154]}
{"question":"Convert 9.5 yards to feet. Round answers to the nearest tenth. Multiple question? 114 ft . 28.5 ft c3.2 ft","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9.5*3=x","answers":[28.5]}
{"question":"The ratio of cars to trucks is 5 : 2. If there are 140 cars in a parking lot, how many trucks are there?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=280\/5","answers":[56.0]}
{"question":"how many must he buy and sell to make a profit of about 500 cents a store buys oranges at 8 for 5 cents and sell them at 4 for 11 cents.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"660-150=x","answers":[510.0]}
{"question":"A roof rises 9.75 ft over a horizontal distance of 17.24 ft. What is the slope of the roof to the nearest hundredth?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9.75\/17.24=x","answers":[0.5655452436]}
{"question":"your business buys a product for $300.00.your business model tells you to mark up your product 33%. much is the markup?a.1 99.00 b.$109.00 c.$99.00 d.$89.00","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"300*0.33=x","answers":[99.0]}
{"question":"a race car driver traveled 240 miles in 2 1\/2 hours. His rate of speed was? 00 mph b.1 20mph c. 96mph d. 90mph","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"240\/2.5=x","answers":[96.0]}
{"question":"22 is what percent of 92 rounded to the nearest 10th?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"22\/92=x","answers":[0.239]}
{"question":"what does 255 divided by 15 equal?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"255\/15=x","answers":[17.0]}
{"question":"75 is what percent of 80?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"80*x=75","answers":[0.938]}
{"question":"3 1\/2 is what percent of 5?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3.5=x*5","answers":[0.7]}
{"question":"At a Texas college, 60% of the students are from the southern part of the state, 30% are from the northern part of the state, and the remaining 10% are from out-of-state. All students must take and pass an Entry Level Math (ELM) test. 60% of the southerners have passed the ELM, 70% of the northerners have passed the ELM, and 90% of the out-of-staters have passed the ELM. If a randomly selecteds tudent has not passed the ELM, the probability the student is from southern Texas is what?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.6*0.4=x","answers":[0.24]}
{"question":"takes 2 gardeners 8 days to mow a lawn. One of the gardeners is energetic and the other one is lazy. If the energetic gardener can mow the lawn in 12 days on his own, how long would it take for the lazy gardener to mow the lawn on his own?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3*8=x","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"A cube has an edge length of 4 inches. The cube is painted red all over and then cut into 64 cubes of edge length 1 inch. How many of these cubes have exactly one face painted red?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4*6=x","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"what's the area of this Triangle?t coordinates are: (2,1), (3,4), (0,1)","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6\/2=x","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"Find the number of board feet in 80 pieces of lumber, 2\" x 4\", 18'?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1*80=x","answers":[80.0]}
{"question":"the length of one side of a triangle is 5, which of following can't be lengths of other 2? a and 3 b3 and 5 c and 8 d7 and 3 e and 12","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5+7=x","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"width of a swimming pool is 12 ft and the whole area of the swimming pool is 192 ft ( with a little 2 behind the ft). What is the swimming pool's length?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"192=12*x","answers":[16.0]}
{"question":"able wif p rows and q columns is filled with whole numbers from 1 to pq. they are written in increasing order, along row 1, then row 2 and so on. the number 20 is in the third row, 41 is in the fifth row and 103 in the last row. find the value of p+q","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12+9=z","answers":[21.0]}
{"question":"question is find percent notation for 11\/16","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"11\/16=x","answers":[0.6875]}
{"question":"A penquin swims 12 meters per second. How long does it take the penguin to swim 60 meters? a.ec. 8 b.ec. 4 c.ec. 6 d.ec.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"60\/12=x","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"how many ways can a jury of 8 men and 6 women be selected from 12 men and 10 women?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"495*210=z","answers":[103950.0]}
{"question":"what is 20% of 182?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"182*0.2=x","answers":[36.4]}
{"question":"the herkimer COunty Fair, Luke saw a tomato that weighed 2 \/8 pounds. What is 2 3\/8 written as a decimal? e","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"19\/8=x","answers":[2.375]}
{"question":"198 is 60% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.6*x=198","answers":[330.0]}
{"question":"How do i add radical 121 and radical 100 with a radical answer?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"11+10=x","answers":[21.0]}
{"question":"A semicircular window of radius 15 inches is to be laminated with a sunblock coating that costs $0.85 per square inch to apply. What is the total cost of coating the window, to the nearest cent?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"353.25*0.85=m","answers":[300.2625]}
{"question":"number of ounces of water needed to reduce 9 ounces of shaving lotion containing 50% of alcohool o a lotion containing 30% alcohol is?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15-9=x","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"i have 6 briefcases and 2 among them will have 100$.. hat is the probability that you pick a briefcase which has 100$ bill in it..","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2\/6=x","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"els are Five hundred pixels per square inch creates a good picture ho.w many pixels would there be in a 3\" x 5\" picture?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15*500=x","answers":[7500.0]}
{"question":"2 girls can fill 2 notebooks in 2 weeks and 3 boys can fill 3 notebooks in 3 weeks, how many notebooks can 6 girls and 6 boys fill in 6 weeks?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12+18=x","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"write 3\/4 as a percent? 0.75% b.7.5% c.75% d.34%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3\/4=x","answers":[0.75]}
{"question":"speed of light is 11,160,000 miles\/minute the distance from the sun to the earth is 93,000,000 miles.Find the time in seconds it takes for light to travel from the sun to the earth?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"93000000\/186000=x","answers":[500.0]}
{"question":"what is 40% of $65.00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4*6.50=x","answers":[26.0]}
{"question":"What percentage Of 10,016.58 is 35.08??","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"35.08\/10016.58=x","answers":[0.0035021934]}
{"question":"What is 28.4% of 15,000,000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15000000*0.284=x","answers":[4260000.0]}
{"question":"24 is 75% of what number?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24\/x=0.75","answers":[32.0]}
{"question":"mathematical percentage? 16600 out of 19600","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"16600\/19600=y","answers":[0.8469387755]}
{"question":"what is 20% of $62,427.00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.2*62427.00=y","answers":[12485.4]}
{"question":"Amy paid $87.54 for a pair of running shoes during a 25% off sale. What was the regular price?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"87.54=0.75*x","answers":[116.72]}
{"question":"people decide to do podiatry course in total. 2 of them didn't originally make the standard of high school scores to get into the course but were still accepted. many people are in this 2%?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.02*144=y","answers":[2.88]}
{"question":"d the slope of the line that passes through the points (-3, -5) and (3, 2).","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7\/6=x","answers":[1.1666666667]}
{"question":"What is 10 percent of 35 cents?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"35*0.1=x","answers":[3.5]}
{"question":"a class of 32 students, 4 were absent on monday. What percent of the students were absent monday? Ho","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/32=y","answers":[0.125]}
{"question":"ie get a commission in addition to her hourly pay. she earns 5% commission for sales up to 4000$ and a 7% commission for all sales in a month above 4000$. last month her sales were 5400$. how much was her commission. a. 37b. 29c. 27d. dolhanks:) 5 tars","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5400*0.07=x","answers":[378.0]}
{"question":"Subtract 27 8\/9 from 59 5\/12 and reduce answer to lowest terms?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"59.4166666667-(27.8888888889)=y","answers":[31.527778]}
{"question":"How many meters is 63 inches?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.0254*63=y","answers":[1.6002]}
{"question":"What is the probability of getting 1 specific items from randomly chosen 3 items from a total of 8 items?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"m=3\/8","answers":[0.375]}
{"question":"what is the smallest 4 digit number divisble by 5 and 9?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"23*45=x","answers":[1035.0]}
{"question":"i got a 16 out of 26 right, what is my grade?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"16\/26=x","answers":[0.6153846154]}
{"question":"leg of a 45*-45*-90* right triangle is 3\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a2 inches long. Find the length of the hypotenuse.\"","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3*2=x","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"What's 15% of$\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00a34.50","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.15*4.5=y","answers":[0.675]}
{"question":"he man hires a marquee for the main concerts. He makes a scale drawing of the festival field. The scale of his drawing is 1 : 250 The actual length of the marquee is 24 metres. The actual length of the marquee on the plr?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24\/250=x","answers":[0.096]}
{"question":"what is the solution to (sqrt10+(sqrt10+(sqrt10))) ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(3.16227766+6.32455532)=y","answers":[9.486833]}
{"question":"Mr. Hernandez had to interview a total of 63 house holds in his assignment. He has already finished 28. What percentage of the households did he finished? ( Round your andswer to the nearest tenth of a percent.).","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"28\/63=x","answers":[0.4444444444]}
{"question":"to do 35% of 80. co","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.35*(80)=x","answers":[28.0]}
{"question":"if you roll on a number of cube what is the probability of getting a 4?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1\/6","answers":[0.1666666667]}
{"question":"wo number cubes are rolled. What is the probability that the sum of the numbers rolled is either a 6 or an 8? a. 1\/4 b. 5\/18 c. 2\/9 d. 1\/2","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10\/36=y","answers":[0.2777777778]}
{"question":"A bag contains 5 yellow marbles, 16 green marbles, and 2 red marbles. What is the chance of drawing a yellow marble? If a red marble is drawn the first time and then a second marble is drawn without replacement, what is the probability of drawing a green marble? Give solutions exactly in reduced fraction form, separated by a comma.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"16\/22=x","answers":[0.7272727273]}
{"question":"highest wind speed recorded, as of the year 2000 on the top of Mount Washington was 231 mi\/h, which is about 298% faster than the highest wind speed recorded in Chicago. What was the highest wind speed recorded in Chicago as of the year 2000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2.98*y=231","answers":[77.5167785235]}
{"question":"hjust dug a well, trying to figure out how many gallons per minute it is pumping into a 5 gallon bucket. pumped 5 gallons in 1 min 30 seconds. how do I figure out how many gallons a minute?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5\/1.5=x","answers":[3.3333333333]}
{"question":"what number is 45 percent of 20?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.45*20=x","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"takes 60 oz of grass seed to seed 3000 feet squared of lawn. At this rate how much would be needed for 5000 feet squared of lawn?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3000*x=300000","answers":[100.0]}
{"question":"If 1 inch is 2.5cm, how many inches in 20.6cm?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20.6\/2.5=x","answers":[8.24]}
{"question":"If a test was out of 100%, what would a 26\/32 be?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"26\/32=x","answers":[0.8125]}
{"question":"find the greatest common factor 189, 441?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"189\/3=x","answers":[63.0]}
{"question":"What grade is 132 out of 150?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"132\/150=x","answers":[0.88]}
{"question":"ave a 500 gallon tank. The supply pump fills the tank at a 50 GPM flow rate (can fill the tank in 10 minutes) and the draining pump drains the tank at a 85 GPM flow rate (can drain the tank in 6 minutes). How long would it take to empty the tank if both pumps run at the same time? Ca","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=500\/35","answers":[14.2857142857]}
{"question":"3 1\/2 divide by 2 1\/4?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(3.5)\/(2.25)=x","answers":[1.5555555556]}
{"question":"Using the geometric sequence of numbers 1, 3, 9, 27.wWat is r, the ratio between 2 consecutive terms? sSow work .","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=27\/9","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"listing salesperson on a sale receives a $2300 commission. Th seller pays an 8% commission, which is divided between the brokers. Te listing broker pays the selling broker 40% of the total commission, and pays the salesperson 52% of his (the listing broker\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0080\u00c2\u0099s)'share. What is the sale price of the house? Sho work.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(0.02496)*x=2300","answers":[92147.4358974]}
{"question":"What is the density of this object? Ang with a mass of 368gra ms if drop in the initial volume of water which is 48ml if the water rose at 68ml ifthe ring is dropped in the water?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"368\/20=m","answers":[18.4]}
{"question":"What is 0.18 divided by 12?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"m","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.18\/12=m","answers":[0.015]}
{"question":"i says that she is 107 inches tall. Mitchell says that he is 2 yards tall. Kung says that he is 5 feet 8 inches tall. One of them gane an unlikely measurement of his or her height. What is the name of the student?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"107\/12=x","answers":[8.9166666667]}
{"question":"of 10,000 is what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.24*10000=x","answers":[2400.0]}
{"question":"37 and 1\/2% of what number is 60?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.375*x=60","answers":[160.0]}
{"question":"A truck is 26 feet long. Find the length on a scale model if 1 inch represents 5 1\/2 feet. UND TO THE NEAREST TENTH IF NECESSARY.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"26\/5.5=x","answers":[4.7272727273]}
{"question":"If you count from 0 to 100 how many number 7's will you pass along the way?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10+10=x","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"bject traveled for 3 hours at a rate of 30mil es\/hr. and then for another 2 and 1\/4 hours at a rate of 10 and 1\/2mil es\/hr. How many total miles did the object travel?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"90+23.625=x","answers":[113.625]}
{"question":"A backyard has dimensions 3 and 4\/5 yards by 1 and 1\/2 yards. What is the area of the back yard in square?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3.8*1.5","answers":[5.7]}
{"question":"chart shows 17% as some other color eyes, blue eyes at 33%, and brown eyes at 50%The. refore, if there were 82 students in the class, how many students had brown eyes? Show steps.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.5*82=x","answers":[41.0]}
{"question":"ing that ) is the radical sign... uld 3)24 become 12)2?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3*2","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"There are 8 numbers: 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, and 9. t is the probability of getting a number greater than 2 and less than or equal to 5?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3\/8=z","answers":[0.375]}
{"question":"5.4 is to 0.6 as 12.6 is to 1.4?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5.4\/0.6=y","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"What is the actual distance between Houston & Dallas, if the map shows the two cities to be 1.25 inches apart? a map, the scale 1 inch represents 180 miles.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"180*1.25=x","answers":[225.0]}
{"question":"Use the following information to answer the question below. Polly Rhodes bought a car for $9,200. She drove the car 12,000 miles last year. Her car expenses for the year were insurance, $436; gas and oil, $670; repairs, $28; license plates, $42; loss of interest on original investment, $460; depreciation, 18 percent. Find last year's operating cost per mile, to the nearest cent. ______ cents","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3292.00\/12000=x","answers":[0.2743333333]}
{"question":"Write the fraction in simplest form. 66\/116 a. 58\/33 b. 23\/13 c. 33\/58 d. 67\/117","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"66\/116=x","answers":[0.5689655172]}
{"question":"are driving at a speed of 85 km\/h. How long will it take you to travel 255 km? PleS thewor.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=255\/(85)","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"About what percent of 80 is 50?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"50\/80=x","answers":[0.625]}
{"question":"6 is 3% of what numbe","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6=0.03*x","answers":[200.0]}
{"question":"You save 40% when buying a shirt that originally cost $29. How much do you save?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2.90*4=x","answers":[11.6]}
{"question":"paid $140 over the purchase price of $2,300 due to interest. If she paid off the item in 1 year, what was the interest rate she paid? nd to the nearest percent and express your answer as a percent.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"140\/2300=x","answers":[0.0608695652]}
{"question":"I am a number less than 60 two of my factors are 2 and 7 I am a common multiple of 8 and 14?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"14*4=x","answers":[56.0]}
{"question":"How do you convert 6 7\/11 to a decimal? Then round your answerto the nearest hundredth.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"73\/11=y","answers":[6.6363636364]}
{"question":"Determine the smaller angle between the hands when the time is a. 1 o'clock b. 2 o'clock c. 1.30 d. 1.45 e. 1.27 f. 1.52 Find a rule which expresses the angle between the hands when the time is A minutes past B.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"30*2=x","answers":[60.0]}
{"question":"If the clock now reads 10 : 45. What time will the clock read in 96 hours from now?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"96\/24=x","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"what is the answer to 562,867 plus 786,564?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"562867+786564=x","answers":[1349431.0]}
{"question":"Two dice are rolled. FInd the probability that a 5 appears on exactly one die or the sum? Probablity question. Two dice are rolled. FInd the probability that a 5 appears on exactly one die or the sum is 9.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1\/3","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"got an exam, meaning that she earned 74 points out of 80 possible. Write the decimal equivalent of this fraction.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"74\/80=x","answers":[0.925]}
{"question":"whats 30 percent of 270?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"270*0.3=x","answers":[81.0]}
{"question":"re are 71 stamps cost 19 pence by rounding find the approxcosimate t of 71 stamps","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20*70=x","answers":[1400.0]}
{"question":"1 inch corresponds to 15 miles . what is the actual distance between two cities 6.5 inches apart?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6.5*15=x","answers":[97.5]}
{"question":"The student teacher ratio is 27.5 to 1. if there is 42 teachers how many students are there?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"42*27.5=x","answers":[1155.0]}
{"question":"ts 1'5% of $4,630,966","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4630966*0.15=x","answers":[694644.9]}
{"question":"reduce to lowest term 34\/68?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"34\/68=x","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"33 1\/3 % of what number is 36","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"z*(0.33333333)=36","answers":[108.00000108]}
{"question":"heigths its 17m h. much will that be on a scale 1:12 5 0","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"417\/1250=x","answers":[0.3336]}
{"question":"What is 75% of 445?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"445*0.75=x","answers":[333.75]}
{"question":"Nate is working at the concession stand at his brothers baseball game. He only has cola and lemon-lime to drink. He has sold 45 colas and 27 lemon-lime drinks. What is the probability the next person wants a lemon-lime drink? a)3\/5. b)4\/9. c)1\/3. d)3\/8.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"27\/72=z","answers":[0.375]}
{"question":"what is 15 percent of seven-hundred and 58 dollars and 10 cents?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.15*758.10=y","answers":[113.715]}
{"question":"find the area of a triangle whose vertices have coordinates:(2, -5)(6, 1)(-3, -4)?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"34\/2=y","answers":[17.0]}
{"question":"A fair coin is tossed 5 times. What is the probability that exactly 2 heads are observed?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5\/16","answers":[0.3125]}
{"question":"The height of an inclined plane is 2 ft. Based on ADA codes, the slope must be 1 : 12 or less. Using the ADA code, what is the allowable minimum length for the ramps base.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2*12=x","answers":[24.0]}
{"question":"what is 6 over 30?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6\/30=x","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"25% of what number is 20?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20\/0.25=x","answers":[80.0]}
{"question":"uppose you repeatedly roll a die for which the probability of a 2 is 0.7. Let X denote the number 2's you get in 11 rolls.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.7*11=x","answers":[7.7]}
{"question":"The sum of the measures of the interior angles of a quadrilateral is? . 360\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0 B. 720\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0 . 90\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0 D. 180\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"180+180=x","answers":[360.0]}
{"question":"If you count 1 to 100, how many 6's do you pass on the way?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"19+1=y","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"in a class of 55 students, 23 study english, 21 study spanish and 26 study french . 5 study all three subjects. students study both english and spanish, 11 study both french and spanish and 8 study english and french. . how many students student spanish only . how many students do neither of the three subject.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"55-49=x","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"ix people were asked to determine the amount of money they were carrying,, to the nearest dollar. The results were $27, $54, $35 ,,48, $30,a nd $40. lease tell me what the range and mode is.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"54-27=x","answers":[27.0]}
{"question":"In a 100 meter race three students were ale running at a constant speed throughout the race. Greg was 10 meters ahead of Bob, and Bob was 10 meters ahead of Frank. How far was Greg ahead of Frank when he crossed the finish line to win the race?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10+10=x","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"A health research fund drive has raised $18,700. That is 22% of the goal. What is the goal?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.22*x=18700","answers":[85000.0]}
{"question":"What percent of 55 is 20?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*55=20","answers":[0.3636363636]}
{"question":"FRACTION 5\/12 AS A DECIMAL!","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5\/12=x","answers":[0.4166666667]}
{"question":"How could it be that 7 out of 50 is 35%? nd how could it be that 3 out of 50 is 9%?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7\/20=z","answers":[0.35]}
{"question":"howard is flying a kite and wants to find its angle of elevation. the string on the kite is 32 meters long and the kite is level with the top of a building that he knows is 28 meters high. to the nearest tenth of a degree, find the angle of elevation.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(28)\/(32)=x","answers":[0.875]}
{"question":"What's the nth term for the these arithmetic sequence 2, 4, 8, 16, 32?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/2=x","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"Using arithmetic sequence of numbers 2, 4, 6, 8, 10.wWat is d, the difference between any 2 terms?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4-2=x","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"What is 33 1\/3% of 12?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.3333*12=x","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"T won 9 of its 1st 20 gms.HHw many of the remaining 16 gms does T have to win to have a 50% winning record?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"18-9=x","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"What is 1\/3 of $125,000?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"125000\/3=x","answers":[41666.6666667]}
{"question":"325e6.5% is ofat number of T","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.065*x=325","answers":[5000.0]}
{"question":"What's 4\/10 in the simplest form please answer this?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/10=x","answers":[0.4]}
{"question":"Find: 32 out of 110 in percentage. 1% 51% 34.4% 29.1%","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"32\/110=x","answers":[0.2909090909]}
{"question":"Csome one find out what percent of $1.2 Billion of $6 Billion?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.2\/6=x","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"what is the measure of each exterior of a regular 12 sided polygon? . A. 40 . B. 48 . C. 36 . D. 150 . E. 30 . F. 144.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"360\/12=x","answers":[30.0]}
{"question":"269 is what percent of 400?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"269\/400=x","answers":[0.6725]}
{"question":"How many 4 digit numbers have the thousands digit equal to 2 and the units digit equal to 7?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10*10=x","answers":[100.0]}
{"question":"A ball is thrown upward from the roof of a building 100 m tall with an initial velocity of 20 m\/s. When will the ball reach a height of 80 m?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20*x=80","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"What is 35% of $9,252.07?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9252.07*0.35=x","answers":[3238.2245]}
{"question":"Acream is sold in a 34 gram container. the average amount of cram used per application is 2 3\/7 grams. hHw many applications can be made with the container?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"34\/2.42857=z","answers":[14.0000082353]}
{"question":"ox contains 20 numbers. One of the numbers is drawn. What is the probability that it will be even? a \/20 b9\/20 c \/2 d I","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10\/20=x","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"t is the average (Arithmetic mean) of 8,7,7 ,5 ,3 ,2 , ad 2 ? -","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"34\/7=x","answers":[4.8571428571]}
{"question":"Find the least common multiple of 9, 20, and 30?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9*20=x","answers":[180.0]}
{"question":"1, 4, 13, 40, 121 Describe the rule in the pattern and find the next term. Show how you found the next term in the pattern.","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"121+243=x","answers":[364.0]}
{"question":"A black racer snake travels 46.0 km in 20 hours. What is the speed in km\/h?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"46\/20=x","answers":[2.3]}
{"question":"How do you convert 7\/8 to a decimal without a calculator?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7\/8=x","answers":[0.875]}
{"question":"80% of all customers are satisfied .if there are 7840 satisfied customers,h ow many customers are there? 800 customers b. 272 customers c.39,2000 customers d. 920 customers","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"y=7840\/0.8","answers":[9800.0]}
{"question":"How many counting numbers between 100 and 1000 remain the same when the order of the digits is reversed is one of the numbers.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10*9=x","answers":[90.0]}
{"question":"Is the LCM for 6 & 9?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9*2=x","answers":[18.0]}
{"question":"o pass algebra, a student must have an average of at least 70 on 5 tests. On the first four tests, a student has scores of 75, 79, 64, and 71. What possible scores on the fifth test would guarantee the student a passing grade in the class?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"350=289+y","answers":[61.0]}
{"question":"How do u write fractions into decimals? over 20 in decimal form","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"13\/20=x","answers":[0.65]}
{"question":"What would 0.86 be as a decimal with a repeating bar over the 6?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"90*x=78","answers":[0.8666666667]}
{"question":"pecial lottery is to be held to select the student who will live in the only deluxe room in a college dormitory. There are 100 seniors, 150 juniors, and 200 sophomores who applied. Each seniors name is placed in the lottery 3 times; each juniors name, 2 times; and each sophomores name, 1 time. What is the probability that a seniors name will be chosen?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3\/8","answers":[0.375]}
{"question":"2004, there were 653 evening newspapers in the United Stares. This is about 44.8% of the number if evening newspapers were there in United States in 1960. How many evening newspapers were there in 1960? Round your answer to the nearest whole number. P","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"653=0.448*x","answers":[1457.58928571]}
{"question":"What is the fractional equivalent of 40%?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"40\/100=x","answers":[0.4]}
{"question":"Te are 275 members, 36% have been in the band for 3 years. How many students have been i nthe band less than 3 years?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"275*0.64=x","answers":[176.0]}
{"question":"A baseball pennant is shaped like a trapezoid. It's bases are 30 cm and its area is 1440cm2.wWat is its height?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1440\/30=x","answers":[48.0]}
{"question":"Convert 558 centimeters to meters. A 5580 B 55,800 C 0.558 D 5.58","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"558*0.01=x","answers":[5.58]}
{"question":"wrapping a gift, you have a choice of 3 different boxes and 4 different wrapping papers. In how many ways can you wrap the gift? E","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3*4=x","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"eam of clothing workers had an output of 1000 uniforms per week. This output was increased by 20%, which demanded an increase of 50 uniforms per worker. How many workers are there on the team?\"","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"200\/50=x","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"te the fraction 148\/264 in simplest form? A 36\/64 B 37\/64 C.37\/66 D.36\/66","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"148\/264=x","answers":[0.5606060606]}
{"question":"It takes 1.75 minutes to analyze 100,000 sectors of digital space. How long would it take to analyze 7,000,000?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.75*70=x","answers":[122.5]}
{"question":". .265 kg converts to how many g? a, 265 g b, 2.65 g c, 0.265 kg d, 2.65 kg","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.265*1000=y","answers":[265.0]}
{"question":"t percent of 119 is 3? If necessary, round your answer to the nearest tenth of a percent.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3\/119=x","answers":[0.025210084]}
{"question":"Haley's car gets at least 17 miles per gallon. If she plans a trip that is 250 miles, what is the minimum number of gallons she'll need?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"17*x=250","answers":[14.7058823529]}
{"question":"What is 20 percent of 30?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.2*30=x","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"What 60% of a number is 45?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x*0.6=45","answers":[75.0]}
{"question":"What 3 identical numbers can add up to 12?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12\/3=x","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"n was building a new fence, and he wants it to stand 8 1\/2 feet above ground level. To make sure it is secure he must place it 2 3\/4 feet into the ground. How long of a post should John buy? Oions: 101\/2 feet 103\/4 feet 1111 feet 1\/4 feet 1111 1\/2 feet","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8.5+2.75=x","answers":[11.25]}
{"question":"has a part-time job at the fun station. Suppose he worked 13.5 hours last week and ade $81. How much does Ben earn per hour? S","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=81\/13.5","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"Hand what is 11to the negitive 3rd power?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(11)^(-3)=x","answers":[0.0007513148]}
{"question":"Carpet 1 sells for 6.99\/ sq yd. carpet b is a remnant 9 ft by 12 ft sells for 99. you want a carpet that is 9ft y 12ft, will it cost less to buy the remnant or to buy carpet a by the square yard","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6.99*12=x","answers":[83.88]}
{"question":"If an exam is worth 20 pts. and you score 88 correct on the test, what is 88 of that 20 pts?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.88*20=x","answers":[17.6]}
{"question":"I print from an app that produces the following job log. Print size: 22.6 Inch X 16.1 inch = 363.9 SQ. I need to convert to feetHOWhow","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(363.9\/144)=x","answers":[2.5270833333]}
{"question":"Tsum of a number and one is at least 3 and at most 3.wri We two algebraic sentences to describe the number and find the number.","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x+1=3","answers":[2.0]}
{"question":"5 is what percent of 14?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5\/14=x","answers":[0.357]}
{"question":"If the base of a rectangle is 3 2\/5cm and the area is 28 1\/3cm squared what is the height of the rectangle?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"28.3333333333=(3.4)*x","answers":[8.3333333333]}
{"question":"Write o.735 repeating as a fraction?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"735\/1000=x","answers":[0.735]}
{"question":"How many Quarters are equal to $20? 0 b60 c.0 d100","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20*4=y","answers":[80.0]}
{"question":"How long (in inches) is 6 centmeters?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6\/2.54=x","answers":[2.3622047244]}
{"question":"A ski resort boast of having 5 lifts from the chalet at the base of the mountain to the tea house half way up the mountain and 3 lifts from the tea house to the summit. In how many ways can a skier get from the chalet to the summit by taking two lifts?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5*3=x","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"324 is 90% of what number?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"324\/0.90=y","answers":[360.0]}
{"question":"baseball a player's batting average is the ratio of hits to the number of times he or she has batted. Thus, if the plater ter has an average of 00, it means that he\/she got 300 hits in 1000 at bats. In order to have an average of .3000 , ow many hits would the batter have to get in 400 times a bat?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(0.3)*(400)=x","answers":[120.0]}
{"question":"How do I convert 95 degrees to radians?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1=x\/180","answers":[180.0]}
{"question":"the here what you need to average. 9 100 8\/100 74100 3436 1\/20 1830 1\/25 1527 2\/30 3335 2\/24 2628 3840","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"495\/595=x","answers":[0.8319327731]}
{"question":"Choose the best estimate: 37% of 55.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.37*55=x","answers":[20.35]}
{"question":"If the 2 factors are 25 and 12, what is the product?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"25*12=x","answers":[300.0]}
{"question":"Order from least to greatest? 6 9\/20 , 7.42, 15\/2, 7.403","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15\/2=y","answers":[7.5]}
{"question":"A number is drawn at random from the numbers 1 through 20. The probability the number is a multiple of 3 is? A. 1\/3 B. 1\/5 C. 3\/10 D. 7\/20","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6\/20=x","answers":[0.3]}
{"question":"A studious Bruce was walking home from school one day when a sudden rainstorm drenched him his homework. When he got home, he saw that the water rendered his multiplication homework illegible. He did, however, remember that all of the digits in the entire pro.Heere either 2,3,5 , or 7. at was the solution (i.e. the last line) of the multiplication problem? Do","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"775*33=x","answers":[25575.0]}
{"question":"I have to find the average of a weeks takings e.g. 180,120,180,320,245. with the total of 1045","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1045\/5=x","answers":[209.0]}
{"question":"How do you convert to base 10? example: ONVERT TO BASE 10 0100 (it has a little two next to the right bottom) H the hell do you do that?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"16+4=x","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"anta and Cincinnati are 440 miles apart. John leaves Cincinatti, driving toward Atlanta at an average speed of 60mph . May leaves Atlanta at the same time, driving toward Cincinatti in her antique car, averaging 28mph . How long will it take them to meet?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"440\/88=x","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"Explain how dividing $6.75 by 9.","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6.75\/9=x","answers":[0.75]}
{"question":"Which one of the following is equivalent to 7 to the negative second power? a. -14 b. -7 to the second power c. -1\/14 d. 1\/49","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7^(-2)=x","answers":[0.0204081633]}
{"question":"Find time, do you do the distance divided by the speed. This person lives 5 miles away from a store, she is riding her bike to the store at 10 mph. So does that mean I do 5 divided by 10. the answer is 0.50 So whwould the answer be???","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"5=10*x","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"25% of what number is 10?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.25*x=10","answers":[40.0]}
{"question":"6\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a27 \/ 12\u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0088\u00c2\u009a3?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3\/2","answers":[1.5]}
{"question":"n the 7th grade class of 40 students at school #6 surveyed to find out what their favorite course was, 22 students said they liked mathmateics, 18 students said they liked science, and 7 students said they liked both mathmemtics and science. How many students liked neither mathmemtics nor science?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"22+18=x","answers":[40.0]}
{"question":"4 7\/24 minus 3 9\/32","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4.29166666667-3.28125=x","answers":[1.010417]}
{"question":"Express The Following As A Unit Rate. If Necessary, Round To The Nearest Tenth 325.4 Miles On 17.3 Gallons? 18.8 Miles Per Gallon B 188 Miles Per Gallon C.18.809 Miles Per Gallon D.18.81 Miles Per Gallon","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"325.4\/17.3=x","answers":[18.8092485549]}
{"question":"What's 42% of 138?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"138*0.42=x","answers":[57.96]}
{"question":"What is 2% of 5,100?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.02*5100=y","answers":[102.0]}
{"question":"perimeter of a square can be found by adding all four sides together. If the perimeter of a square is 64m, how long is one side? (A) (B)m (C)m (D)m","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4*x=64","answers":[16.0]}
{"question":"What is the lowest common multiple of 24 and 60?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24*5=x","answers":[120.0]}
{"question":"provided with 2 candles *.th are of same length *. h are different in shape *. h burn for 10 min u. lso have a match box u. in a dark room .hHwill u cyoalculate the end of 15min ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"10+5=x","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"What is 10% of 41.58?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"41.58*0.10=x","answers":[4.158]}
{"question":"Need a reduced fraction from 9\/36?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9\/36=x","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"Carlos drove 145 miles from 2pm to 5.30 pm. Find his average speed, rounded to the nearest mile per hour?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"145\/3.5=x","answers":[41.4285714286]}
{"question":"titanic hit an iceberg at 11:59 pm,apr Al 15,1912.The ship sank 7,260 seconds later.At what time did the titanic sink?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7260\/60=x","answers":[121.0]}
{"question":"How much is 3% of $900?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.03*900=x","answers":[27.0]}
{"question":"How do you figure out and express \"7 out of 12\" as a percentage?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"7\/12=x","answers":[0.5833333333]}
{"question":"I have 1.81 days left of vacation time. So I have 1 day and 0.81 (how much time is 0.81 of an eight hour day?)?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.81*8=x","answers":[6.48]}
{"question":"A car travels a distance of 60 miles, the first half at 30 mph and the second half at 60 mph. If a headlight is equally likely to burn out at anytime during the trip, what is the probability that it will burn out during the first 30 miles?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1\/1.5=x","answers":[0.6666666667]}
{"question":"opy machine makes 161 copies in 5 minutes and 45 seconds. How many copies does it make per minute? C ies per minute =","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"161\/5.75=x","answers":[28.0]}
{"question":"1.6 is 20% of what number ?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.6=0.2*x","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"bought a camera of $250 This price included a tax of 8% find the amount of tax paid","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.08*250=x","answers":[20.0]}
{"question":"hysician has ordered 0.32mg of atropine. If atropine were available as 0.10 mg\/ml of solution ho,w many ml would u nyoeed to give? round answer to 3 sig figs","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.32\/0.10=x","answers":[3.2]}
{"question":"What does 3 1\/5 divided by 1 7\/15 equal?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"3.2\/1.46666666667=x","answers":[2.1818181818]}
{"question":"12 is 66 2\/3% of what number?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12=0.667*x","answers":[18.00180018]}
{"question":"What is the product of 6 and 12?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"6*12=x","answers":[72.0]}
{"question":"is 21\/40 closer to 0 one half or 1?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1\/2","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"If you're born Dec 1988 would you really be 20 now? or 19","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2009-1988=x","answers":[21.0]}
{"question":"ry year, x increases by 1.3% or 30 years, 1.3% becomes 1.013 hHdid the answer book get from 1.3% to 1.013?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1+0.013=x","answers":[1.013]}
{"question":"400 students, 360 students are taking a math class or an English course. Eighty-five of the students in math classes are also taking an English class. If a total of 190 students are taking a math course, how many are taking an English course but not a math course?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"360-190=x","answers":[170.0]}
{"question":"What percent of one third be?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1\/3=x","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"The volume V of blood pumped from your heart each minutolues directly with your plse rate p. Each time your heart beats, it pumps approximately 0.05 liter of liter of b od. Write an equation that relates V to P. If your pulse rate for 15 seconds is 12, find o how much blood your heart pumps in one minute. H","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"48*0.05=x","answers":[2.4]}
{"question":"How much do I need to make an hour to make 100,000 a year?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"52-2=x","answers":[50.0]}
{"question":"In 1968, a car company made 30 different models of vehicles. Today, the same company makes 43 models of vehicles. What is the percent of increase in the number of models of vehicles manufactured?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=13\/30","answers":[0.4333333333]}
{"question":"1n96,THEVtheBcivilianRlabor forceEofItheAunitedCstates included7 MILmillionOpeopleD and WERwereEunemployedOW owNmanyOpeople inEtheLcaecilianBlaborRforceRwereEunemployed","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.05*127=x","answers":[6.35]}
{"question":"Solve 5% of 180 is what number?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x\/180=0.05","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"what is 45% of $15,000.00?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.45*15000.00=y","answers":[6750.0]}
{"question":"7% of what number equals 84?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.07*x=84","answers":[1200.0]}
{"question":"In a marathonunners who finish 1th through 75th receive gift certificates ; those who finish 76th and higher do not . f 312 runners participated in the race , ow many did NOTnotceive gift certificates ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"312-75=x","answers":[237.0]}
{"question":"re are three buckets A1, A2 and A3 Buket A1 having capacity of 19 liters and is empty. B ket A2 having capacity of 13 liters and is full. B ket A3 having capacity of 7 liters and is full. A I need is two buckets with 10 liters of water. How?.","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"(13-3)=x","answers":[10.0]}
{"question":"At the company I work for, our service fee is 15% of the original debt amount that a client enrolls into our debt settlement program. I am trying to figure how much debt was enrolled if the company earned a total of $30,000 in fees","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.15*x=30000","answers":[200000.0]}
{"question":"What is the order from least to greatest of 4\/9, 0.4, 0.45?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4\/9=x","answers":[0.4444444444]}
{"question":"What is 33 1\/3% of $250,000.","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.3333333*250000=x","answers":[83333.3333333]}
{"question":"If the markup formula is 40% of cost and the selling price of an iteam is $49.99 what is the cost? $37.76 b.33.33 c$34.33 d.35.71","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1.4*x=49.99","answers":[35.7071428571]}
{"question":"What is 60 percent off a $200?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"200*0.6=x","answers":[120.0]}
{"question":"A wheel makes 2 5\/6 revolutions per minute. If it rotates for 28 minutes, how many revolutions does it make?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"2.83333333333*(28)=x","answers":[79.333333]}
{"question":"What is 20% written as a fraction? (A)1\/20 (B)3\/25 (C)4\/25 (D)1\/5","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"y","noEquations":[1],"equations":"20\/100=y","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"What is the side length of a regular hexagon with perimeter 15 inches?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"15\/6=x","answers":[2.5]}
{"question":"A researcher wishes to estimate the proportion of all adults who own a cell phone. He takes a random sample of 1,572 adults; 1,298 of them own a cell phone, hence 1298\/1572 \u00c3\u00a2\u00c2\u0089\u00c2\u0088 0.83 or about 83% own a cell phone. b. What is the parameter of interest? c. What is the statistic involved? for b. is it the 1.572 adults who own cellphones? forc. is it the 83% of adults who own cellphones?","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"1298\/1572=z","answers":[0.8256997455]}
{"question":"A ramp is 17 feet in length and covers a horizontal distance of 15 feet. It rises vertically 8 feet above the floor. What is the sine of the? A.815 B.158 C.1517 D.817","operation":"Division","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"z","noEquations":[1],"equations":"8\/17=z","answers":[0.4705882353]}
{"question":"7% of 33m?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"0.07*33=x","answers":[2.31]}
{"question":"If acceleration due to gravity on the moon is 1.64 m\/sec\/sec. now your mass is 68kg. what would be your weight on the moon?","operation":"Multiplication","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1.64*68","answers":[111.52]}
{"question":"There were 28 bales of hay in the barn . Tim stacked bales in the barn today . There are now 54 bales of hay in the barn . How many bales did he store in the barn ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=54-28","answers":[26.0]}
{"question":"Mary is baking a cake . The recipe wants 8 cups of flour . She already put in 2 cups . How many cups does she need to add ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=8-2","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"Sara 's high school played 12 basketball games this year . The team won most of their games . They were defeated during 4 games . How many games did they win ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=12-4","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"There are 22 walnut trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant walnut trees today . When the workers are finished there will be 55 walnut trees in the park . How many walnut trees did the workers plant today ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=55-22","answers":[33.0]}
{"question":"Mike had 34 peaches at his roadside fruit dish . He went to the orchard and picked peaches to stock up . There are now 86 peaches . how many did he pick ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=86-34","answers":[52.0]}
{"question":"Joan went to 4 football games this year . She went to 9 games last year . How many football games did Joan go to in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4+9","answers":[13.0]}
{"question":"There are 4 walnut trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant 6 walnut trees today . How many walnut trees will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4+6","answers":[10.0]}
{"question":"Alyssa 's dog had puppies . She gave 7 to her friends . She now has 5 puppies . How many puppies did she have to start with ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=7+5","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"A restaurant served 9 pizzas during lunch and 6 during dinner today . How many pizzas were served today ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9+6","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"There are 2 pencils in the drawer . Tim placed 3 pencils in the drawer . How many pencils are now there in total ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2+3","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"There are 11 rulers and 34 crayons in the drawer . Tim placed 14 rulers in the drawer . How many rulers are now there in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=11+14","answers":[25.0]}
{"question":"Fred went to 36 basketball games this year , but missed 35 . He went to 11 games last year . How many basketball games did Fred go to in total ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=36+11","answers":[47.0]}
{"question":"There are 33 pencils and 44 crayons in the drawer . Joan placed 27 pencils in the drawer . How many pencils are now there in total ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=33+27","answers":[60.0]}
{"question":"There are 33 walnut trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant 44 walnut trees today . How many walnut trees will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=33+44","answers":[77.0]}
{"question":"There are 41 pencils in the drawer . Mike placed 30 pencils in the drawer . How many pencils are now there in total ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=41+30","answers":[71.0]}
{"question":"Sam went to 14 football games this year . He went to 29 games last year . How many football games did Sam go to in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=14+29","answers":[43.0]}
{"question":"Mike has 35 books in his library . He bought several books at a yard sale over the weekend . He now has 56 books in his library . How many books did he buy at the yard sale ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"35+x=56","answers":[21.0]}
{"question":"There are 53 maple trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant maple trees today . When the workers are finished there will be 64 maple trees in the park . How many maple trees did the workers plant today ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"53+x=64","answers":[11.0]}
{"question":"Sally had 13 peaches at her roadside fruit dish . She went to the orchard and picked peaches to stock up . There are now 55 peaches . how many did she pick ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"13+x=55","answers":[42.0]}
{"question":"There were 73 bales of hay in the barn . Jason stacked bales in the barn today . There are now 96 bales of hay in the barn . How many bales did he store in the barn ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"73+x=96","answers":[23.0]}
{"question":"There are 9 crayons in the drawer . Benny placed 3 crayons in the drawer . How many crayons are now there in total ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9+3","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"There are 5 oak trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant 4 oak trees today . How many oak trees will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5+4","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"There are 34 dogwood trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant 49 dogwood trees today . How many dogwood trees will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=34+49","answers":[83.0]}
{"question":"There are 27 pencils in the drawer . Nancy placed 45 pencils in the drawer . How many pencils are now there in total ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=27+45","answers":[72.0]}
{"question":"There are 25 popular trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant 73 popular trees today . How many popular trees will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=25+73","answers":[98.0]}
{"question":"Jason has 676 Pokemon cards . Alyssa bought 224 of Jason 's Pokemon cards . How many Pokemon cards does Jason have now ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=676-224","answers":[452.0]}
{"question":"There are 107 walnut trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant 104 walnut trees today . How many walnut trees will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=107+104","answers":[211.0]}
{"question":"There are 115 pencils in the drawer . Sara placed 100 pencils in the drawer . How many pencils are now there in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=115+100","answers":[215.0]}
{"question":"There are 2 orchid bushes currently in the park . Park workers will plant 4 orchid bushes today . How many orchid bushes will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2+4","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"Sam grew 4 watermelons , but the rabbits ate 3 watermelons . How many watermelons does Sam have ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4-3","answers":[1.0]}
{"question":"Mary had 8 potatoes in the garden . The rabbits ate 3 of the potatoes . How many potatoes does Mary now have ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=8-3","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"There are 9 oak trees currently in the park . Park workers had to cut down 2 oak trees that were damaged . How many oak trees will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9-2","answers":[7.0]}
{"question":"A restaurant made 9 hamburgers to serve during lunch . Only 3 were actually served . How many hamburgers were over from lunch ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9-3","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"Dan picked 9 limes and gave Sara 4 of the limes . How many limes does Dan have now ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9-4","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"Joan picked 43 apples from the orchard , and gave 27 apples to Melanie . How many apples does Joan have now ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=43-27","answers":[16.0]}
{"question":"Joan decided to sell all of her old books . She gathered up 33 books to sell . She sold 26 books in a yard sale . How many books does Joan now have ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=33-26","answers":[7.0]}
{"question":"There are 46 rulers in the drawer . Tim took 25 rulers from the drawer . How many rulers are now in the drawer ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=46-25","answers":[21.0]}
{"question":"There are 33 oak trees currently in the park . Park workers had to cut down 18 oak trees that were damaged . How many oak trees will be in the park when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=33-18","answers":[15.0]}
{"question":"Mike joined his school 's band . He bought a trumpet for $ 145.16 , and a song book which was $ 5.84 . How much did Mike spend at the music store ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=145.16+5.84","answers":[151.0]}
{"question":"Alyssa bought some toys . She bought a football for $ 5.71 , and spent $ 6.59 on marbles . In total , how much did Alyssa spend on toys ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5.71+6.59","answers":[12.3]}
{"question":"Jessica spent $ 10.22 on a cat toy , and a cage cost her $ 11.73 . What was the total cost of Jessica 's purchases ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=10.22+11.73","answers":[21.95]}
{"question":"Sara got fast food for lunch . Sara spent $ 5.36 on a hotdog and $ 5.10 on a salad . What was the total of the lunch bill ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5.36+5.10","answers":[10.46]}
{"question":"Jason went to the mall on Saturday to buy clothes . He spent $ 14.28 on shorts and $ 4.74 on a jacket . In total , how much money did Jason spend on clothing ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=14.28+4.74","answers":[19.02]}
{"question":"Alyssa loves eating fruits . Alyssa paid $ 12.08 for grapes , and $ 9.85 for cherries . In total , how much money did Alyssa spend ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=12.08+9.85","answers":[21.93]}
{"question":"A ship is filled with 5973 tons of cargo . It stops in the Bahamas , where sailors load 8723 tons of cargo onboard . How many tons of cargo does the ship hold now ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5973.0+8723.0","answers":[14696.0]}
{"question":"An oil pipe in the sea broke . Before engineers started to fix the pipe , 6522 liters of oil leaked into the water . While the engineers worked , the pipe leaked 5165 liters of oil . In all , how many liters of oil leaked into the water ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6522.0+5165.0","answers":[11687.0]}
{"question":"Abe 's family moved from the Bahamas to Japan , so they had convert their money into Japanese yen . Their checking account now has 6359 yen and their savings account now has 3485 yen . How many yen do they have ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6359.0+3485.0","answers":[9844.0]}
{"question":"There are 1986 books in Oak Grove 's public library . In addition , there are 5106 books in its school libraries . How many books do the libraries in Oak Grove have overall ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1986.0+5106.0","answers":[7092.0]}
{"question":"There were originally 20817 houses in Lincoln County . During a housing boom , developers built 97741 . How many houses are there now in Lincoln County ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=20817.0+97741.0","answers":[118558.0]}
{"question":"A farmer estimates that he will harvest 48097 bushels of wheat . The weather is perfect during the growing season , so he harvests 684 bushels of wheat than expected . How many bushels of wheat does the farmer harvest ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=48097.0+684.0","answers":[48781.0]}
{"question":"Christina just transferred $ 69 out of her bank account . As a result , the account now has $ 26935 in it . How much money was in the account before the transfer ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=69.0+26935.0","answers":[27004.0]}
{"question":"A dust storm sweeps across the prairie . It covers 64535 acres of the prairie in dust , but leaves 522 acres untouched . How many acres does the prairie cover ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=64535.0-522.0","answers":[64013.0]}
{"question":"Some insects called aphids attack a large farm . In response , the farmer releases ladybugs onto the fields . There are 12170 ladybugs with spots and 54912 ladybugs without spots . How many ladybugs are there in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=12170.0+54912.0","answers":[67082.0]}
{"question":"Last year , 90171 people were born in a country , and 16320 people immigrated to it . How many new people began living in the country last year ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=90171.0+16320.0","answers":[106491.0]}
{"question":"A ship full of grain crashes into a coral reef . By the time the ship is fixed , 49952 tons of grain have spilled into the water . Only 918 tons of grain remain onboard . How many tons of grain did the ship originally contain ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=49952.0+918.0","answers":[50870.0]}
{"question":"To fill an order , the factory dyed 61921 yards of silk green and 49500 yards pink . How many yards of silk did it dye for that order ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=61921.0+49500.0","answers":[111421.0]}
{"question":"A multi-national corporation has 2041 part-time employees and 63093 full-time employees . How many employees work for the corporation ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2041.0+63093.0","answers":[65134.0]}
{"question":"Each year , salmon travel upstream , going from the ocean to the rivers where they were born . This year , 712261 male and 259378 female salmon returned to their rivers . How many salmon made the trip ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=712261.0+259378.0","answers":[971639.0]}
{"question":"A bathing suit manufacturer has a supply of 14797 bathing suits for men . In addition , it has 4969 bathing suits for women . How many bathing suits are available overall ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=14797.0+4969.0","answers":[19766.0]}
{"question":"Before the recent housing boom , there were 1426 houses in Lawrence County . Now , there are 2000 houses . How many houses did developers build during the housing boom ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2000.0-1426.0","answers":[574.0]}
{"question":"A worker at a medical lab is studying blood samples . 2 samples contained a total of 7341 blood cells . The first sample contained 4221 blood cells . How many blood cells were in the second sample ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=7341.0-4221.0","answers":[3120.0]}
{"question":"So far , an orchard has sold a combined total of 9792 pounds of fresh and frozen fruit this season . If they have sold 3513 pounds of frozen fruit , how many pounds of fresh fruit have been sold so far ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9792.0-3513.0","answers":[6279.0]}
{"question":"Recently , the value of Kate 's retirement fund decreased by $ 12 . If her fund was worth $ 1472 before , how much is it worth now ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1472.0-12.0","answers":[1460.0]}
{"question":"The Richmond Tigers sold a total of 9570 tickets last season . If they sold 3867 tickets in the first half of the season , how many tickets did they sell in the second half ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9570.0-3867.0","answers":[5703.0]}
{"question":"Molly owns the Wafting Pie Company . This morning , her employees used 816 eggs to bake pumpkin pies . If her employees used a total of 1339 eggs today , how many eggs did they use in the afternoon ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1339.0-816.0","answers":[523.0]}
{"question":"Students at Arcadia schools are participating in a coat drive . 9437 coats have been collected so far . 6922 coats were collected from the high schools , and the rest from the elementary schools . How many coats were collected at the elementary schools ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9437.0-6922.0","answers":[2515.0]}
{"question":"A company painted some houses in Hancock County white and blue using a total of 6689 gallons of paint . If they used 660 gallons of white paint , how many gallons of blue paint did the company use ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6689.0-660.0","answers":[6029.0]}
{"question":"A cell phone company has a total of 7422 customers across the world . If 723 of its customers live in the United States , how many of its customers live in other countries ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=7422.0-723.0","answers":[6699.0]}
{"question":"Last year , egg producers in Douglas County produced 1416 eggs . This year , those same farms produced 4636 eggs . How many more eggs did the farms produce this year ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4636.0-1416.0","answers":[3220.0]}
{"question":"An oil pipe in the sea broke . Before engineers started to fix the pipe , 2475 gallons of oil leaked into the water . A total of 6206 gallons of oil leaked before the pipe was fixed . How many gallons of oil leaked while the engineers were fixing the pipe ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6206.0-2475.0","answers":[3731.0]}
{"question":"While playing a video game , Paul scored 3103 points . He and his cousin together have a total of 5816 points . How many points does Paul 's cousin have ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5816.0-3103.0","answers":[2713.0]}
{"question":"A construction company is repaving a damaged road . So far , they have repaved a total of 4938 inches of the road . Today , they repaved 805 inches of the road . How many inches of the road had they repaved before today ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4938.0-805.0","answers":[4133.0]}
{"question":"Oscar 's bus ride to school is 0.75 mile and Charlie 's bus ride is 0.25 mile . How much longer is Oscar 's bus ride than Charlie 's ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.75-0.25","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"Karen added 0.25 cup of walnuts to a batch of trail mix . Later , she added 0.25 cup of almonds . How many cups of nuts did Karen put in the trail mix in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.25+0.25","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"At Lindsey 's Vacation Wear , 0.375 the garments are bikinis and 0.25 are trunks . What fraction of the garments are either bikinis or trunks ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.375+0.25","answers":[0.625]}
{"question":"A marine biologist measured 1 fish that was 0.3 foot long and a second fish that was 0.2 foot long . How much longer was the first fish ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.3-0.2","answers":[0.1]}
{"question":"Hannah 's Vegetarian Restaurant bought 0.3333333333333333 pound of green peppers and 0.3333333333333333 pound of red peppers . How many pounds of peppers did Hannah 's Vegetarian Restaurant buy in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.3333333333333333+0.3333333333333333","answers":[0.6666666667]}
{"question":"Blake filled a bucket with 0.8 gallon of water . Later , he poured out 0.2 gallon of the water . How much water is in the bucket ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.8-0.2","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"In Mr. Olsen 's mathematics class , 0.7 the students received A 's and 0.2 received B 's . What fraction of the students received either A 's or B 's ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.7+0.2","answers":[0.9]}
{"question":"1 evening , a restaurant served a total of 0.2 loaf of wheat bread and 0.4 loaf of white bread . How many loaves were served in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.2+0.4","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"Each day , the polar bear at Richmond 's zoo eats 0.2 bucket of trout and 0.4 bucket of salmon . How many buckets of fish does the polar bear eat daily ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.2+0.4","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"0.5 the students in the band are in the trumpet section . 0.125 the students in the band are in the trombone section . What fraction of the students in the band are in either the trumpet section or the trombone section ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.5+0.125","answers":[0.625]}
{"question":"Suzie found 2 worms in the yard and measured them with a ruler . 1 worm was 0.8 inch long . The other worm was 0.1 inch long . How much longer was the longer worm ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.8-0.1","answers":[0.7]}
{"question":"Scarlett made a fruit salad with 0.25 pound of melon and 0.375 pound of berries . How many pounds of fruit did Scarlett use in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.25+0.375","answers":[0.625]}
{"question":"Vince 's bus ride to school is 0.625 mile and Zachary 's bus ride is 0.5 mile . How much longer is Vince 's bus ride than Zachary 's ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.625-0.5","answers":[0.125]}
{"question":"In Shannon 's apartment complex , 0.16666666666666666 the apartments are one-bedroom apartments and 0.3333333333333333 are two-bedroom apartments . What fraction of the apartments are either 1 - or two-bedroom apartments ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.16666666666666666+0.3333333333333333","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"Michelle began her pizza delivery route with 0.5 tank of gas in her car . When she made it back to the pizzeria , 0.16666666666666666 tank of gas was . How much gas did Michelle use ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.5-0.16666666666666666","answers":[0.3333333333]}
{"question":"At the hardware store , 0.25 the nails are size 2d and 0.5 the nails are size 4d . What fraction of the nails are either size 2d or 4d ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.25+0.5","answers":[0.75]}
{"question":"Jonah added 0.3 cup of yellow raisins and 0.4 cup of black raisins to a batch of trail mix . How many cups of raisins did Jonah add in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.3+0.4","answers":[0.7]}
{"question":"When Jake had 1 cat , he needed to serve 0.5 can of cat food each day . Now that Jake has adopted a second cat , he needs to serve a total of 0.9 can each day . How much extra food is needed to feed the second cat ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.9-0.5","answers":[0.4]}
{"question":"While making pastries , a bakery used 0.2 bag of wheat flour and 0.1 bag of white flour . How many bags of flour did the bakery use in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.2+0.1","answers":[0.3]}
{"question":"Kaleen filled a bucket with 0.75 gallon of water . A few minutes later , she realized only 0.5 gallon of water remained . How much water had leaked out of the bucket ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.75-0.5","answers":[0.25]}
{"question":"Carefully following a recipe , Kenny used exactly 0.16666666666666666 cup of oil and 1.1666666666666667 cups of water . How many cups of liquid did Kenny use in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.16666666666666666+1.1666666666666667","answers":[1.3333333333]}
{"question":"Dale 's Vegetarian Restaurant bought 2.8333333333333335 pounds of green peppers and 2.8333333333333335 pounds of red peppers . How many pounds of peppers did Dale 's Vegetarian Restaurant buy in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2.8333333333333335+2.8333333333333335","answers":[5.6666666667]}
{"question":"On a hot day , Sam poured 1 bucket of water into a plastic wading pool . A few minutes later he added another 8.8 buckets . How much water did Sam pour into the pool ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1.0+8.8","answers":[9.8]}
{"question":"As part of a lesson on earthquakes , a science class is researching the movement of a nearby fault line . The fault line moved 1.25 inches during the past year and 5.25 inches the year before . How far did the fault line move in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1.25+5.25","answers":[6.5]}
{"question":"At the beach , Janet and her sister both built sandcastles and then measured their heights . Janet 's sandcastle was 3.6666666666666665 feet tall and her sister 's was 2.3333333333333335 feet tall . How much taller was Janet 's sandcastle than her sister 's ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3.6666666666666665-2.3333333333333335","answers":[1.3333333333]}
{"question":"A farmer started the day with 8.75 buckets of seeds . After spending the morning sowing seeds , she now has 6 buckets . How many buckets of seeds did the farmer sow ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=8.75-6.0","answers":[2.75]}
{"question":"A carpenter bought a piece of wood that was 0.41 meters long . Then she sawed 0.33 meters off the end . How long is the piece of wood now ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.41-0.33","answers":[0.08]}
{"question":"Kelly bought 0.1 pounds of peanuts and 0.4 pounds of raisins . How many pounds of snacks did she buy in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.1+0.4","answers":[0.5]}
{"question":"Kevin bought 2 watermelons . The first watermelon was 9.91 pounds , and the second watermelon was 4.11 pounds . How many pounds of watermelon did Kevin buy ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9.91+4.11","answers":[14.02]}
{"question":"In March it rained 0.81 inches . It rained 0.35 inches less in April than in March . How much did it rain in April ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.81-0.35","answers":[0.46]}
{"question":"Ron weighed 2 colored metal balls during a science class . The blue ball weighed 6 pounds and the brown ball weighed 3.12 pounds . If Ron places both balls on the scale at the same time , what will the scale read ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6.0+3.12","answers":[9.12]}
{"question":"It rained 0.9 inches on Monday . On Tuesday , it rained 0.7 inches less than on Monday . How much did it rain on Tuesday ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.9-0.7","answers":[0.2]}
{"question":"It rained 0.2 inches on Saturday and 0.4 inches on Sunday . How much did it rain on Saturday and Sunday combined ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=0.2+0.4","answers":[0.6]}
{"question":"Pamela bought 9.8 ounces of sugar , and she spilled 5.2 ounces of it on the floor . How much is ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9.8-5.2","answers":[4.6]}
{"question":"Gordon bought 3.42 pounds of fruit for a class party . The class ate 2.2 pounds of the fruit . How much fruit is ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3.42-2.2","answers":[1.22]}
{"question":"Tori was 4.4 feet tall . Then she grew 2.86 feet taller . How tall is Tori now ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4.4+2.86","answers":[7.26]}
{"question":"A carpenter bought a piece of wood that was 8.9 centimeters long . Then he sawed 2.3 centimeters off the end . How long is the piece of wood now ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=8.9-2.3","answers":[6.6]}
{"question":"There are 41 crayons and 26 pencils in the drawer . Sam placed 12 crayons in the drawer . How many crayons are now there in total ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=41+12","answers":[53.0]}
{"question":"There are 41 short trees and 44 tall trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant 57 short trees today . How many short trees will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=41+57","answers":[98.0]}
{"question":"There are 139 erasers and 118 scissors in the drawer . Jason placed 131 erasers in the drawer . How many erasers are now there in total ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=139+131","answers":[270.0]}
{"question":"Joan had 695 Pokemon cards , and 6 were torn . Sara bought 133 of Joan 's Pokemon cards . How many Pokemon cards does Joan have now ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=695-133","answers":[562.0]}
{"question":"There are 112 short trees and 119 tall trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant 105 short trees today . How many short trees will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=112+105","answers":[217.0]}
{"question":"A restaurant made 9 hamburgers and 4 hot dogs to serve during lunch . Only 3 hamburgers were actually served . How many hamburgers were over ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9-3","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"Melanie picked 7 plums and 4 oranges from the orchard . She gave 3 plums to Sam . How many plums does she have now ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=7-3","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"There are 6 short bushes and 4 tall trees currently in the park . Park workers had to cut down 2 short bushes that were damaged . How many short bushes will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6-2","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"There were a total of 8 football games this year , 4 are played at night . Keith missed 4 of the games . How many football games did Keith go to in total ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=8-4","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"There are 9 pencils and 4 rulers in the drawer . Sally took 4 pencils out of the drawer . How many pencils are there now ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9-4","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"Dan had 7 potatoes and 4 cantelopes in the garden . The rabbits ate 4 of the potatoes . How many potatoes does Dan now have ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=7-4","answers":[3.0]}
{"question":"Sara picked 35 pears and 27 apples from the orchard . She gave 28 pears to Dan . How many pears does Sara have ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=35-28","answers":[7.0]}
{"question":"There are 42 walnut trees and 12 orange trees currently in the park . Park workers had to cut down 13 walnut trees that were damaged . How many walnut trees will be in the park when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=42-13","answers":[29.0]}
{"question":"There are 34 pencils and 49 crayons in the drawer . Dan took 22 pencils from the drawer . How many pencils are now in the drawer ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=34-22","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"Sally paid $ 12.32 total for peaches , after a 3 dollar coupon , and $ 11.54 for cherries . In total , how much money did Sally spend ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=12.32+11.54","answers":[23.86]}
{"question":"Dan spent $ 11.76 on a snake toy , and a cage cost him $ 14.54 . Dan also found a dollar bill on the ground . What was the total cost of Dan 's purchases ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=11.76+14.54","answers":[26.3]}
{"question":"Mary went to the mall . She spent $ 13.04 on a shirt and $ 12.27 on a jacket . She went to 2 shops . In total , how much money did Mary spend on clothing ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=13.04+12.27","answers":[25.31]}
{"question":"Dan joined his school 's band . He bought a clarinet for $ 130.30 , and a song book which was $ 11.24 . Dan found $ 12.32 in his pocket . How much did Dan spend at the music store ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=130.30+11.24","answers":[141.54]}
{"question":"Mary got fast food for lunch . Mary spent $ 1.08 on soup and $ 4.80 on a salad . Mary paid with a 20 dollar bill . What was the total of the lunch bill ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=1.08+4.80","answers":[5.88]}
{"question":"For his car , Mike spent $ 118.54 on speakers and $ 106.33 on new tires . Mike wanted 3 CD 's for $ 4.58 but decided not to . In total , how much did Mike spend on car parts ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=118.54+106.33","answers":[224.87]}
{"question":"There were 46 bales of hay in the barn and 32 bales in the shed . Tom stacked bales in the barn today . There are now 60 bales of hay in the barn . How many bales did he store in the barn ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"46+x=60","answers":[14.0]}
{"question":"Mary is baking a cake . The recipe calls for 7 cups of flour and 3 cups of sugar . She already put in 2 cups of flour . How many cups of flour does she need to add ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=7-2","answers":[5.0]}
{"question":"There are 31 short trees and 32 tall trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant short trees today . When the workers are finished there will be 95 short trees in the park . How many short trees did the workers plant today ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"31+x=95","answers":[64.0]}
{"question":"There were 9 red orchids and 3 white orchids in the vase . Sally cut some red orchids from her flower garden . There are now 15 red orchids in the vase . How many red orchids did she cut ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9+x=15","answers":[6.0]}
{"question":"Sara had 24 peaches and 37 pears at her fruit dish . She went to the orchard and picked peaches . There are now 61 peaches . how many did she pick ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"24+x=61","answers":[37.0]}
{"question":"There are 6 pencils and 7 rulers in the drawer . Benny placed 3 pencils in the drawer . How many pencils are now there in total ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=6+3","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"There are 2 maple trees and 5 popular trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant 9 maple trees today . How many maple trees will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=2+9","answers":[11.0]}
{"question":"Tom went to 4 hockey games this year , but missed 7 . He went to 9 games last year . How many hockey games did Tom go to in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=4+9","answers":[13.0]}
{"question":"Sam 's dog had puppies and 8 had spots . He gave 2 to his friends . He now has 6 puppies . How many puppies did he have to start with ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x-2=6","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"There are 39 scissors and 22 pencils in the drawer . Dan placed 13 scissors in the drawer . How many scissors are now there in total ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=39+13","answers":[52.0]}
{"question":"There are 22 orchid bushes and 40 orange trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant 13 orchid bushes today . How many orchid bushes will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=22+13","answers":[35.0]}
{"question":"Mary had 33 Pokemon cards , and 6 were torn . Sam gave Mary 23 new Pokemon cards . How many Pokemon cards does Mary have now ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=33+23","answers":[56.0]}
{"question":"Mike went to 15 basketball games this year , but missed 41 . He went to 39 games last year . How many basketball games did Mike go to in total ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=15+39","answers":[54.0]}
{"question":"There are 43 maple trees and 22 orange trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant maple trees today . When the workers are finished there will be 54 maple trees in the park . How many maple trees did the workers plant today ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"43+x=54","answers":[11.0]}
{"question":"Melanie has 41 books and 31 magazines in her library . She bought several books at a yard sale over the weekend . She now has 87 books in her library . How many books did she buy at the yard sale ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"41+x=87","answers":[46.0]}
{"question":"There were 32 bales of hay in the barn and 26 bales in the shed . Jason stacked bales in the barn today . There are now 98 bales of hay in the barn . How many bales did he store in the barn ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"32+x=98","answers":[66.0]}
{"question":"Jessica is baking a cake . The recipe calls for 8 cups of flour and 2 cups of sugar . She already put in 4 cups of flour . How many cups of flour does she need to add ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=8-4","answers":[4.0]}
{"question":"There are 5 scissors and 3 pencils in the drawer . Jason placed 4 scissors in the drawer . How many scissors are now there in total ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=5+4","answers":[9.0]}
{"question":"A restaurant served 9 hot dogs during lunch and 2 during dinner today . It served 5 of them yesterday . How many hot dogs were served today ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=9+2","answers":[11.0]}
{"question":"There are 3 short trees and 6 tall trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant 9 short trees today . How many short trees will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=3+9","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"There are 48 pencils and 40 scissors in the drawer . Joan placed 29 pencils in the drawer . How many pencils are now there in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=48+29","answers":[77.0]}
{"question":"There are 37 short bushes and 30 tall trees currently in the park . Park workers will plant 20 short bushes today . How many short bushes will the park have when the workers are finished ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x=37+20","answers":[57.0]}
{"question":"Sara's high school played 12 basketball games this year. The team won most of their games. They were defeated during 4 games. How many games did they win ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"12=x+4","answers":[8.0]}
{"question":"Joan went to 4 football games this year. She went to 9 football games last year. How many football games did Joan go to in all ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"4+9=x","answers":[13.0]}
{"question":"Alyssa's dog had puppies. She gave 7 to her friends. She now has 5 puppies left. How many puppies did she have to start with ?","operation":"Subtraction","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"x-7=5","answers":[12.0]}
{"question":"A restaurant served 9 pizzas during lunch and 6 during dinner today. How many pizzas were served today ?","operation":"Addition","noUnknowns":[1],"unknowns":"x","noEquations":[1],"equations":"9+6=x","answers":[15.0]}